YOU.
>>
>> MR.
YOU.
>> MR. TRUMP
>> MR. TRUMP WILL
YOU.
>> MR. TRUMP WILL JOIN
>> MR. TRUMP WILL JOIN US
MOMENTARILY.
-
- IT'S
MOMENTARILY.
- IT'S THE
- IT'S THE LARGEST
MOMENTARILY.
- IT'S THE LARGEST CROWD
- IT'S THE LARGEST CROWD THE
FACILITY
FACILITY HAS
- IT'S THE LARGEST CROWD THE
FACILITY HAS EVER
FACILITY HAS EVER SEEN
- IT'S THE LARGEST CROWD THE
FACILITY HAS EVER SEEN WITH
FACILITY HAS EVER SEEN WITH AN
OVERFLOW
OVERFLOW CAPACITY,
FACILITY HAS EVER SEEN WITH AN
OVERFLOW CAPACITY, THOUSANDS
OVERFLOW CAPACITY, THOUSANDS OF
PEOPLE
PEOPLE INSIDE
OVERFLOW CAPACITY, THOUSANDS OF
PEOPLE INSIDE AND
PEOPLE INSIDE AND OUT.
PLEASE
PLEASE WELCOME,
PEOPLE INSIDE AND OUT.
PLEASE WELCOME, THE
PLEASE WELCOME, THE NEXT
PRESIDENT
PRESIDENT OF
PLEASE WELCOME, THE NEXT
PRESIDENT OF THE
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
PLEASE WELCOME, THE NEXT
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES,
DONALD
DONALD J.
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES,
DONALD J. TRUMP.
[APPLAUSE]
(music)
TRY
TRY TO
(music)
TRY TO BELIEVE
TRY TO BELIEVE WHEN
(music)
TRY TO BELIEVE WHEN THE
TRY TO BELIEVE WHEN THE GOING
GETS
GETS ROUGH
TRY TO BELIEVE WHEN THE GOING
GETS ROUGH THAT
GETS ROUGH THAT YOU
TRY TO BELIEVE WHEN THE GOING
GETS ROUGH THAT YOU HAVE
GETS ROUGH THAT YOU HAVE TO
TRY TO BELIEVE WHEN THE GOING
GETS ROUGH THAT YOU HAVE TO HANG
TOUGH
TOUGH TO
GETS ROUGH THAT YOU HAVE TO HANG
TOUGH TO MAKE
TOUGH TO MAKE IT
HISTORY
HISTORY REPEATS
TOUGH TO MAKE IT
HISTORY REPEATS ITSELF
NEVER
NEVER DOUBT
HISTORY REPEATS ITSELF
NEVER DOUBT THAT
NEVER DOUBT THAT YOU
HISTORY REPEATS ITSELF
NEVER DOUBT THAT YOU ARE
NEVER DOUBT THAT YOU ARE THE
HISTORY REPEATS ITSELF
NEVER DOUBT THAT YOU ARE THE ONE
AND
AND YOU
NEVER DOUBT THAT YOU ARE THE ONE
AND YOU CAN
AND YOU CAN HAVE
NEVER DOUBT THAT YOU ARE THE ONE
AND YOU CAN HAVE YOUR
AND YOU CAN HAVE YOUR DREAM.
(music)
(music) (music)
MR.
MR. TRUMP:
(music) (music)
MR. TRUMP: BEAUTIFUL.
SO
SO NICE.
[APPLAUSE]
THEY
THEY SAY
[APPLAUSE]
THEY SAY WE
THEY SAY WE SET
[APPLAUSE]
THEY SAY WE SET A
THEY SAY WE SET A RECORD
TONIGHT.
[APPLAUSE]
I
I AM
[APPLAUSE]
I AM GOING
I AM GOING TO
[APPLAUSE]
I AM GOING TO MAKE
I AM GOING TO MAKE THE
[APPLAUSE]
I AM GOING TO MAKE THE PEOPLE
OUTSIDE
OUTSIDE ANGRY.
THEY
THEY LOVE
OUTSIDE ANGRY.
THEY LOVE ME.
I
I LOVE
THEY LOVE ME.
I LOVE THEM.
WE
WE HAVE
I LOVE THEM.
WE HAVE OVER
WE HAVE OVER 1000
I LOVE THEM.
WE HAVE OVER 1000 PEOPLE
OUTSIDE.
HUNDREDS
HUNDREDS IN
OUTSIDE.
HUNDREDS IN THE
HUNDREDS IN THE SECOND
AUDITORIUM.
YOU
YOU PEOPLE
AUDITORIUM.
YOU PEOPLE GOT
YOU PEOPLE GOT THE
AUDITORIUM.
YOU PEOPLE GOT THE GOOD
YOU PEOPLE GOT THE GOOD REAL
ESTATE.
[APPLAUSE]
THIS
THIS HAS
[APPLAUSE]
THIS HAS BEEN
THIS HAS BEEN AN
[APPLAUSE]
THIS HAS BEEN AN AMAZING
THIS HAS BEEN AN AMAZING TIME.
I
I KNOW
THIS HAS BEEN AN AMAZING TIME.
I KNOW IT
I KNOW IT IS
THIS HAS BEEN AN AMAZING TIME.
I KNOW IT IS VERY
I KNOW IT IS VERY EARLY.
THE
THE POLLS
I KNOW IT IS VERY EARLY.
THE POLLS HAVE
THE POLLS HAVE BEEN
I KNOW IT IS VERY EARLY.
THE POLLS HAVE BEEN THROUGH
THE POLLS HAVE BEEN THROUGH THE
ROOF.
EVERY
EVERY ONE
ROOF.
EVERY ONE OF
EVERY ONE OF THEM.
[APPLAUSE]
BECAUSE,
BECAUSE, I
[APPLAUSE]
BECAUSE, I DON'T
BECAUSE, I DON'T KNOW
[APPLAUSE]
BECAUSE, I DON'T KNOW IF
BECAUSE, I DON'T KNOW IF IT
[APPLAUSE]
BECAUSE, I DON'T KNOW IF IT IS
ME
ME OR
BECAUSE, I DON'T KNOW IF IT IS
ME OR THE
ME OR THE MESSAGE,
BECAUSE, I DON'T KNOW IF IT IS
ME OR THE MESSAGE, OR
ME OR THE MESSAGE, OR A
COMBINATION,
COMBINATION, BUT
ME OR THE MESSAGE, OR A
COMBINATION, BUT I
COMBINATION, BUT I BROUGHT
ME OR THE MESSAGE, OR A
COMBINATION, BUT I BROUGHT BACK
A
A TERM
COMBINATION, BUT I BROUGHT BACK
A TERM THAT
A TERM THAT HASN'T
COMBINATION, BUT I BROUGHT BACK
A TERM THAT HASN'T BEEN
A TERM THAT HASN'T BEEN USED
COMBINATION, BUT I BROUGHT BACK
A TERM THAT HASN'T BEEN USED IN
A
A LONG
A TERM THAT HASN'T BEEN USED IN
A LONG TIME
A LONG TIME FOR
A TERM THAT HASN'T BEEN USED IN
A LONG TIME FOR THE
A LONG TIME FOR THE SILENT
MAJORITY.
THERE
THERE IS
MAJORITY.
THERE IS A
THERE IS A TREMENDOUS
MAJORITY.
THERE IS A TREMENDOUS SILENT
MAJORITY
MAJORITY THAT
THERE IS A TREMENDOUS SILENT
MAJORITY THAT POLITICIANS
MAJORITY THAT POLITICIANS HAVE
TAKEN
TAKEN ADVANTAGE
MAJORITY THAT POLITICIANS HAVE
TAKEN ADVANTAGE OF.
THEY
THEY HAVE
TAKEN ADVANTAGE OF.
THEY HAVE TAKEN
THEY HAVE TAKEN ADVANTAGE
TAKEN ADVANTAGE OF.
THEY HAVE TAKEN ADVANTAGE OF
THEY HAVE TAKEN ADVANTAGE OF THE
PEOPLE
PEOPLE OF
THEY HAVE TAKEN ADVANTAGE OF THE
PEOPLE OF THIS
PEOPLE OF THIS COUNTRY
THEY HAVE TAKEN ADVANTAGE OF THE
PEOPLE OF THIS COUNTRY LONG
ENOUGH.
LARGELY
LARGELY INCOMPETENT
ENOUGH.
LARGELY INCOMPETENT EXCEPT
LARGELY INCOMPETENT EXCEPT WHEN
IT
IT COMES
LARGELY INCOMPETENT EXCEPT WHEN
IT COMES TO
IT COMES TO GETTING
LARGELY INCOMPETENT EXCEPT WHEN
IT COMES TO GETTING REELECTED.
THAT
THAT IS
IT COMES TO GETTING REELECTED.
THAT IS WHAT
THAT IS WHAT THEY
IT COMES TO GETTING REELECTED.
THAT IS WHAT THEY DO.
I
I HAVE
THAT IS WHAT THEY DO.
I HAVE CONTRIBUTED
I HAVE CONTRIBUTED TO
THAT IS WHAT THEY DO.
I HAVE CONTRIBUTED TO EVERYBODY.
WHO
WHO KNOWS
I HAVE CONTRIBUTED TO EVERYBODY.
WHO KNOWS THEM
WHO KNOWS THEM BETTER
I HAVE CONTRIBUTED TO EVERYBODY.
WHO KNOWS THEM BETTER THAN
WHO KNOWS THEM BETTER THAN ME?
THEY
THEY ARE
WHO KNOWS THEM BETTER THAN ME?
THEY ARE GREAT
THEY ARE GREAT AT
WHO KNOWS THEM BETTER THAN ME?
THEY ARE GREAT AT ONE
THEY ARE GREAT AT ONE THING.
DON'T
DON'T MAKE
THEY ARE GREAT AT ONE THING.
DON'T MAKE WAVES,
DON'T MAKE WAVES, SURF
THEY ARE GREAT AT ONE THING.
DON'T MAKE WAVES, SURF IT
DON'T MAKE WAVES, SURF IT OUT.
GET
GET REELECTED
DON'T MAKE WAVES, SURF IT OUT.
GET REELECTED AGAIN.
I
I HAVE
GET REELECTED AGAIN.
I HAVE BEEN
I HAVE BEEN WATCHING
GET REELECTED AGAIN.
I HAVE BEEN WATCHING IT
I HAVE BEEN WATCHING IT FOR
GET REELECTED AGAIN.
I HAVE BEEN WATCHING IT FOR SO
MANY
MANY YEARS.
I
I PERSONALLY
MANY YEARS.
I PERSONALLY AM
I PERSONALLY AM SICK
MANY YEARS.
I PERSONALLY AM SICK AND
I PERSONALLY AM SICK AND TIRED
OF
OF IT.
[APPLAUSE]
BACKSTAGE
BACKSTAGE I
[APPLAUSE]
BACKSTAGE I MET
BACKSTAGE I MET SOME
[APPLAUSE]
BACKSTAGE I MET SOME OF
BACKSTAGE I MET SOME OF THE
VETS.
THE
THE GREATEST
VETS.
THE GREATEST PEOPLE
THE GREATEST PEOPLE WE
VETS.
THE GREATEST PEOPLE WE HAVE
THE GREATEST PEOPLE WE HAVE IN
THIS
THIS COUNTRY.
[APPLAUSE]
THEY
THEY HAVE
[APPLAUSE]
THEY HAVE BEEN
THEY HAVE BEEN MISTREATED.
THEY
THEY HAVE
THEY HAVE BEEN MISTREATED.
THEY HAVE BEEN
THEY HAVE BEEN TREATED
THEY HAVE BEEN MISTREATED.
THEY HAVE BEEN TREATED LIKE
THIRD
THIRD CLASS
THEY HAVE BEEN TREATED LIKE
THIRD CLASS CITIZENS.
IT
IT IS
THIRD CLASS CITIZENS.
IT IS GOING
IT IS GOING TO
THIRD CLASS CITIZENS.
IT IS GOING TO STOP.
[APPLAUSE]
YOU
YOU LOOK
[APPLAUSE]
YOU LOOK AT
YOU LOOK AT THE
[APPLAUSE]
YOU LOOK AT THE SENATORS
YOU LOOK AT THE SENATORS AND
[APPLAUSE]
YOU LOOK AT THE SENATORS AND THE
CONGRESSMEN.
THEY
THEY RIDE
CONGRESSMEN.
THEY RIDE AROUND
THEY RIDE AROUND LIKE
CONGRESSMEN.
THEY RIDE AROUND LIKE KINGS.
THEY
THEY THINK
THEY RIDE AROUND LIKE KINGS.
THEY THINK ISN'T
THEY THINK ISN'T THAT
THEY RIDE AROUND LIKE KINGS.
THEY THINK ISN'T THAT GREAT?
THEY
THEY MAKE
THEY THINK ISN'T THAT GREAT?
THEY MAKE SPEECHES.
NOTHING
NOTHING HAPPENS.
TWO
TWO WEEKS
NOTHING HAPPENS.
TWO WEEKS AGO,
TWO WEEKS AGO, THEY
NOTHING HAPPENS.
TWO WEEKS AGO, THEY HAD
TWO WEEKS AGO, THEY HAD THE
LONGEST
LONGEST WAITS
TWO WEEKS AGO, THEY HAD THE
LONGEST WAITS IN
LONGEST WAITS IN RECEPTION
TWO WEEKS AGO, THEY HAD THE
LONGEST WAITS IN RECEPTION ROOMS
AND
AND RECEPTION
LONGEST WAITS IN RECEPTION ROOMS
AND RECEPTION AREAS
AND RECEPTION AREAS IN
LONGEST WAITS IN RECEPTION ROOMS
AND RECEPTION AREAS IN THE
HISTORY
HISTORY OF
AND RECEPTION AREAS IN THE
HISTORY OF THE
HISTORY OF THE VETERANS
ADMINISTRATION.
PEOPLE
PEOPLE WAITING
ADMINISTRATION.
PEOPLE WAITING THREE
PEOPLE WAITING THREE DAYS,
ADMINISTRATION.
PEOPLE WAITING THREE DAYS, FOUR
DAYS,
DAYS, FIVE
PEOPLE WAITING THREE DAYS, FOUR
DAYS, FIVE DAYS
DAYS, FIVE DAYS TO
PEOPLE WAITING THREE DAYS, FOUR
DAYS, FIVE DAYS TO SEE
DAYS, FIVE DAYS TO SEE A
PEOPLE WAITING THREE DAYS, FOUR
DAYS, FIVE DAYS TO SEE A DOCTOR.
WE
WE ARE
DAYS, FIVE DAYS TO SEE A DOCTOR.
WE ARE GOING
WE ARE GOING TO
DAYS, FIVE DAYS TO SEE A DOCTOR.
WE ARE GOING TO STRAIGHTEN
WE ARE GOING TO STRAIGHTEN THAT.
IT
IT IS
WE ARE GOING TO STRAIGHTEN THAT.
IT IS CALLED
IT IS CALLED MANAGEMENT.
THAT
THAT IS
IT IS CALLED MANAGEMENT.
THAT IS ALL
THAT IS ALL IT
IT IS CALLED MANAGEMENT.
THAT IS ALL IT IS.
[APPLAUSE]
THE
THE MILITARY
[APPLAUSE]
THE MILITARY IS
THE MILITARY IS GOING
[APPLAUSE]
THE MILITARY IS GOING TO
THE MILITARY IS GOING TO BE
[APPLAUSE]
THE MILITARY IS GOING TO BE SO
STRONG
STRONG IN
THE MILITARY IS GOING TO BE SO
STRONG IN THIS
STRONG IN THIS COUNTRY.
[APPLAUSE]
NOBODY
NOBODY IS
[APPLAUSE]
NOBODY IS GOING
NOBODY IS GOING TO
[APPLAUSE]
NOBODY IS GOING TO MESS
NOBODY IS GOING TO MESS AROUND
WITH
WITH THE
NOBODY IS GOING TO MESS AROUND
WITH THE UNITED
WITH THE UNITED STATES.
THAT
THAT I
WITH THE UNITED STATES.
THAT I CAN
THAT I CAN TELL
WITH THE UNITED STATES.
THAT I CAN TELL YOU.
NOBODY.
[APPLAUSE]
OVER
OVER THE
[APPLAUSE]
OVER THE LAST
OVER THE LAST FEW
[APPLAUSE]
OVER THE LAST FEW WEEKS,
OVER THE LAST FEW WEEKS, JEB
BUSH
BUSH --
OVER THE LAST FEW WEEKS, JEB
BUSH -- [BOOING]
IN
IN FAVOR
BUSH -- [BOOING]
IN FAVOR OF
IN FAVOR OF COMMON
BUSH -- [BOOING]
IN FAVOR OF COMMON CORE,
IN FAVOR OF COMMON CORE, WEAK
BUSH -- [BOOING]
IN FAVOR OF COMMON CORE, WEAK ON
MILITARY.
BUT
BUT THE
MILITARY.
BUT THE IRAQ
BUT THE IRAQ WAR
MILITARY.
BUT THE IRAQ WAR WAS
BUT THE IRAQ WAR WAS A
MILITARY.
BUT THE IRAQ WAR WAS A GOOD
THING.
I'M
I'M THE
THING.
I'M THE MOST
I'M THE MOST MILITARISTIC
THING.
I'M THE MOST MILITARISTIC PERSON
IN
IN THIS
I'M THE MOST MILITARISTIC PERSON
IN THIS ROOM
IN THIS ROOM BUT
I'M THE MOST MILITARISTIC PERSON
IN THIS ROOM BUT YOU
IN THIS ROOM BUT YOU HAVE
I'M THE MOST MILITARISTIC PERSON
IN THIS ROOM BUT YOU HAVE TO
KNOW
KNOW WHEN
IN THIS ROOM BUT YOU HAVE TO
KNOW WHEN TO
KNOW WHEN TO USE
IN THIS ROOM BUT YOU HAVE TO
KNOW WHEN TO USE IT.
THINK
THINK ABOUT
KNOW WHEN TO USE IT.
THINK ABOUT IT.
WE
WE SPENT
THINK ABOUT IT.
WE SPENT $2
WE SPENT $2 TRILLION
THINK ABOUT IT.
WE SPENT $2 TRILLION IN
WE SPENT $2 TRILLION IN IRAQ.
CHINA
CHINA IS
WE SPENT $2 TRILLION IN IRAQ.
CHINA IS TAKING
CHINA IS TAKING THE
WE SPENT $2 TRILLION IN IRAQ.
CHINA IS TAKING THE OIL.
ISIS
ISIS MAY
CHINA IS TAKING THE OIL.
ISIS MAY HAVE
ISIS MAY HAVE IT
CHINA IS TAKING THE OIL.
ISIS MAY HAVE IT AND
ISIS MAY HAVE IT AND IRAN
CHINA IS TAKING THE OIL.
ISIS MAY HAVE IT AND IRAN MAY
HAVE
HAVE IT
ISIS MAY HAVE IT AND IRAN MAY
HAVE IT BUT
HAVE IT BUT CHINA
ISIS MAY HAVE IT AND IRAN MAY
HAVE IT BUT CHINA IS
HAVE IT BUT CHINA IS TAKING
ISIS MAY HAVE IT AND IRAN MAY
HAVE IT BUT CHINA IS TAKING THE
OIL.
CAN
CAN YOU
OIL.
CAN YOU IMAGINE?
WE
WE NEVER
CAN YOU IMAGINE?
WE NEVER DO
WE NEVER DO ANYTHING
CAN YOU IMAGINE?
WE NEVER DO ANYTHING RIGHT
WE NEVER DO ANYTHING RIGHT WITH
CHINA.
WE
WE SPENT
CHINA.
WE SPENT $2
WE SPENT $2 TRILLION,
CHINA.
WE SPENT $2 TRILLION, THOUSANDS
OF
OF LIVES
WE SPENT $2 TRILLION, THOUSANDS
OF LIVES OF
OF LIVES OF GREAT
WE SPENT $2 TRILLION, THOUSANDS
OF LIVES OF GREAT PEOPLE,
OF LIVES OF GREAT PEOPLE, MOSTLY
YOUNG,
YOUNG, BEAUTIFUL
OF LIVES OF GREAT PEOPLE, MOSTLY
YOUNG, BEAUTIFUL PEOPLE,
YOUNG, BEAUTIFUL PEOPLE, WOUNDED
WARRIORS
WARRIORS WHO
YOUNG, BEAUTIFUL PEOPLE, WOUNDED
WARRIORS WHO I
WARRIORS WHO I LOVE
YOUNG, BEAUTIFUL PEOPLE, WOUNDED
WARRIORS WHO I LOVE ALL
WARRIORS WHO I LOVE ALL OVER
YOUNG, BEAUTIFUL PEOPLE, WOUNDED
WARRIORS WHO I LOVE ALL OVER THE
PLACE,
PLACE, NOT
WARRIORS WHO I LOVE ALL OVER THE
PLACE, NOT TREATED
PLACE, NOT TREATED PROPERLY
WARRIORS WHO I LOVE ALL OVER THE
PLACE, NOT TREATED PROPERLY BY
THE
THE WAY.
[APPLAUSE]
AND
AND WE
[APPLAUSE]
AND WE HAVE
AND WE HAVE NOTHING.
IRAN
IRAN IS
AND WE HAVE NOTHING.
IRAN IS TAKING
IRAN IS TAKING OVER
AND WE HAVE NOTHING.
IRAN IS TAKING OVER IRAQ.
THE
THE PARTS
IRAN IS TAKING OVER IRAQ.
THE PARTS THEY
THE PARTS THEY WANT
IRAN IS TAKING OVER IRAQ.
THE PARTS THEY WANT TO
THE PARTS THEY WANT TO GIVE
IRAN IS TAKING OVER IRAQ.
THE PARTS THEY WANT TO GIVE UP,
THEY
THEY ARE
THE PARTS THEY WANT TO GIVE UP,
THEY ARE GIVING
THEY ARE GIVING OIL
THE PARTS THEY WANT TO GIVE UP,
THEY ARE GIVING OIL TO
THEY ARE GIVING OIL TO ISIS.
ISIS
ISIS HAS
THEY ARE GIVING OIL TO ISIS.
ISIS HAS THE
ISIS HAS THE OIL.
YOU
YOU REMEMBER
ISIS HAS THE OIL.
YOU REMEMBER WHEN
YOU REMEMBER WHEN I
ISIS HAS THE OIL.
YOU REMEMBER WHEN I SAID
YOU REMEMBER WHEN I SAID YOU
SHOULDN'T
SHOULDN'T GO
YOU REMEMBER WHEN I SAID YOU
SHOULDN'T GO IN.
REUTERS
REUTERS WROTE
SHOULDN'T GO IN.
REUTERS WROTE AN
REUTERS WROTE AN ARTICLE
SHOULDN'T GO IN.
REUTERS WROTE AN ARTICLE IN
REUTERS WROTE AN ARTICLE IN 2004
THAT
THAT TRUMP,
REUTERS WROTE AN ARTICLE IN 2004
THAT TRUMP, DON'T
THAT TRUMP, DON'T GO
REUTERS WROTE AN ARTICLE IN 2004
THAT TRUMP, DON'T GO IN.
YOU'RE
YOU'RE GOING
THAT TRUMP, DON'T GO IN.
YOU'RE GOING TO
YOU'RE GOING TO RUIN
THAT TRUMP, DON'T GO IN.
YOU'RE GOING TO RUIN THE
BALANCE.
IRAN
IRAN AND
BALANCE.
IRAN AND IRAQ
IRAN AND IRAQ WERE
BALANCE.
IRAN AND IRAQ WERE THE
IRAN AND IRAQ WERE THE SAME.
TWINS.
THEY
THEY HAVE
TWINS.
THEY HAVE WARS
THEY HAVE WARS FOR
TWINS.
THEY HAVE WARS FOR YEARS.
ONE
ONE GOES
THEY HAVE WARS FOR YEARS.
ONE GOES THIS
ONE GOES THIS WAY,
THEY HAVE WARS FOR YEARS.
ONE GOES THIS WAY, ONE
ONE GOES THIS WAY, ONE GOES
THEY HAVE WARS FOR YEARS.
ONE GOES THIS WAY, ONE GOES THAT
WAY.
IF
IF YOU
WAY.
IF YOU TAKE
IF YOU TAKE OUT
WAY.
IF YOU TAKE OUT ONE,
IF YOU TAKE OUT ONE, THE
WAY.
IF YOU TAKE OUT ONE, THE OTHER
IS
IS GOING
IF YOU TAKE OUT ONE, THE OTHER
IS GOING TO
IS GOING TO TAKE
IF YOU TAKE OUT ONE, THE OTHER
IS GOING TO TAKE OVER.
WE
WE TOOK
IS GOING TO TAKE OVER.
WE TOOK OUT
WE TOOK OUT ONE
IS GOING TO TAKE OVER.
WE TOOK OUT ONE AND
WE TOOK OUT ONE AND LOOK
IS GOING TO TAKE OVER.
WE TOOK OUT ONE AND LOOK AT
WE TOOK OUT ONE AND LOOK AT THE
MESS
MESS WE
WE TOOK OUT ONE AND LOOK AT THE
MESS WE HAVE.
WE
WE HAVE
MESS WE HAVE.
WE HAVE DESTABILIZED
WE HAVE DESTABILIZED THE
MESS WE HAVE.
WE HAVE DESTABILIZED THE MIDDLE
EAST
EAST AND
WE HAVE DESTABILIZED THE MIDDLE
EAST AND IT
EAST AND IT IS
WE HAVE DESTABILIZED THE MIDDLE
EAST AND IT IS A
EAST AND IT IS A MESS.
[APPLAUSE]
JEB
JEB BUSH
[APPLAUSE]
JEB BUSH COULDN'T
JEB BUSH COULDN'T --
[APPLAUSE]
JEB BUSH COULDN'T -- HE
JEB BUSH COULDN'T -- HE DIDN'T
KNOW
KNOW THE
JEB BUSH COULDN'T -- HE DIDN'T
KNOW THE DIFFERENCE.
HE
HE COULDN'T
KNOW THE DIFFERENCE.
HE COULDN'T ANSWER
HE COULDN'T ANSWER A
KNOW THE DIFFERENCE.
HE COULDN'T ANSWER A QUESTION,
WAS
WAS IRAQ
HE COULDN'T ANSWER A QUESTION,
WAS IRAQ A
WAS IRAQ A GOOD
HE COULDN'T ANSWER A QUESTION,
WAS IRAQ A GOOD THING
WAS IRAQ A GOOD THING OR
HE COULDN'T ANSWER A QUESTION,
WAS IRAQ A GOOD THING OR BAD
THING?
FINALLY
FINALLY AFTER
THING?
FINALLY AFTER GOING
FINALLY AFTER GOING TO
THING?
FINALLY AFTER GOING TO HIS
POLLSTER,
POLLSTER, AFTER
FINALLY AFTER GOING TO HIS
POLLSTER, AFTER FIVE
POLLSTER, AFTER FIVE DAYS
FINALLY AFTER GOING TO HIS
POLLSTER, AFTER FIVE DAYS HE
SAID
SAID IT
POLLSTER, AFTER FIVE DAYS HE
SAID IT WAS
SAID IT WAS A
POLLSTER, AFTER FIVE DAYS HE
SAID IT WAS A BAD
SAID IT WAS A BAD THING.
THAT'S
THAT'S OK.
THE
THE OTHER
THAT'S OK.
THE OTHER DAY
THE OTHER DAY I'M
THAT'S OK.
THE OTHER DAY I'M WATCHING.
HE
HE IS
THE OTHER DAY I'M WATCHING.
HE IS SAYING
HE IS SAYING WE
THE OTHER DAY I'M WATCHING.
HE IS SAYING WE GOT
HE IS SAYING WE GOT SADDAM
HUSSEIN
HUSSEIN OUT,
HE IS SAYING WE GOT SADDAM
HUSSEIN OUT, DIDN'T
HUSSEIN OUT, DIDN'T WE?
I'M
I'M NOT
HUSSEIN OUT, DIDN'T WE?
I'M NOT A
I'M NOT A FAN
HUSSEIN OUT, DIDN'T WE?
I'M NOT A FAN OF
I'M NOT A FAN OF SADDAM
HUSSEIN OUT, DIDN'T WE?
I'M NOT A FAN OF SADDAM HUSSEIN,
BUT
BUT HE
I'M NOT A FAN OF SADDAM HUSSEIN,
BUT HE RAN
BUT HE RAN THE
I'M NOT A FAN OF SADDAM HUSSEIN,
BUT HE RAN THE PLACE,
BUT HE RAN THE PLACE, AND
I'M NOT A FAN OF SADDAM HUSSEIN,
BUT HE RAN THE PLACE, AND HE
BUT HE RAN THE PLACE, AND HE HAD
NO
NO WEAPONS
BUT HE RAN THE PLACE, AND HE HAD
NO WEAPONS OF
NO WEAPONS OF MASS
BUT HE RAN THE PLACE, AND HE HAD
NO WEAPONS OF MASS DESTRUCTION.
NOW
NOW INSTEAD
NO WEAPONS OF MASS DESTRUCTION.
NOW INSTEAD OF
NOW INSTEAD OF SADDAM
NO WEAPONS OF MASS DESTRUCTION.
NOW INSTEAD OF SADDAM HUSSEIN
NOW INSTEAD OF SADDAM HUSSEIN WE
ARE
ARE FAR
NOW INSTEAD OF SADDAM HUSSEIN WE
ARE FAR MORE
ARE FAR MORE BRUTAL.
WE
WE HAVE
ARE FAR MORE BRUTAL.
WE HAVE ISIS.
WE
WE WILL
WE HAVE ISIS.
WE WILL HAVE
WE WILL HAVE IRAN.
THEY
THEY ARE
WE WILL HAVE IRAN.
THEY ARE MAKING
THEY ARE MAKING DEALS.
THE
THE LEADERS
THEY ARE MAKING DEALS.
THE LEADERS OF
THE LEADERS OF IRAQ
THEY ARE MAKING DEALS.
THE LEADERS OF IRAQ ARE
THE LEADERS OF IRAQ ARE VISITING
THE
THE LEADERS
THE LEADERS OF IRAQ ARE VISITING
THE LEADERS OF
THE LEADERS OF IRAN.
WHAT
WHAT DO
THE LEADERS OF IRAN.
WHAT DO WE
WHAT DO WE GET
THE LEADERS OF IRAN.
WHAT DO WE GET OUT
WHAT DO WE GET OUT OF
THE LEADERS OF IRAN.
WHAT DO WE GET OUT OF THIS?
WE
WE HAVE
WHAT DO WE GET OUT OF THIS?
WE HAVE STUPID
WE HAVE STUPID LEADERSHIP.
[APPLAUSE]
I
I DIDN'T
[APPLAUSE]
I DIDN'T TO
I DIDN'T TO WANT
[APPLAUSE]
I DIDN'T TO WANT TO
I DIDN'T TO WANT TO GO
[APPLAUSE]
I DIDN'T TO WANT TO GO IN
I DIDN'T TO WANT TO GO IN BUT
[APPLAUSE]
I DIDN'T TO WANT TO GO IN BUT I
WAS
WAS RIGHT.
IT
IT WAS
WAS RIGHT.
IT WAS BAD.
AT
AT SOME
IT WAS BAD.
AT SOME POINT
AT SOME POINT WE
IT WAS BAD.
AT SOME POINT WE HAVE
AT SOME POINT WE HAVE TO
IT WAS BAD.
AT SOME POINT WE HAVE TO GO
AT SOME POINT WE HAVE TO GO OUT.
WE
WE HAVE
AT SOME POINT WE HAVE TO GO OUT.
WE HAVE TO
WE HAVE TO REBUILD
AT SOME POINT WE HAVE TO GO OUT.
WE HAVE TO REBUILD THIS
WE HAVE TO REBUILD THIS COUNTRY.
WE
WE HAVE
WE HAVE TO REBUILD THIS COUNTRY.
WE HAVE TO
WE HAVE TO REBUILD
WE HAVE TO REBUILD THIS COUNTRY.
WE HAVE TO REBUILD OUR
WE HAVE TO REBUILD OUR COUNTRY.
WE
WE HAVE
WE HAVE TO REBUILD OUR COUNTRY.
WE HAVE TO.
OUR
OUR BRIDGES
WE HAVE TO.
OUR BRIDGES ARE
OUR BRIDGES ARE FALLING
WE HAVE TO.
OUR BRIDGES ARE FALLING APART.
OUR
OUR ROADS
OUR BRIDGES ARE FALLING APART.
OUR ROADS ARE
OUR ROADS ARE A
OUR BRIDGES ARE FALLING APART.
OUR ROADS ARE A MESS.
OUR
OUR SCHOOLS,
OUR ROADS ARE A MESS.
OUR SCHOOLS, OUR
OUR SCHOOLS, OUR HIGHWAYS.
EVERYTHING.
WHO
WHO IS
EVERYTHING.
WHO IS BETTER
WHO IS BETTER AT
EVERYTHING.
WHO IS BETTER AT INFRASTRUCTURE
THAN
THAN TRUMP?
[APPLAUSE]
THEY
THEY TALKED
[APPLAUSE]
THEY TALKED ABOUT
THEY TALKED ABOUT THE
[APPLAUSE]
THEY TALKED ABOUT THE SURGE.
BUSH'S
BUSH'S BROTHER
THEY TALKED ABOUT THE SURGE.
BUSH'S BROTHER SAID
BUSH'S BROTHER SAID THE
THEY TALKED ABOUT THE SURGE.
BUSH'S BROTHER SAID THE WAR
BUSH'S BROTHER SAID THE WAR IS
OVER.
TWO
TWO DAYS
OVER.
TWO DAYS LATER
TWO DAYS LATER THE
OVER.
TWO DAYS LATER THE WAS
TWO DAYS LATER THE WAS A
DISASTER.
OBAMA
OBAMA SAID
DISASTER.
OBAMA SAID THAT
OBAMA SAID THAT WITH
DISASTER.
OBAMA SAID THAT WITH YEMEN.
HE
HE ANNOUNCED
OBAMA SAID THAT WITH YEMEN.
HE ANNOUNCED YEMEN
HE ANNOUNCED YEMEN WAS
OBAMA SAID THAT WITH YEMEN.
HE ANNOUNCED YEMEN WAS A
VICTORY.
THEN
THEN THREE
VICTORY.
THEN THREE MONTHS
THEN THREE MONTHS LATER
VICTORY.
THEN THREE MONTHS LATER IT
THEN THREE MONTHS LATER IT WAS
VICTORY.
THEN THREE MONTHS LATER IT WAS A
DISASTER.
WE
WE DON'T
DISASTER.
WE DON'T HAVE
WE DON'T HAVE YEMEN.
WE
WE DON'T
WE DON'T HAVE YEMEN.
WE DON'T HAVE
WE DON'T HAVE ANYTHING.
WE
WE SEND
WE DON'T HAVE ANYTHING.
WE SEND OVER
WE SEND OVER TO
WE DON'T HAVE ANYTHING.
WE SEND OVER TO OUR
WE SEND OVER TO OUR ALLIES,
WE DON'T HAVE ANYTHING.
WE SEND OVER TO OUR ALLIES, IF
YOU
YOU CALL
WE SEND OVER TO OUR ALLIES, IF
YOU CALL THEM
YOU CALL THEM THAT,
WE SEND OVER TO OUR ALLIES, IF
YOU CALL THEM THAT, THERE'S
YOU CALL THEM THAT, THERE'S NO
WORD
WORD FOR
YOU CALL THEM THAT, THERE'S NO
WORD FOR THEM.
IRAQ
IRAQ ISN'T
WORD FOR THEM.
IRAQ ISN'T A
IRAQ ISN'T A COUNTRY.
IT
IT IS
IRAQ ISN'T A COUNTRY.
IT IS A
IT IS A CORRUPT
IRAQ ISN'T A COUNTRY.
IT IS A CORRUPT PEOPLE
IT IS A CORRUPT PEOPLE THAT
STRING
STRING SOMETHING
IT IS A CORRUPT PEOPLE THAT
STRING SOMETHING TOGETHER.
IT
IT IS
STRING SOMETHING TOGETHER.
IT IS NOT
IT IS NOT A
STRING SOMETHING TOGETHER.
IT IS NOT A COUNTRY.
WE
WE SEND
IT IS NOT A COUNTRY.
WE SEND OVER
WE SEND OVER TO
IT IS NOT A COUNTRY.
WE SEND OVER TO OUR
WE SEND OVER TO OUR ALLIES
IT IS NOT A COUNTRY.
WE SEND OVER TO OUR ALLIES 2500
HUMVEES.
SO
SO WHEN
HUMVEES.
SO WHEN I
SO WHEN I HEARD
HUMVEES.
SO WHEN I HEARD 2500
SO WHEN I HEARD 2500 I
HUMVEES.
SO WHEN I HEARD 2500 I THOUGHT
IT
IT WAS
SO WHEN I HEARD 2500 I THOUGHT
IT WAS A
IT WAS A TYPO
SO WHEN I HEARD 2500 I THOUGHT
IT WAS A TYPO IN
IT WAS A TYPO IN THE
SO WHEN I HEARD 2500 I THOUGHT
IT WAS A TYPO IN THE NEW
IT WAS A TYPO IN THE NEW YORK
TIMES.
THEY
THEY MEAN
TIMES.
THEY MEAN 25.
THEY
THEY MEAN
THEY MEAN 25.
THEY MEAN 2.5.
THEY
THEY MEAN
THEY MEAN 2.5.
THEY MEAN 250,
THEY MEAN 250, MAYBE.
2500 HUMVEES,
2500 HUMVEES, ARMOR
THEY MEAN 250, MAYBE.
2500 HUMVEES, ARMOR PLATED.
WHEN
WHEN THE
2500 HUMVEES, ARMOR PLATED.
WHEN THE BOMBS
WHEN THE BOMBS GO
2500 HUMVEES, ARMOR PLATED.
WHEN THE BOMBS GO OFF
WHEN THE BOMBS GO OFF YOU
2500 HUMVEES, ARMOR PLATED.
WHEN THE BOMBS GO OFF YOU DON'T
LOSE
LOSE YOUR
WHEN THE BOMBS GO OFF YOU DON'T
LOSE YOUR LEGS
LOSE YOUR LEGS AND
WHEN THE BOMBS GO OFF YOU DON'T
LOSE YOUR LEGS AND YOUR
LOSE YOUR LEGS AND YOUR LIFE
WHEN THE BOMBS GO OFF YOU DON'T
LOSE YOUR LEGS AND YOUR LIFE IN
YOUR
YOUR ARMS.
GREAT
GREAT VEHICLES.
ONE
ONE SHOT
GREAT VEHICLES.
ONE SHOT IS
ONE SHOT IS FIRED
GREAT VEHICLES.
ONE SHOT IS FIRED AND
ONE SHOT IS FIRED AND THESE
GREAT VEHICLES.
ONE SHOT IS FIRED AND THESE GUYS
RUN
RUN AWAY
ONE SHOT IS FIRED AND THESE GUYS
RUN AWAY AND
RUN AWAY AND THE
ONE SHOT IS FIRED AND THESE GUYS
RUN AWAY AND THE ENEMY
RUN AWAY AND THE ENEMY PICKS
ONE SHOT IS FIRED AND THESE GUYS
RUN AWAY AND THE ENEMY PICKS UP
2500.
THINK
THINK OF
2500.
THINK OF IT.
WE
WE NEED
THINK OF IT.
WE NEED THE
WE NEED THE RIGHT
THINK OF IT.
WE NEED THE RIGHT THINKING.
I
I SAID,
WE NEED THE RIGHT THINKING.
I SAID, WHAT
I SAID, WHAT A
WE NEED THE RIGHT THINKING.
I SAID, WHAT A TERRIBLE
STATEMENT
STATEMENT HE
I SAID, WHAT A TERRIBLE
STATEMENT HE MADE
STATEMENT HE MADE BECAUSE
I SAID, WHAT A TERRIBLE
STATEMENT HE MADE BECAUSE WHEN
WE
WE HAD
STATEMENT HE MADE BECAUSE WHEN
WE HAD TO
WE HAD TO LEAVE,
STATEMENT HE MADE BECAUSE WHEN
WE HAD TO LEAVE, YOU
WE HAD TO LEAVE, YOU CAN
STATEMENT HE MADE BECAUSE WHEN
WE HAD TO LEAVE, YOU CAN TALK
ABOUT
ABOUT SURGING
WE HAD TO LEAVE, YOU CAN TALK
ABOUT SURGING BUT
ABOUT SURGING BUT AT
WE HAD TO LEAVE, YOU CAN TALK
ABOUT SURGING BUT AT SOME
ABOUT SURGING BUT AT SOME POINT
WE
WE HAVE
ABOUT SURGING BUT AT SOME POINT
WE HAVE TO
WE HAVE TO LEAVE,
ABOUT SURGING BUT AT SOME POINT
WE HAVE TO LEAVE, WE
WE HAVE TO LEAVE, WE CAN'T
ABOUT SURGING BUT AT SOME POINT
WE HAVE TO LEAVE, WE CAN'T STAY
THERE
THERE FOREVER.
WE
WE WOULD
THERE FOREVER.
WE WOULD LOOSEN
WE WOULD LOOSEN UP
THERE FOREVER.
WE WOULD LOOSEN UP THESE
WE WOULD LOOSEN UP THESE RULES.
WE
WE HAVE
WE WOULD LOOSEN UP THESE RULES.
WE HAVE SO
WE HAVE SO MUCH
WE WOULD LOOSEN UP THESE RULES.
WE HAVE SO MUCH OIL
WE HAVE SO MUCH OIL UNDER
WE WOULD LOOSEN UP THESE RULES.
WE HAVE SO MUCH OIL UNDER OUR
OWN
OWN FEET
WE HAVE SO MUCH OIL UNDER OUR
OWN FEET WE
OWN FEET WE DON'T
WE HAVE SO MUCH OIL UNDER OUR
OWN FEET WE DON'T NEED
OWN FEET WE DON'T NEED THEM
WE HAVE SO MUCH OIL UNDER OUR
OWN FEET WE DON'T NEED THEM FOR
THOSE
THOSE THINGS
OWN FEET WE DON'T NEED THEM FOR
THOSE THINGS BECAUSE
THOSE THINGS BECAUSE OF
OWN FEET WE DON'T NEED THEM FOR
THOSE THINGS BECAUSE OF NEW
TECHNOLOGIES.
[APPLAUSE]
SO,
SO, WE
[APPLAUSE]
SO, WE LEAVE
SO, WE LEAVE AND
[APPLAUSE]
SO, WE LEAVE AND I
SO, WE LEAVE AND I SAY
[APPLAUSE]
SO, WE LEAVE AND I SAY LEAVE
SO, WE LEAVE AND I SAY LEAVE BUT
TAKE
TAKE THE
SO, WE LEAVE AND I SAY LEAVE BUT
TAKE THE OIL.
DID
DID ANYONE
TAKE THE OIL.
DID ANYONE EVER
DID ANYONE EVER HEAR
TAKE THE OIL.
DID ANYONE EVER HEAR ME
DID ANYONE EVER HEAR ME SAY
THAT?
TAKE
TAKE THE
THAT?
TAKE THE OIL.
I
I WATCH
TAKE THE OIL.
I WATCH THESE
I WATCH THESE GUYS
TAKE THE OIL.
I WATCH THESE GUYS ON
TELEVISION,
TELEVISION, POLITICAL
I WATCH THESE GUYS ON
TELEVISION, POLITICAL PEOPLE,
MANY
MANY OF
TELEVISION, POLITICAL PEOPLE,
MANY OF THEM
MANY OF THEM WITH
TELEVISION, POLITICAL PEOPLE,
MANY OF THEM WITH THE
ADMINISTRATION.
I
I THINK
ADMINISTRATION.
I THINK THEY
I THINK THEY MEAN
ADMINISTRATION.
I THINK THEY MEAN WELL.
THEY
THEY DON'T
I THINK THEY MEAN WELL.
THEY DON'T HAVE
THEY DON'T HAVE A
I THINK THEY MEAN WELL.
THEY DON'T HAVE A CLUE.
THEY
THEY SAY
THEY DON'T HAVE A CLUE.
THEY SAY ISN'T
THEY SAY ISN'T THAT
THEY DON'T HAVE A CLUE.
THEY SAY ISN'T THAT SILLY?
HE
HE SAYS
THEY SAY ISN'T THAT SILLY?
HE SAYS TAKE
HE SAYS TAKE THE
THEY SAY ISN'T THAT SILLY?
HE SAYS TAKE THE OIL.
YOU
YOU KNOW
HE SAYS TAKE THE OIL.
YOU KNOW WHERE
YOU KNOW WHERE IS
HE SAYS TAKE THE OIL.
YOU KNOW WHERE IS THE
YOU KNOW WHERE IS THE OIL
HE SAYS TAKE THE OIL.
YOU KNOW WHERE IS THE OIL NOW?
IRAN
IRAN AND
YOU KNOW WHERE IS THE OIL NOW?
IRAN AND ISIS.
EVERYBODY
EVERYBODY HAS
IRAN AND ISIS.
EVERYBODY HAS IT
EVERYBODY HAS IT BUT
IRAN AND ISIS.
EVERYBODY HAS IT BUT US.
[LAUGHTER]
IT
IT IS
[LAUGHTER]
IT IS HARD
IT IS HARD TO
[LAUGHTER]
IT IS HARD TO BELIEVE.
WE
WE NEED
IT IS HARD TO BELIEVE.
WE NEED GENERAL
WE NEED GENERAL DOUGLAS
MACARTHUR.
I
I THOUGHT
MACARTHUR.
I THOUGHT HE
I THOUGHT HE WAS
MACARTHUR.
I THOUGHT HE WAS GREAT.
THE
THE HIGHEST
I THOUGHT HE WAS GREAT.
THE HIGHEST ACADEMIC.
I
I WENT
THE HIGHEST ACADEMIC.
I WENT TO
I WENT TO A
THE HIGHEST ACADEMIC.
I WENT TO A REALLY
I WENT TO A REALLY GOOD
THE HIGHEST ACADEMIC.
I WENT TO A REALLY GOOD SCHOOL,
YOU
YOU HAD
I WENT TO A REALLY GOOD SCHOOL,
YOU HAD TO
YOU HAD TO BE
I WENT TO A REALLY GOOD SCHOOL,
YOU HAD TO BE SMART
YOU HAD TO BE SMART TO
I WENT TO A REALLY GOOD SCHOOL,
YOU HAD TO BE SMART TO GET
YOU HAD TO BE SMART TO GET IN.
THAT
THAT WAS
YOU HAD TO BE SMART TO GET IN.
THAT WAS BEFORE
THAT WAS BEFORE I
YOU HAD TO BE SMART TO GET IN.
THAT WAS BEFORE I WAS
THAT WAS BEFORE I WAS TRUMP.
BUT
BUT YOU
THAT WAS BEFORE I WAS TRUMP.
BUT YOU HAVE
BUT YOU HAVE TO
THAT WAS BEFORE I WAS TRUMP.
BUT YOU HAVE TO BE
BUT YOU HAVE TO BE REALLY
THAT WAS BEFORE I WAS TRUMP.
BUT YOU HAVE TO BE REALLY SMART.
THAT
THAT IS
BUT YOU HAVE TO BE REALLY SMART.
THAT IS THE
THAT IS THE HARDEST
BUT YOU HAVE TO BE REALLY SMART.
THAT IS THE HARDEST ONE.
EVEN
EVEN THEN,
THAT IS THE HARDEST ONE.
EVEN THEN, BY
EVEN THEN, BY THE
THAT IS THE HARDEST ONE.
EVEN THEN, BY THE WAY.
GENERAL
GENERAL DOUGLAS
EVEN THEN, BY THE WAY.
GENERAL DOUGLAS MACARTHUR
GENERAL DOUGLAS MACARTHUR TO
THIS
THIS DAY
GENERAL DOUGLAS MACARTHUR TO
THIS DAY WAS
THIS DAY WAS THE
GENERAL DOUGLAS MACARTHUR TO
THIS DAY WAS THE GREATEST
STUDENTS
STUDENTS IN
THIS DAY WAS THE GREATEST
STUDENTS IN THE
STUDENTS IN THE HISTORY
THIS DAY WAS THE GREATEST
STUDENTS IN THE HISTORY OF
STUDENTS IN THE HISTORY OF WEST
POINT
POINT PLUS
STUDENTS IN THE HISTORY OF WEST
POINT PLUS HE
POINT PLUS HE HAD
STUDENTS IN THE HISTORY OF WEST
POINT PLUS HE HAD THE
POINT PLUS HE HAD THE LOOK,
STUDENTS IN THE HISTORY OF WEST
POINT PLUS HE HAD THE LOOK, HE
HAD
HAD THE
POINT PLUS HE HAD THE LOOK, HE
HAD THE WHOLE
HAD THE WHOLE DEAL.
HE
HE WAS
HAD THE WHOLE DEAL.
HE WAS A
HE WAS A GENERAL.
I
I DON'T
HE WAS A GENERAL.
I DON'T SEE
I DON'T SEE IT
HE WAS A GENERAL.
I DON'T SEE IT NOW
I DON'T SEE IT NOW SO
HE WAS A GENERAL.
I DON'T SEE IT NOW SO MUCH.
I
I DON'T
I DON'T SEE IT NOW SO MUCH.
I DON'T WANT
I DON'T WANT TO
I DON'T SEE IT NOW SO MUCH.
I DON'T WANT TO KNOCK
I DON'T WANT TO KNOCK THE
GENERALS
GENERALS BUT
I DON'T WANT TO KNOCK THE
GENERALS BUT I
GENERALS BUT I SEE
I DON'T WANT TO KNOCK THE
GENERALS BUT I SEE SOME
GENERALS BUT I SEE SOME OF
I DON'T WANT TO KNOCK THE
GENERALS BUT I SEE SOME OF THESE
GUYS.
CAN
CAN WE
GUYS.
CAN WE DEFEAT
CAN WE DEFEAT ISIS?
I
I DON'T
CAN WE DEFEAT ISIS?
I DON'T THINK
I DON'T THINK SO.
I
I DON'T
I DON'T THINK SO.
I DON'T WANT
I DON'T WANT TO
I DON'T THINK SO.
I DON'T WANT TO USE
I DON'T WANT TO USE NAMES.
[LAUGHTER]
THEN
THEN YOU
[LAUGHTER]
THEN YOU HAVE
THEN YOU HAVE GENERAL
[LAUGHTER]
THEN YOU HAVE GENERAL GEORGE
PATTON.
[APPLAUSE]
DO
DO YOU
[APPLAUSE]
DO YOU THINK
DO YOU THINK GENERAL
[APPLAUSE]
DO YOU THINK GENERAL PATTON,
WHEN
WHEN PRESIDENT
DO YOU THINK GENERAL PATTON,
WHEN PRESIDENT OBAMA
WHEN PRESIDENT OBAMA SAID
DO YOU THINK GENERAL PATTON,
WHEN PRESIDENT OBAMA SAID WE
WERE
WERE GOING
WHEN PRESIDENT OBAMA SAID WE
WERE GOING TO
WERE GOING TO ATTACK
WHEN PRESIDENT OBAMA SAID WE
WERE GOING TO ATTACK A
WERE GOING TO ATTACK A CERTAIN
CITY
CITY AND
WERE GOING TO ATTACK A CERTAIN
CITY AND HE
CITY AND HE SAID
WERE GOING TO ATTACK A CERTAIN
CITY AND HE SAID IN
CITY AND HE SAID IN TWO
WERE GOING TO ATTACK A CERTAIN
CITY AND HE SAID IN TWO WEEKS
CITY AND HE SAID IN TWO WEEKS WE
ARE
ARE GOING
CITY AND HE SAID IN TWO WEEKS WE
ARE GOING TO
ARE GOING TO ATTACK
CITY AND HE SAID IN TWO WEEKS WE
ARE GOING TO ATTACK THIS
ARE GOING TO ATTACK THIS CITY,
AND
AND WE'RE
ARE GOING TO ATTACK THIS CITY,
AND WE'RE GOING
AND WE'RE GOING TO
ARE GOING TO ATTACK THIS CITY,
AND WE'RE GOING TO ATTACK
AND WE'RE GOING TO ATTACK FROM
THE
THE FRONT,
AND WE'RE GOING TO ATTACK FROM
THE FRONT, AND
THE FRONT, AND WE
AND WE'RE GOING TO ATTACK FROM
THE FRONT, AND WE WANT
THE FRONT, AND WE WANT TO
AND WE'RE GOING TO ATTACK FROM
THE FRONT, AND WE WANT TO USE
DRONES.
THE
THE ENEMY
DRONES.
THE ENEMY IS
THE ENEMY IS SAYING
DRONES.
THE ENEMY IS SAYING --
THE ENEMY IS SAYING -- IT
DRONES.
THE ENEMY IS SAYING -- IT IS
BRUTAL.
IT
IT TURNED
BRUTAL.
IT TURNED OUT
IT TURNED OUT TO
BRUTAL.
IT TURNED OUT TO BE
IT TURNED OUT TO BE A
BRUTAL.
IT TURNED OUT TO BE A BRUTAL
SITUATION.
I
I SAID
SITUATION.
I SAID THAT
I SAID THAT IS
SITUATION.
I SAID THAT IS GREAT.
THAT
THAT IS
I SAID THAT IS GREAT.
THAT IS CAMOUFLAGE.
WHAT
WHAT A
THAT IS CAMOUFLAGE.
WHAT A SMART
WHAT A SMART THING
THAT IS CAMOUFLAGE.
WHAT A SMART THING HE
WHAT A SMART THING HE IS
THAT IS CAMOUFLAGE.
WHAT A SMART THING HE IS DOING.
HE
HE IS
WHAT A SMART THING HE IS DOING.
HE IS PROBABLY
HE IS PROBABLY GOING
WHAT A SMART THING HE IS DOING.
HE IS PROBABLY GOING TO
HE IS PROBABLY GOING TO DO
WHAT A SMART THING HE IS DOING.
HE IS PROBABLY GOING TO DO THE
OPPOSITE.
IT
IT WAS
OPPOSITE.
IT WAS THE
IT WAS THE CRAZIEST
OPPOSITE.
IT WAS THE CRAZIEST THING
IT WAS THE CRAZIEST THING I'VE
EVER
EVER SEEN.
SOMETHING
SOMETHING THAT
EVER SEEN.
SOMETHING THAT SHOULD
SOMETHING THAT SHOULD HAVE
EVER SEEN.
SOMETHING THAT SHOULD HAVE TAKEN
24 HOURS,
24 HOURS, IT
SOMETHING THAT SHOULD HAVE TAKEN
24 HOURS, IT WAS
24 HOURS, IT WAS MONTHS.
I
I WONDER
24 HOURS, IT WAS MONTHS.
I WONDER WHAT
I WONDER WHAT GENERAL
24 HOURS, IT WAS MONTHS.
I WONDER WHAT GENERAL MACARTHUR
AND
AND GENERAL
I WONDER WHAT GENERAL MACARTHUR
AND GENERAL PATTON
AND GENERAL PATTON ARE
I WONDER WHAT GENERAL MACARTHUR
AND GENERAL PATTON ARE DOING
AND GENERAL PATTON ARE DOING NOW
IN
IN THEIR
AND GENERAL PATTON ARE DOING NOW
IN THEIR GRAVES?
SPINNING.
SAYING
SAYING I
SPINNING.
SAYING I DON'T
SAYING I DON'T BELIEVE
SPINNING.
SAYING I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
I
I DON'T
SAYING I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
I DON'T BELIEVE
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
WE
WE HAVE
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
WE HAVE SUCH
WE HAVE SUCH A
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
WE HAVE SUCH A GREAT
WE HAVE SUCH A GREAT COUNTRY
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
WE HAVE SUCH A GREAT COUNTRY BUT
WE
WE HAVE
WE HAVE SUCH A GREAT COUNTRY BUT
WE HAVE GONE
WE HAVE GONE DOWN
WE HAVE SUCH A GREAT COUNTRY BUT
WE HAVE GONE DOWN SO
WE HAVE GONE DOWN SO FAR.
CHINA
CHINA YESTERDAY,
WE HAVE GONE DOWN SO FAR.
CHINA YESTERDAY, I'M
CHINA YESTERDAY, I'M BIG
WE HAVE GONE DOWN SO FAR.
CHINA YESTERDAY, I'M BIG IN
CHINA YESTERDAY, I'M BIG IN THE
WORLD
WORLD OF
CHINA YESTERDAY, I'M BIG IN THE
WORLD OF FINANCIAL,
WORLD OF FINANCIAL, CNN
CHINA YESTERDAY, I'M BIG IN THE
WORLD OF FINANCIAL, CNN DID
WORLD OF FINANCIAL, CNN DID A
POLL,
POLL, I
WORLD OF FINANCIAL, CNN DID A
POLL, I WAS
POLL, I WAS THROUGH
WORLD OF FINANCIAL, CNN DID A
POLL, I WAS THROUGH THE
POLL, I WAS THROUGH THE ROOF
WORLD OF FINANCIAL, CNN DID A
POLL, I WAS THROUGH THE ROOF ON
THE
THE ECONOMY.
I
I HAVE
THE ECONOMY.
I HAVE TO
I HAVE TO BE
THE ECONOMY.
I HAVE TO BE ACCURATE
I HAVE TO BE ACCURATE BECAUSE
OTHERWISE
OTHERWISE THEY
I HAVE TO BE ACCURATE BECAUSE
OTHERWISE THEY WILL
OTHERWISE THEY WILL HAVE
I HAVE TO BE ACCURATE BECAUSE
OTHERWISE THEY WILL HAVE A
OTHERWISE THEY WILL HAVE A FRONT
PAGE
PAGE STORY
OTHERWISE THEY WILL HAVE A FRONT
PAGE STORY THAT
PAGE STORY THAT I
OTHERWISE THEY WILL HAVE A FRONT
PAGE STORY THAT I WAS
PAGE STORY THAT I WAS FALSE.
OTHERWISE THEY WILL HAVE A FRONT
PAGE STORY THAT I WAS FALSE. I
WAS
WAS MANY
PAGE STORY THAT I WAS FALSE. I
WAS MANY TIMES
WAS MANY TIMES OVER
PAGE STORY THAT I WAS FALSE. I
WAS MANY TIMES OVER NUMBER
WAS MANY TIMES OVER NUMBER TWO.
IT
IT IS
WAS MANY TIMES OVER NUMBER TWO.
IT IS A
IT IS A PRETTY
WAS MANY TIMES OVER NUMBER TWO.
IT IS A PRETTY IMPORTANT
SUBJECT.
LEADERSHIP.
I
I KILLED
LEADERSHIP.
I KILLED EVERYBODY
I KILLED EVERYBODY ON
LEADERSHIP.
I
I DID
LEADERSHIP.
I DID GREAT
I DID GREAT ON
LEADERSHIP.
I DID GREAT ON THE
I DID GREAT ON THE MILITARY.
I
I THINK
I DID GREAT ON THE MILITARY.
I THINK THE
I THINK THE MILITARY
I DID GREAT ON THE MILITARY.
I THINK THE MILITARY WOULD
I THINK THE MILITARY WOULD BE
JUST
JUST AS
I THINK THE MILITARY WOULD BE
JUST AS GOOD
JUST AS GOOD AS
I THINK THE MILITARY WOULD BE
JUST AS GOOD AS THE
JUST AS GOOD AS THE ECONOMIC
I THINK THE MILITARY WOULD BE
JUST AS GOOD AS THE ECONOMIC FOR
ME
ME PERSONALLY.
THESE
THESE POOR
ME PERSONALLY.
THESE POOR PEOPLE.
I
I WOULD
THESE POOR PEOPLE.
I WOULD BE
I WOULD BE CREATING
THESE POOR PEOPLE.
I WOULD BE CREATING THINGS
I WOULD BE CREATING THINGS THAT
NOBODY
NOBODY WOULD
I WOULD BE CREATING THINGS THAT
NOBODY WOULD BE
NOBODY WOULD BE PLAYING
I WOULD BE CREATING THINGS THAT
NOBODY WOULD BE PLAYING WITH
NOBODY WOULD BE PLAYING WITH US.
NOBODY.
[APPLAUSE]
I
I DON'T
[APPLAUSE]
I DON'T NECESSARILY
I DON'T NECESSARILY MEAN
SOLDIERS.
WE
WE LOVE
SOLDIERS.
WE LOVE OUR
WE LOVE OUR SOLDIERS
SOLDIERS.
WE LOVE OUR SOLDIERS BUT
WE LOVE OUR SOLDIERS BUT I
SOLDIERS.
WE LOVE OUR SOLDIERS BUT I MEAN,
WE
WE HAVE
WE LOVE OUR SOLDIERS BUT I MEAN,
WE HAVE WEAPONRY
WE HAVE WEAPONRY THAT
WE LOVE OUR SOLDIERS BUT I MEAN,
WE HAVE WEAPONRY THAT IS
OBSOLETE.
NUCLEAR
NUCLEAR WEAPONS.
60 MINUTES
60 MINUTES DOES
NUCLEAR WEAPONS.
60 MINUTES DOES A
60 MINUTES DOES A SHOW,
NUCLEAR WEAPONS.
60 MINUTES DOES A SHOW, THEY
SHOW
SHOW HOW
60 MINUTES DOES A SHOW, THEY
SHOW HOW BAD
SHOW HOW BAD A
60 MINUTES DOES A SHOW, THEY
SHOW HOW BAD A CONDITION
SHOW HOW BAD A CONDITION OUR
NUCLEAR
NUCLEAR WEAPONS
SHOW HOW BAD A CONDITION OUR
NUCLEAR WEAPONS ARE
NUCLEAR WEAPONS ARE IN.
DID
DID ANYBODY
NUCLEAR WEAPONS ARE IN.
DID ANYBODY SEE
DID ANYBODY SEE THAT?
CAN
CAN YOU
DID ANYBODY SEE THAT?
CAN YOU --
CAN YOU -- EVEN
DID ANYBODY SEE THAT?
CAN YOU -- EVEN IF
CAN YOU -- EVEN IF IT
DID ANYBODY SEE THAT?
CAN YOU -- EVEN IF IT IS
CAN YOU -- EVEN IF IT IS TRUE,
WE
WE ARE
CAN YOU -- EVEN IF IT IS TRUE,
WE ARE PUTTING
WE ARE PUTTING THIS
CAN YOU -- EVEN IF IT IS TRUE,
WE ARE PUTTING THIS FOR
WE ARE PUTTING THIS FOR THE
WORLD
WORLD TO
WE ARE PUTTING THIS FOR THE
WORLD TO SEE.
THE
THE REASON
WORLD TO SEE.
THE REASON THEY
THE REASON THEY DID
WORLD TO SEE.
THE REASON THEY DID THAT
THE REASON THEY DID THAT IS
WORLD TO SEE.
THE REASON THEY DID THAT IS THE
PRESIDENT
PRESIDENT WANTED
THE REASON THEY DID THAT IS THE
PRESIDENT WANTED THE
PRESIDENT WANTED THE PRESS
THE REASON THEY DID THAT IS THE
PRESIDENT WANTED THE PRESS TO
SEE
SEE HOW
PRESIDENT WANTED THE PRESS TO
SEE HOW WEAK
SEE HOW WEAK OUR
PRESIDENT WANTED THE PRESS TO
SEE HOW WEAK OUR NUCLEAR
CAPABILITIES
CAPABILITIES WERE.
THE
THE TELEPHONES
CAPABILITIES WERE.
THE TELEPHONES DON'T
THE TELEPHONES DON'T WORK.
THEY
THEY HAVE
THE TELEPHONES DON'T WORK.
THEY HAVE WIRES.
THE
THE WIRES
THEY HAVE WIRES.
THE WIRES WERE
THE WIRES WERE ROTTING.
TO
TO WORK
THE WIRES WERE ROTTING.
TO WORK THE
TO WORK THE TELEPHONES,
THE WIRES WERE ROTTING.
TO WORK THE TELEPHONES, THE
SILOS
SILOS WERE
TO WORK THE TELEPHONES, THE
SILOS WERE RUSTING
SILOS WERE RUSTING AND
TO WORK THE TELEPHONES, THE
SILOS WERE RUSTING AND ROTTING.
THE
THE KIDS
SILOS WERE RUSTING AND ROTTING.
THE KIDS SAID
THE KIDS SAID WE
SILOS WERE RUSTING AND ROTTING.
THE KIDS SAID WE DON'T
THE KIDS SAID WE DON'T KNOW
SILOS WERE RUSTING AND ROTTING.
THE KIDS SAID WE DON'T KNOW IF
THEY
THEY WORK.
GREAT.
[LAUGHTER]
THEY
THEY ARE
[LAUGHTER]
THEY ARE SCREAMING
THEY ARE SCREAMING OVER
[LAUGHTER]
THEY ARE SCREAMING OVER THE
PHONE
PHONE BECAUSE
THEY ARE SCREAMING OVER THE
PHONE BECAUSE THE
PHONE BECAUSE THE WIRES
THEY ARE SCREAMING OVER THE
PHONE BECAUSE THE WIRES ARE
PHONE BECAUSE THE WIRES ARE SO
DAMAGED
DAMAGED AND
PHONE BECAUSE THE WIRES ARE SO
DAMAGED AND OLD.
THIS
THIS IS
DAMAGED AND OLD.
THIS IS OUR
THIS IS OUR NUCLEAR.
ASSUMING
ASSUMING IT
THIS IS OUR NUCLEAR.
ASSUMING IT IS
ASSUMING IT IS TRUE,
THIS IS OUR NUCLEAR.
ASSUMING IT IS TRUE, WHO
ASSUMING IT IS TRUE, WHO THE
HELL
HELL WOULD
ASSUMING IT IS TRUE, WHO THE
HELL WOULD SHOW
HELL WOULD SHOW THAT
ASSUMING IT IS TRUE, WHO THE
HELL WOULD SHOW THAT TO
HELL WOULD SHOW THAT TO THE
ENEMY?
THE
THE REASON
ENEMY?
THE REASON HE
THE REASON HE DID
ENEMY?
THE REASON HE DID WAS
THE REASON HE DID WAS BECAUSE
ENEMY?
THE REASON HE DID WAS BECAUSE HE
WANTS
WANTS FUNDING.
WE
WE HAVE
WANTS FUNDING.
WE HAVE TO
WE HAVE TO GET
WANTS FUNDING.
WE HAVE TO GET SMART
WE HAVE TO GET SMART PEOPLE,
TOUGH
TOUGH PEOPLE.
CHINA.
THEY
THEY DID
CHINA.
THEY DID THE
THEY DID THE LARGEST
CHINA.
THEY DID THE LARGEST DEVALUATION
IN
IN THE
THEY DID THE LARGEST DEVALUATION
IN THE HISTORY
IN THE HISTORY OF
THEY DID THE LARGEST DEVALUATION
IN THE HISTORY OF CHINA.
THEY
THEY THINK
IN THE HISTORY OF CHINA.
THEY THINK THE
THEY THINK THE HISTORY
IN THE HISTORY OF CHINA.
THEY THINK THE HISTORY BUT
THEY THINK THE HISTORY BUT THEY
SAY
SAY ONLY
THEY THINK THE HISTORY BUT THEY
SAY ONLY THE
SAY ONLY THE LAST
THEY THINK THE HISTORY BUT THEY
SAY ONLY THE LAST TWO
SAY ONLY THE LAST TWO DECADES.
NOW
NOW I
SAY ONLY THE LAST TWO DECADES.
NOW I FEEL
NOW I FEEL BETTER.
THEY
THEY BROUGHT
NOW I FEEL BETTER.
THEY BROUGHT IT
THEY BROUGHT IT DOWN
NOW I FEEL BETTER.
THEY BROUGHT IT DOWN TO
THEY BROUGHT IT DOWN TO TWO
DECADES.
IN
IN OTHER
DECADES.
IN OTHER WORDS,
IN OTHER WORDS, 20
DECADES.
IN OTHER WORDS, 20 YEARS.
OK.
WHAT
WHAT THAT
OK.
WHAT THAT MEANS
WHAT THAT MEANS IS,
OK.
WHAT THAT MEANS IS, YOU
WHAT THAT MEANS IS, YOU HEAR
OK.
WHAT THAT MEANS IS, YOU HEAR THE
SUCKING
SUCKING SOUND.
JOBS.
THAT
THAT MEANS
JOBS.
THAT MEANS MONEY.
THAT
THAT MEANS
THAT MEANS MONEY.
THAT MEANS ALL
THAT MEANS ALL OF
THAT MEANS MONEY.
THAT MEANS ALL OF THIS
THAT MEANS ALL OF THIS COMING
OUT.
THEY
THEY DID
OUT.
THEY DID A
THEY DID A NUMBER
OUT.
THEY DID A NUMBER ON
THEY DID A NUMBER ON US.
WHEN
WHEN THEY
THEY DID A NUMBER ON US.
WHEN THEY DID
WHEN THEY DID THE
THEY DID A NUMBER ON US.
WHEN THEY DID THE LAST
WHEN THEY DID THE LAST ONE
THEY DID A NUMBER ON US.
WHEN THEY DID THE LAST ONE WHICH
WASN'T
WASN'T LONG
WHEN THEY DID THE LAST ONE WHICH
WASN'T LONG AGO,
WASN'T LONG AGO, IT
WHEN THEY DID THE LAST ONE WHICH
WASN'T LONG AGO, IT WAS
WASN'T LONG AGO, IT WAS A
WHEN THEY DID THE LAST ONE WHICH
WASN'T LONG AGO, IT WAS A MUCH
MORE
MORE MODEST
WASN'T LONG AGO, IT WAS A MUCH
MORE MODEST DEVALUATION,
MORE MODEST DEVALUATION, I
WASN'T LONG AGO, IT WAS A MUCH
MORE MODEST DEVALUATION, I SAID
I
I CAN'T
MORE MODEST DEVALUATION, I SAID
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I CAN'T BELIEVE OBAMA
MORE MODEST DEVALUATION, I SAID
I CAN'T BELIEVE OBAMA IS
ALLOWING
ALLOWING THIS
I CAN'T BELIEVE OBAMA IS
ALLOWING THIS TO
ALLOWING THIS TO HAPPEN.
WE
WE HAVE
ALLOWING THIS TO HAPPEN.
WE HAVE ALL
WE HAVE ALL THE
ALLOWING THIS TO HAPPEN.
WE HAVE ALL THE CARDS.
I
I TOLD
WE HAVE ALL THE CARDS.
I TOLD THE
I TOLD THE PRESS
WE HAVE ALL THE CARDS.
I TOLD THE PRESS IT
I TOLD THE PRESS IT IS
WE HAVE ALL THE CARDS.
I TOLD THE PRESS IT IS THE
GREATEST
GREATEST THEFT
I TOLD THE PRESS IT IS THE
GREATEST THEFT IN
GREATEST THEFT IN THE
I TOLD THE PRESS IT IS THE
GREATEST THEFT IN THE HISTORY
GREATEST THEFT IN THE HISTORY OF
THE
THE UNITED
GREATEST THEFT IN THE HISTORY OF
THE UNITED STATES,
THE UNITED STATES, WHAT
GREATEST THEFT IN THE HISTORY OF
THE UNITED STATES, WHAT CHINA
HAS
HAS DONE.
WE
WE HAVE
HAS DONE.
WE HAVE REBUILT
WE HAVE REBUILT CHINA.
OUR
OUR MONEY
WE HAVE REBUILT CHINA.
OUR MONEY HAS
OUR MONEY HAS REBUILT
WE HAVE REBUILT CHINA.
OUR MONEY HAS REBUILT CHINA.
[APPLAUSE]
YOU
YOU GO
[APPLAUSE]
YOU GO OVER
YOU GO OVER TO
[APPLAUSE]
YOU GO OVER TO CHINA,
YOU GO OVER TO CHINA, BRIDGES
ARE
ARE BEING
YOU GO OVER TO CHINA, BRIDGES
ARE BEING BUILT
ARE BEING BUILT ALL
YOU GO OVER TO CHINA, BRIDGES
ARE BEING BUILT ALL OVER
ARE BEING BUILT ALL OVER THE
PLACE
PLACE THAT
ARE BEING BUILT ALL OVER THE
PLACE THAT MAKE
PLACE THAT MAKE THE
ARE BEING BUILT ALL OVER THE
PLACE THAT MAKE THE GEORGE
WASHINGTON
WASHINGTON BRIDGE
PLACE THAT MAKE THE GEORGE
WASHINGTON BRIDGE AND
WASHINGTON BRIDGE AND OTHER
BRIDGES
BRIDGES LOOK
WASHINGTON BRIDGE AND OTHER
BRIDGES LOOK SMALL.
I
I AM
BRIDGES LOOK SMALL.
I AM NOT
I AM NOT USING
BRIDGES LOOK SMALL.
I AM NOT USING THE
I AM NOT USING THE GEORGE
WASHINGTON
WASHINGTON BRIDGE
I AM NOT USING THE GEORGE
WASHINGTON BRIDGE FOR
WASHINGTON BRIDGE FOR POLITICAL
PURPOSES.
I
I WOULDN'T
PURPOSES.
I WOULDN'T DO
I WOULDN'T DO THAT.
IT
IT MAKES
I WOULDN'T DO THAT.
IT MAKES IT
IT MAKES IT LOOK
I WOULDN'T DO THAT.
IT MAKES IT LOOK SMALL
IT MAKES IT LOOK SMALL TIME.
MASSIVE
MASSIVE HIGHWAYS,
IT MAKES IT LOOK SMALL TIME.
MASSIVE HIGHWAYS, MASSIVE
MASSIVE HIGHWAYS, MASSIVE ROADS.
I
I WAS
MASSIVE HIGHWAYS, MASSIVE ROADS.
I WAS IN
I WAS IN DUBAI.
GREAT
GREAT PLACE
I WAS IN DUBAI.
GREAT PLACE FOR
GREAT PLACE FOR THEY
I WAS IN DUBAI.
GREAT PLACE FOR THEY HAVE
GREAT PLACE FOR THEY HAVE AN
AIRPORT,
AIRPORT, IT
GREAT PLACE FOR THEY HAVE AN
AIRPORT, IT IS
AIRPORT, IT IS LIKE
GREAT PLACE FOR THEY HAVE AN
AIRPORT, IT IS LIKE MAGIC.
THE
THE MOST
AIRPORT, IT IS LIKE MAGIC.
THE MOST INCREDIBLE
THE MOST INCREDIBLE THING
AIRPORT, IT IS LIKE MAGIC.
THE MOST INCREDIBLE THING YOU
HAVE
HAVE EVER
THE MOST INCREDIBLE THING YOU
HAVE EVER SEEN.
YOU
YOU GO
HAVE EVER SEEN.
YOU GO TO
YOU GO TO QATAR,
HAVE EVER SEEN.
YOU GO TO QATAR, YOU
YOU GO TO QATAR, YOU GO
HAVE EVER SEEN.
YOU GO TO QATAR, YOU GO TO
ALL
ALL THESE
YOU GO TO QATAR, YOU GO TO
ALL THESE PLACES.
WE
WE LAND
ALL THESE PLACES.
WE LAND AT
WE LAND AT KENNEDY
ALL THESE PLACES.
WE LAND AT KENNEDY WHERE
WE LAND AT KENNEDY WHERE THEY
HAVE
HAVE HANGERS
WE LAND AT KENNEDY WHERE THEY
HAVE HANGERS THAT
HAVE HANGERS THAT ARE
WE LAND AT KENNEDY WHERE THEY
HAVE HANGERS THAT ARE FALLING
DOWN,
DOWN, ROTTING
HAVE HANGERS THAT ARE FALLING
DOWN, ROTTING AND
DOWN, ROTTING AND RUSTING.
IT
IT IS
DOWN, ROTTING AND RUSTING.
IT IS SUCH
IT IS SUCH A
DOWN, ROTTING AND RUSTING.
IT IS SUCH A SHOCK.
WE
WE GO
IT IS SUCH A SHOCK.
WE GO TO
WE GO TO KENNEDY.
YOU
YOU GET
WE GO TO KENNEDY.
YOU GET USED
YOU GET USED TO
WE GO TO KENNEDY.
YOU GET USED TO THINGS.
WHEN
WHEN YOUR
YOU GET USED TO THINGS.
WHEN YOUR HOUSE
WHEN YOUR HOUSE GETS
YOU GET USED TO THINGS.
WHEN YOUR HOUSE GETS DIRTY.
THESE
THESE ARE
WHEN YOUR HOUSE GETS DIRTY.
THESE ARE SO
THESE ARE SO BAD,
WHEN YOUR HOUSE GETS DIRTY.
THESE ARE SO BAD, THESE
THESE ARE SO BAD, THESE AIRLINES
ARE
ARE SO
THESE ARE SO BAD, THESE AIRLINES
ARE SO SAD.
YOU
YOU LOOK
ARE SO SAD.
YOU LOOK AT
YOU LOOK AT THE
ARE SO SAD.
YOU LOOK AT THE AGE
YOU LOOK AT THE AGE OF
ARE SO SAD.
YOU LOOK AT THE AGE OF OUR
INFRASTRUCTURE.
LOOK
LOOK AT
INFRASTRUCTURE.
LOOK AT ALL
LOOK AT ALL OF
INFRASTRUCTURE.
LOOK AT ALL OF THE
LOOK AT ALL OF THE DIFFERENT
THINGS.
EVEN
EVEN THE
THINGS.
EVEN THE AIRPLANES.
THEY
THEY LIKE
EVEN THE AIRPLANES.
THEY LIKE QATAR.
THEY
THEY ASKED
THEY LIKE QATAR.
THEY ASKED ME
THEY ASKED ME TO
THEY LIKE QATAR.
THEY ASKED ME TO GO
THEY ASKED ME TO GO TO
THEY LIKE QATAR.
THEY ASKED ME TO GO TO A
THEY ASKED ME TO GO TO A DINNER
AND
AND I
THEY ASKED ME TO GO TO A DINNER
AND I SAID
AND I SAID I
THEY ASKED ME TO GO TO A DINNER
AND I SAID I CAN'T.
THEY
THEY SAID
AND I SAID I CAN'T.
THEY SAID WE
THEY SAID WE WILL
AND I SAID I CAN'T.
THEY SAID WE WILL PAY
THEY SAID WE WILL PAY YOU
AND I SAID I CAN'T.
THEY SAID WE WILL PAY YOU A
THEY SAID WE WILL PAY YOU A LOT
OF
OF MONEY.
IT
IT WAS
OF MONEY.
IT WAS A
IT WAS A LOT
OF MONEY.
IT WAS A LOT OF
IT WAS A LOT OF MONEY
OF MONEY.
IT WAS A LOT OF MONEY TO
IT WAS A LOT OF MONEY TO HAVE
OF MONEY.
IT WAS A LOT OF MONEY TO HAVE A
DINNER.
LIKE
LIKE A
DINNER.
LIKE A TREMENDOUS
LIKE A TREMENDOUS AMOUNT
DINNER.
LIKE A TREMENDOUS AMOUNT OF
MONEY.
I
I SAID
MONEY.
I SAID I'LL
I SAID I'LL GO.
[LAUGHTER]
YOU
YOU HAVE
[LAUGHTER]
YOU HAVE TO
YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND.
YOU
YOU CAN
YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND.
YOU CAN BE
YOU CAN BE REALLY
YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND.
YOU CAN BE REALLY RICH,
YOU CAN BE REALLY RICH, BUT
YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND.
YOU CAN BE REALLY RICH, BUT IF
YOU'RE
YOU'RE GOING
YOU CAN BE REALLY RICH, BUT IF
YOU'RE GOING TO
YOU'RE GOING TO GET
YOU CAN BE REALLY RICH, BUT IF
YOU'RE GOING TO GET HUNDREDS
YOU'RE GOING TO GET HUNDREDS OF
THOUSANDS
THOUSANDS OF
YOU'RE GOING TO GET HUNDREDS OF
THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS
THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS TO
YOU'RE GOING TO GET HUNDREDS OF
THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS TO HAVE
THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS TO HAVE A
DINNER
DINNER TWO
THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS TO HAVE A
DINNER TWO BLOCKS
DINNER TWO BLOCKS FROM
THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS TO HAVE A
DINNER TWO BLOCKS FROM YOUR
HOUSE
HOUSE AND
DINNER TWO BLOCKS FROM YOUR
HOUSE AND YOU
HOUSE AND YOU DON'T
DINNER TWO BLOCKS FROM YOUR
HOUSE AND YOU DON'T DO
HOUSE AND YOU DON'T DO IT
DINNER TWO BLOCKS FROM YOUR
HOUSE AND YOU DON'T DO IT IT
HOUSE AND YOU DON'T DO IT IT IS
TIME
TIME TO
HOUSE AND YOU DON'T DO IT IT IS
TIME TO RETIRE.
DO
DO YOU
TIME TO RETIRE.
DO YOU AGREE?
I
I WENT.
IT
IT WAS
I WENT.
IT WAS SO
IT WAS SO AMAZING.
I
I SAID
IT WAS SO AMAZING.
I SAID TO
I SAID TO THE
IT WAS SO AMAZING.
I SAID TO THE MAN
I SAID TO THE MAN OF
IT WAS SO AMAZING.
I SAID TO THE MAN OF THE
AIRLINE,
AIRLINE, WHAT
I SAID TO THE MAN OF THE
AIRLINE, WHAT IS
AIRLINE, WHAT IS THE
I SAID TO THE MAN OF THE
AIRLINE, WHAT IS THE AVERAGE
AIRLINE, WHAT IS THE AVERAGE AGE
OF
OF YOUR
AIRLINE, WHAT IS THE AVERAGE AGE
OF YOUR PLANES?
HE
HE SAID
OF YOUR PLANES?
HE SAID ABOUT
HE SAID ABOUT A
OF YOUR PLANES?
HE SAID ABOUT A YEAR
HE SAID ABOUT A YEAR AND
OF YOUR PLANES?
HE SAID ABOUT A YEAR AND A
HE SAID ABOUT A YEAR AND A HALF.
THE
THE AVERAGE
HE SAID ABOUT A YEAR AND A HALF.
THE AVERAGE AGE
THE AVERAGE AGE OF
HE SAID ABOUT A YEAR AND A HALF.
THE AVERAGE AGE OF SOME
THE AVERAGE AGE OF SOME OF
HE SAID ABOUT A YEAR AND A HALF.
THE AVERAGE AGE OF SOME OF OUR
AIRLINES,
AIRLINES, 32
THE AVERAGE AGE OF SOME OF OUR
AIRLINES, 32 YEARS.
15 YEARS
15 YEARS PRE-28
AIRLINES, 32 YEARS.
15 YEARS PRE-28 YEARS.
AND
AND YOU
15 YEARS PRE-28 YEARS.
AND YOU SEE
AND YOU SEE IT.
I
I SAID
AND YOU SEE IT.
I SAID HOW
I SAID HOW DO
AND YOU SEE IT.
I SAID HOW DO YOU
I SAID HOW DO YOU FINANCE
AND YOU SEE IT.
I SAID HOW DO YOU FINANCE YOUR
PLANES.
HE
HE LOOKED
PLANES.
HE LOOKED AT
HE LOOKED AT ME
PLANES.
HE LOOKED AT ME LIKE
HE LOOKED AT ME LIKE FINANCE?
WE
WE DON'T
HE LOOKED AT ME LIKE FINANCE?
WE DON'T FINANCE.
WE
WE PAY
WE DON'T FINANCE.
WE PAY CASH.
SAUDI
SAUDI ARABIA.
I
I WAS
SAUDI ARABIA.
I WAS IMPRESSED.
IT
IT WASN'T
I WAS IMPRESSED.
IT WASN'T A
IT WASN'T A QUESTION.
WHEN
WHEN I
IT WASN'T A QUESTION.
WHEN I WENT
WHEN I WENT TO
IT WASN'T A QUESTION.
WHEN I WENT TO QATAR,
WHEN I WENT TO QATAR, I
IT WASN'T A QUESTION.
WHEN I WENT TO QATAR, I WENT
INTO
INTO AN
WHEN I WENT TO QATAR, I WENT
INTO AN AIRLINE
INTO AN AIRLINE TERMINAL
WHEN I WENT TO QATAR, I WENT
INTO AN AIRLINE TERMINAL THAT
WAS
WAS THE
INTO AN AIRLINE TERMINAL THAT
WAS THE MOST
WAS THE MOST BEAUTIFUL
INTO AN AIRLINE TERMINAL THAT
WAS THE MOST BEAUTIFUL TERMINAL
I
I HAVE
WAS THE MOST BEAUTIFUL TERMINAL
I HAVE EVER
I HAVE EVER SEEN.
THE
THE MOST
I HAVE EVER SEEN.
THE MOST MAGNIFICENT.
THEY
THEY HAD
THE MOST MAGNIFICENT.
THEY HAD LOUNGES,
THEY HAD LOUNGES, THEY
THE MOST MAGNIFICENT.
THEY HAD LOUNGES, THEY HAD
THEY HAD LOUNGES, THEY HAD SPAS.
BEFORE
BEFORE YOU
THEY HAD LOUNGES, THEY HAD SPAS.
BEFORE YOU GET
BEFORE YOU GET ON
THEY HAD LOUNGES, THEY HAD SPAS.
BEFORE YOU GET ON THE
BEFORE YOU GET ON THE PLANE
THEY HAD LOUNGES, THEY HAD SPAS.
BEFORE YOU GET ON THE PLANE YOU
CAN
CAN GET
BEFORE YOU GET ON THE PLANE YOU
CAN GET A
CAN GET A MASSAGE.
I'M
I'M NOT
CAN GET A MASSAGE.
I'M NOT INTO
I'M NOT INTO THAT
CAN GET A MASSAGE.
I'M NOT INTO THAT THOUGH.
I
I DON'T
I'M NOT INTO THAT THOUGH.
I DON'T LIKE
I DON'T LIKE PEOPLE
I'M NOT INTO THAT THOUGH.
I DON'T LIKE PEOPLE TOUCHING
I DON'T LIKE PEOPLE TOUCHING ME.
[LAUGHTER]
IT'S
IT'S TRUE.
THEY
THEY HAVE
IT'S TRUE.
THEY HAVE THESE
THEY HAVE THESE MAGNIFICENT
SPAS.
I
I SAID
SPAS.
I SAID THIS
I SAID THIS IS
SPAS.
I SAID THIS IS THE
I SAID THIS IS THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL
BEAUTIFUL AIRLINE
I SAID THIS IS THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL AIRLINE TERMINAL
BEAUTIFUL AIRLINE TERMINAL I'VE
EVER
EVER SEEN.
HE
HE SAID
EVER SEEN.
HE SAID NO.
THIS
THIS IS
HE SAID NO.
THIS IS TEMPORARY.
OUR
OUR NEW
THIS IS TEMPORARY.
OUR NEW ONE
OUR NEW ONE IS
THIS IS TEMPORARY.
OUR NEW ONE IS BEING
OUR NEW ONE IS BEING BUILT
THIS IS TEMPORARY.
OUR NEW ONE IS BEING BUILT OVER
THERE.
THERE
THERE MUST
THERE.
THERE MUST HAVE
THERE MUST HAVE BEEN
THERE.
THERE MUST HAVE BEEN 40
CRANES.
THIS
THIS WAS
CRANES.
THIS WAS A
THIS WAS A TEAR
CRANES.
THIS WAS A TEAR DOWN.
WE
WE ARE
THIS WAS A TEAR DOWN.
WE ARE DOING
WE ARE DOING IT
THIS WAS A TEAR DOWN.
WE ARE DOING IT WRONG.
SAUDI
SAUDI ARABIA,
WE ARE DOING IT WRONG.
SAUDI ARABIA, I
SAUDI ARABIA, I HAVE
WE ARE DOING IT WRONG.
SAUDI ARABIA, I HAVE GOOD
RELATIONSHIPS
RELATIONSHIPS WITH
SAUDI ARABIA, I HAVE GOOD
RELATIONSHIPS WITH SAUDI
RELATIONSHIPS WITH SAUDI ARABIA
AND
AND MEXICO,
RELATIONSHIPS WITH SAUDI ARABIA
AND MEXICO, AS
AND MEXICO, AS I
RELATIONSHIPS WITH SAUDI ARABIA
AND MEXICO, AS I DO
AND MEXICO, AS I DO WITH
EVERYBODY.
THEY
THEY PAY
EVERYBODY.
THEY PAY MILLIONS
THEY PAY MILLIONS OF
EVERYBODY.
THEY PAY MILLIONS OF DOLLARS.
AM
AM I
THEY PAY MILLIONS OF DOLLARS.
AM I SUPPOSED
AM I SUPPOSED TO
THEY PAY MILLIONS OF DOLLARS.
AM I SUPPOSED TO DISLIKE
AM I SUPPOSED TO DISLIKE THEM?
CHINA.
I
I SELL
CHINA.
I SELL APARTMENTS
I SELL APARTMENTS FOR
CHINA.
I SELL APARTMENTS FOR $18
MILLION.
SOME
SOME OF
MILLION.
SOME OF THE
SOME OF THE CHEAP
MILLION.
SOME OF THE CHEAP ONES
SOME OF THE CHEAP ONES ARE
MILLION.
SOME OF THE CHEAP ONES ARE $10
I
MILLION.
I DON'T
I DON'T EVEN
MILLION.
I DON'T EVEN BOTHER
I DON'T EVEN BOTHER TO
MILLION.
I DON'T EVEN BOTHER TO SIGN
THOSE
THOSE CONTRACTS.
I
I GET
THOSE CONTRACTS.
I GET IT
I GET IT FROM
THOSE CONTRACTS.
I GET IT FROM SAUDI
I GET IT FROM SAUDI ARABIA.
FROM
FROM JAPAN.
FROM EVERYBODY.
I
I LOVE
FROM EVERYBODY.
I LOVE THESE
I LOVE THESE PEOPLE.
THE
THE PROBLEM
I LOVE THESE PEOPLE.
THE PROBLEM IS
THE PROBLEM IS MEXICO,
I LOVE THESE PEOPLE.
THE PROBLEM IS MEXICO, I
THE PROBLEM IS MEXICO, I LOVE
THE
THE MEXICAN
THE PROBLEM IS MEXICO, I LOVE
THE MEXICAN PEOPLE.
THEY
THEY HAVE
THE MEXICAN PEOPLE.
THEY HAVE TREMENDOUS
THEY HAVE TREMENDOUS SPIRIT.
WHEN
WHEN I
THEY HAVE TREMENDOUS SPIRIT.
WHEN I OPENED,
WHEN I OPENED, TRUMP
THEY HAVE TREMENDOUS SPIRIT.
WHEN I OPENED, TRUMP HAS
WHEN I OPENED, TRUMP HAS TAKEN
MORE
MORE INCOME
WHEN I OPENED, TRUMP HAS TAKEN
MORE INCOME THAN
MORE INCOME THAN ANY
WHEN I OPENED, TRUMP HAS TAKEN
MORE INCOME THAN ANY HUMAN
MORE INCOME THAN ANY HUMAN BEING
I'VE
I'VE EVER
MORE INCOME THAN ANY HUMAN BEING
I'VE EVER SEEN.
THE
THE PRESS
I'VE EVER SEEN.
THE PRESS CHANGED
THE PRESS CHANGED MY
I'VE EVER SEEN.
THE PRESS CHANGED MY STATEMENT.
THEY
THEY USED
THE PRESS CHANGED MY STATEMENT.
THEY USED HALF
THEY USED HALF A
THE PRESS CHANGED MY STATEMENT.
THEY USED HALF A SENTENCE.
IT
IT TURNED
THEY USED HALF A SENTENCE.
IT TURNED OUT
IT TURNED OUT I
THEY USED HALF A SENTENCE.
IT TURNED OUT I WAS
IT TURNED OUT I WAS RIGHT.
I
I WAS
IT TURNED OUT I WAS RIGHT.
I WAS TALKING
I WAS TALKING ABOUT
IT TURNED OUT I WAS RIGHT.
I WAS TALKING ABOUT ILLEGAL
IMMIGRATION.
IT
IT TURNED
IMMIGRATION.
IT TURNED OUT
IT TURNED OUT THAT
IMMIGRATION.
IT TURNED OUT THAT I
IT TURNED OUT THAT I WAS
IMMIGRATION.
IT TURNED OUT THAT I WAS RIGHT.
WHEN
WHEN YOU
IT TURNED OUT THAT I WAS RIGHT.
WHEN YOU LOOK
WHEN YOU LOOK AT
IT TURNED OUT THAT I WAS RIGHT.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT SAUDI
WHEN YOU LOOK AT SAUDI ARABIA,
WHEN
WHEN YOU
WHEN YOU LOOK AT SAUDI ARABIA,
WHEN YOU LOOK
WHEN YOU LOOK AT
WHEN YOU LOOK AT SAUDI ARABIA,
WHEN YOU LOOK AT MEXICO,
WHEN YOU LOOK AT MEXICO, THEY
ARE
ARE TAKING
WHEN YOU LOOK AT MEXICO, THEY
ARE TAKING OVER.
NABISCO
NABISCO IS
ARE TAKING OVER.
NABISCO IS CLOSING
NABISCO IS CLOSING A
ARE TAKING OVER.
NABISCO IS CLOSING A FACTORY
NABISCO IS CLOSING A FACTORY IN
CHICAGO.
THEY
THEY ARE
CHICAGO.
THEY ARE MOVING
THEY ARE MOVING TO
CHICAGO.
THEY ARE MOVING TO MEXICO.
THIS
THIS BIG
THEY ARE MOVING TO MEXICO.
THIS BIG FACTORY.
1200 JOBS
1200 JOBS GOING
THIS BIG FACTORY.
1200 JOBS GOING TO
1200 JOBS GOING TO BE
THIS BIG FACTORY.
1200 JOBS GOING TO BE LOST
1200 JOBS GOING TO BE LOST IN
CHICAGO.
NO
NO MORE
CHICAGO.
NO MORE ORIOLES.
OREOS.
THEY
THEY ANNOUNCED.
THEY ARE
THEY ARE DOING
THEY ANNOUNCED.
THEY ARE DOING OTHER
THEY ARE DOING OTHER THINGS.
IT
IT IS
THEY ARE DOING OTHER THINGS.
IT IS GREAT.
MEXICO.
IF
IF YOU
MEXICO.
IF YOU CAN
IF YOU CAN GET
MEXICO.
IF YOU CAN GET AWAY
IF YOU CAN GET AWAY WITH
MEXICO.
IF YOU CAN GET AWAY WITH IT
IF YOU CAN GET AWAY WITH IT IT
IS
IS GREAT.
I
I HAVE
IS GREAT.
I HAVE SUCH
I HAVE SUCH RESPECT
IS GREAT.
I HAVE SUCH RESPECT FOR
I HAVE SUCH RESPECT FOR THE
LEADERS
LEADERS OF
I HAVE SUCH RESPECT FOR THE
LEADERS OF MEXICO
LEADERS OF MEXICO AND
I HAVE SUCH RESPECT FOR THE
LEADERS OF MEXICO AND THEIR
NEGOTIATORS.
I
I DON'T
NEGOTIATORS.
I DON'T DISLIKE
I DON'T DISLIKE THEM.
THE
THE BIGGEST
I DON'T DISLIKE THEM.
THE BIGGEST BANK
THE BIGGEST BANK IN
I DON'T DISLIKE THEM.
THE BIGGEST BANK IN THE
THE BIGGEST BANK IN THE WORLD
I DON'T DISLIKE THEM.
THE BIGGEST BANK IN THE WORLD IS
A
A TENANT
THE BIGGEST BANK IN THE WORLD IS
A TENANT IN
A TENANT IN ONE
THE BIGGEST BANK IN THE WORLD IS
A TENANT IN ONE OF
A TENANT IN ONE OF MY
THE BIGGEST BANK IN THE WORLD IS
A TENANT IN ONE OF MY BUILDINGS.
IT
IT IS
A TENANT IN ONE OF MY BUILDINGS.
IT IS AN
IT IS AN INCREDIBLE
A TENANT IN ONE OF MY BUILDINGS.
IT IS AN INCREDIBLE BANK.
CITIBANK
CITIBANK IS
IT IS AN INCREDIBLE BANK.
CITIBANK IS A
CITIBANK IS A TINY
IT IS AN INCREDIBLE BANK.
CITIBANK IS A TINY SUBSIDIARY
COMPARED
COMPARED TO
CITIBANK IS A TINY SUBSIDIARY
COMPARED TO IT.
I
I NEVER
COMPARED TO IT.
I NEVER HAVE
I NEVER HAVE TO
COMPARED TO IT.
I NEVER HAVE TO WORRY
I NEVER HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT
COMPARED TO IT.
I NEVER HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT THE
RENT.
I
I LOVE
RENT.
I LOVE THESE
I LOVE THESE PEOPLE.
APARTMENTS.
WITH
WITH MEXICO
APARTMENTS.
WITH MEXICO I
WITH MEXICO I HAVE
APARTMENTS.
WITH MEXICO I HAVE HIRED
THOUSANDS
THOUSANDS OVER
WITH MEXICO I HAVE HIRED
THOUSANDS OVER THE
THOUSANDS OVER THE YEARS,
THOUSANDS
THOUSANDS FROM
THOUSANDS OVER THE YEARS,
THOUSANDS FROM MEXICO
THOUSANDS FROM MEXICO AND
THOUSANDS OVER THE YEARS,
THOUSANDS FROM MEXICO AND LOTS
OF
OF OTHER
THOUSANDS FROM MEXICO AND LOTS
OF OTHER PLACES.
THE
THE PROBLEM
OF OTHER PLACES.
THE PROBLEM IS,
THE PROBLEM IS, THEIR
OF OTHER PLACES.
THE PROBLEM IS, THEIR LEADERS
ARE
ARE SMARTER
THE PROBLEM IS, THEIR LEADERS
ARE SMARTER AND
ARE SMARTER AND SHARPER,
THE PROBLEM IS, THEIR LEADERS
ARE SMARTER AND SHARPER, AND
MORE
MORE CUNNING.
THEY
THEY ARE
MORE CUNNING.
THEY ARE MUCH
THEY ARE MUCH MORE
MORE CUNNING.
THEY ARE MUCH MORE CUNNING.
THE
THE WORD
THEY ARE MUCH MORE CUNNING.
THE WORD CUNNING
THE WORD CUNNING IS
IMPORTANT.
THEY
THEY KNOW
IMPORTANT.
THEY KNOW WHAT
THEY KNOW WHAT IS
IMPORTANT.
THEY KNOW WHAT IS GOING
THEY KNOW WHAT IS GOING ON.
THEY
THEY ARE
THEY KNOW WHAT IS GOING ON.
THEY ARE WHIPPING
THEY ARE WHIPPING US
THEY KNOW WHAT IS GOING ON.
THEY ARE WHIPPING US LEFT
THEY ARE WHIPPING US LEFT AND
RIGHT.
ALL
ALL OF
RIGHT.
ALL OF THESE
ALL OF THESE COUNTRIES.
I
I COULD
ALL OF THESE COUNTRIES.
I COULD MENTION
I COULD MENTION 100.
WE
WE DON'T
I COULD MENTION 100.
WE DON'T MAKE
WE DON'T MAKE GOOD
I COULD MENTION 100.
WE DON'T MAKE GOOD DEALS
ANYMORE.
ONE
ONE OF
ANYMORE.
ONE OF OUR
ONE OF OUR GREAT
ANYMORE.
ONE OF OUR GREAT DEALMAKERS,
CARL
CARL ICAHN.
I
I HAD
CARL ICAHN.
I HAD DINNER
I HAD DINNER WITH
CARL ICAHN.
I HAD DINNER WITH HIM
I HAD DINNER WITH HIM AND
CARL ICAHN.
I HAD DINNER WITH HIM AND SAID
CARL,
CARL, IF
I HAD DINNER WITH HIM AND SAID
CARL, IF I
CARL, IF I DO
I HAD DINNER WITH HIM AND SAID
CARL, IF I DO THIS,
CARL, IF I DO THIS, AND
I HAD DINNER WITH HIM AND SAID
CARL, IF I DO THIS, AND I'M
DOING
DOING WELL,
CARL, IF I DO THIS, AND I'M
DOING WELL, ARE
DOING WELL, ARE WE
CARL, IF I DO THIS, AND I'M
DOING WELL, ARE WE LEADING
DOING WELL, ARE WE LEADING IN
EVERY
EVERY SINGLE
DOING WELL, ARE WE LEADING IN
EVERY SINGLE POLL?
[APPLAUSE]
AND
AND IT
[APPLAUSE]
AND IT IS
AND IT IS THE
[APPLAUSE]
AND IT IS THE TALK
AND IT IS THE TALK OF
[APPLAUSE]
AND IT IS THE TALK OF POLITICS.
IT
IT IS
AND IT IS THE TALK OF POLITICS.
IT IS A
IT IS A GREAT
AND IT IS THE TALK OF POLITICS.
IT IS A GREAT HONOR.
WE
WE HAVE
IT IS A GREAT HONOR.
WE HAVE TO
WE HAVE TO GET
IT IS A GREAT HONOR.
WE HAVE TO GET THERE.
I
I WAS
WE HAVE TO GET THERE.
I WAS CALLED
I WAS CALLED BY
WE HAVE TO GET THERE.
I WAS CALLED BY ONE
I WAS CALLED BY ONE OF
WE HAVE TO GET THERE.
I WAS CALLED BY ONE OF THE
BIGGEST
BIGGEST JOURNALISTS
I WAS CALLED BY ONE OF THE
BIGGEST JOURNALISTS IN
BIGGEST JOURNALISTS IN THE
WORLD.
HE
HE SAID
WORLD.
HE SAID MR.
HE SAID MR. TRUMP,
WORLD.
HE SAID MR. TRUMP, COULD
HE SAID MR. TRUMP, COULD I
WORLD.
HE SAID MR. TRUMP, COULD I ASK
YOU
YOU A
HE SAID MR. TRUMP, COULD I ASK
YOU A QUESTION?
HOW
HOW DOES
YOU A QUESTION?
HOW DOES IT
HOW DOES IT FEEL?
HOW
HOW DOES
HOW DOES IT FEEL?
HOW DOES WHAT
HOW DOES WHAT FEEL?
>>
>> HE
HOW DOES WHAT FEEL?
>> HE HAVE
>> HE HAVE DONE
HOW DOES WHAT FEEL?
>> HE HAVE DONE SOMETHING
>> HE HAVE DONE SOMETHING THAT
NOBODY
NOBODY ELSE
>> HE HAVE DONE SOMETHING THAT
NOBODY ELSE HAS
NOBODY ELSE HAS EVER
>> HE HAVE DONE SOMETHING THAT
NOBODY ELSE HAS EVER DONE.
YOU
YOU HAVE
NOBODY ELSE HAS EVER DONE.
YOU HAVE TAKEN
YOU HAVE TAKEN OVER
NOBODY ELSE HAS EVER DONE.
YOU HAVE TAKEN OVER TELEVISION,
THE
THE AIRWAYS.
IT
IT IS
THE AIRWAYS.
IT IS THE
IT IS THE SUMMER
THE AIRWAYS.
IT IS THE SUMMER OF
IT IS THE SUMMER OF TRUMP.
THEY
THEY ARE
IT IS THE SUMMER OF TRUMP.
THEY ARE CALLING
THEY ARE CALLING IT
IT IS THE SUMMER OF TRUMP.
THEY ARE CALLING IT THE
THEY ARE CALLING IT THE SUMMER
OF
OF TRUMP.
[APPLAUSE]
THIS
THIS IS
[APPLAUSE]
THIS IS A
THIS IS A HIGHLY
[APPLAUSE]
THIS IS A HIGHLY RESPECTED
THIS IS A HIGHLY RESPECTED GUY.
I
I SAID
THIS IS A HIGHLY RESPECTED GUY.
I SAID I
I SAID I HAVEN'T
THIS IS A HIGHLY RESPECTED GUY.
I SAID I HAVEN'T DONE
I SAID I HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING.
I
I HAVEN'T
I SAID I HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING.
I HAVEN'T WON.
IT
IT STARTS
I HAVEN'T WON.
IT STARTS WITH
IT STARTS WITH ONE
I HAVEN'T WON.
IT STARTS WITH ONE IN
IT STARTS WITH ONE IN THE
PRIMARIES
PRIMARIES THAN
IT STARTS WITH ONE IN THE
PRIMARIES THAN GOING
PRIMARIES THAN GOING ON
IT STARTS WITH ONE IN THE
PRIMARIES THAN GOING ON AND
WINNING.
I
I CONSIDER
WINNING.
I CONSIDER IT
I CONSIDER IT A
WINNING.
I CONSIDER IT A WASTE
I CONSIDER IT A WASTE OF
WINNING.
I CONSIDER IT A WASTE OF TIME.
HE
HE SAID
I CONSIDER IT A WASTE OF TIME.
HE SAID YOU
HE SAID YOU ARE
I CONSIDER IT A WASTE OF TIME.
HE SAID YOU ARE WRONG.
YOU
YOU HAVE
HE SAID YOU ARE WRONG.
YOU HAVE DONE
YOU HAVE DONE A
HE SAID YOU ARE WRONG.
YOU HAVE DONE A GREAT
THING.
I
I WON'T
THING.
I WON'T BE
I WON'T BE HAPPY.
BUT
BUT WE
I WON'T BE HAPPY.
BUT WE ARE
BUT WE ARE ALL
I WON'T BE HAPPY.
BUT WE ARE ALL DOING
BUT WE ARE ALL DOING WELL.
THINK
THINK OF
BUT WE ARE ALL DOING WELL.
THINK OF THIS.
IF
IF YOU
THINK OF THIS.
IF YOU LOOK
IF YOU LOOK AT
THINK OF THIS.
IF YOU LOOK AT SAUDI
IF YOU LOOK AT SAUDI ARABIA,
THINK OF THIS.
IF YOU LOOK AT SAUDI ARABIA, AND
THEY
THEY MAKE
IF YOU LOOK AT SAUDI ARABIA, AND
THEY MAKE A
THEY MAKE A BILLION
IF YOU LOOK AT SAUDI ARABIA, AND
THEY MAKE A BILLION DOLLARS
THEY MAKE A BILLION DOLLARS A
DAY.
A
A BILLION
DAY.
A BILLION DOLLARS
A BILLION DOLLARS A
DAY.
A BILLION DOLLARS A DAY.
OK.
WHEN
WHEN THEY
OK.
WHEN THEY HAVE
WHEN THEY HAVE A
OK.
WHEN THEY HAVE A PROBLEM
WHEN THEY HAVE A PROBLEM WE
OK.
WHEN THEY HAVE A PROBLEM WE SEND
OVER
OVER SHIPS
WHEN THEY HAVE A PROBLEM WE SEND
OVER SHIPS AND
OVER SHIPS AND PLANES.
I
I DON'T
OVER SHIPS AND PLANES.
I DON'T MIND
I DON'T MIND DOING
OVER SHIPS AND PLANES.
I DON'T MIND DOING THAT.
THEY
THEY HAVE
I DON'T MIND DOING THAT.
THEY HAVE TO
THEY HAVE TO HELP
I DON'T MIND DOING THAT.
THEY HAVE TO HELP US
THEY HAVE TO HELP US OUT.
THEY
THEY HAVE
THEY HAVE TO HELP US OUT.
THEY HAVE NOTHING
THEY HAVE NOTHING BUT
THEY HAVE TO HELP US OUT.
THEY HAVE NOTHING BUT MONEY.
THEY
THEY ARE
THEY HAVE NOTHING BUT MONEY.
THEY ARE WONDERFUL.
I
I LOVE
THEY ARE WONDERFUL.
I LOVE THEIR
I LOVE THEIR INVESTING
THEY ARE WONDERFUL.
I LOVE THEIR INVESTING IN
I LOVE THEIR INVESTING IN THE
UNITED
UNITED STATES
I LOVE THEIR INVESTING IN THE
UNITED STATES GREAT
UNITED STATES GREAT I
I LOVE THEIR INVESTING IN THE
UNITED STATES GREAT I LOVE
UNITED STATES GREAT I LOVE THEIR
INVESTING
INVESTING IN
UNITED STATES GREAT I LOVE THEIR
INVESTING IN NEW
INVESTING IN NEW YORK.
THEY
THEY HAVE
INVESTING IN NEW YORK.
THEY HAVE TO
THEY HAVE TO HELP
INVESTING IN NEW YORK.
THEY HAVE TO HELP US.
WE
WE ARE
THEY HAVE TO HELP US.
WE ARE A
WE ARE A DEBTOR
THEY HAVE TO HELP US.
WE ARE A DEBTOR NATION.
$19
$19 TRILLION.
MASSIVE
MASSIVE UNFUNDED
$19 TRILLION.
MASSIVE UNFUNDED LIABILITIES.
WE
WE ARE
MASSIVE UNFUNDED LIABILITIES.
WE ARE A
WE ARE A NATION
MASSIVE UNFUNDED LIABILITIES.
WE ARE A NATION THAT
WE ARE A NATION THAT IS
MASSIVE UNFUNDED LIABILITIES.
WE ARE A NATION THAT IS IN
SERIOUS
SERIOUS TROUBLE
WE ARE A NATION THAT IS IN
SERIOUS TROUBLE AND
SERIOUS TROUBLE AND IT
WE ARE A NATION THAT IS IN
SERIOUS TROUBLE AND IT IS
SERIOUS TROUBLE AND IT IS GOING
UP
UP RAPIDLY.
OBAMACARE
OBAMACARE IS
UP RAPIDLY.
OBAMACARE IS A
OBAMACARE IS A DISASTER.
A
A CATASTROPHE.
[APPLAUSE]
IT
IT HAS
[APPLAUSE]
IT HAS GOT
IT HAS GOT TO
[APPLAUSE]
IT HAS GOT TO BE
IT HAS GOT TO BE REPEALED
[APPLAUSE]
IT HAS GOT TO BE REPEALED AND
REPLACED.
YOUR
YOUR PREMIUMS.
THEY
THEY HAVE
YOUR PREMIUMS.
THEY HAVE GONE
THEY HAVE GONE UP.
YOUR
YOUR DEDUCTIBLES
THEY HAVE GONE UP.
YOUR DEDUCTIBLES ARE
YOUR DEDUCTIBLES ARE THROUGH
THEY HAVE GONE UP.
YOUR DEDUCTIBLES ARE THROUGH THE
ROOF.
UNLESS
UNLESS YOU'RE
ROOF.
UNLESS YOU'RE HIT
UNLESS YOU'RE HIT BY
ROOF.
UNLESS YOU'RE HIT BY A
UNLESS YOU'RE HIT BY A TRACTOR.
IT
IT IS
UNLESS YOU'RE HIT BY A TRACTOR.
IT IS TRUE.
THE
THE REASON
IT IS TRUE.
THE REASON I
THE REASON I MENTION
IT IS TRUE.
THE REASON I MENTION TRACTORS,
JAPAN
JAPAN HAS
THE REASON I MENTION TRACTORS,
JAPAN HAS A
JAPAN HAS A GREAT
THE REASON I MENTION TRACTORS,
JAPAN HAS A GREAT LEADER.
ABE.
OUR
OUR NEGOTIATOR
ABE.
OUR NEGOTIATOR IS
OUR NEGOTIATOR IS CAROLYN
KENNEDY.
SHE
SHE GOT
KENNEDY.
SHE GOT THE
SHE GOT THE JOB
KENNEDY.
SHE GOT THE JOB BY
SHE GOT THE JOB BY GOING
KENNEDY.
SHE GOT THE JOB BY GOING INTO
THE
THE WHITE
SHE GOT THE JOB BY GOING INTO
THE WHITE HOUSE
THE WHITE HOUSE AND
SHE GOT THE JOB BY GOING INTO
THE WHITE HOUSE AND SAYING
THE WHITE HOUSE AND SAYING I
HAVE
HAVE NOTHING
THE WHITE HOUSE AND SAYING I
HAVE NOTHING TO
HAVE NOTHING TO DO.
SHE'S
SHE'S A
HAVE NOTHING TO DO.
SHE'S A NICE
SHE'S A NICE PERSON.
MY
MY DAUGHTER
SHE'S A NICE PERSON.
MY DAUGHTER LIKES
MY DAUGHTER LIKES HER.
MY
MY DAUGHTER
MY DAUGHTER LIKES HER.
MY DAUGHTER IS
MY DAUGHTER IS GREAT.
MY
MY DAUGHTER
MY DAUGHTER IS GREAT.
MY DAUGHTER LIKES
MY DAUGHTER LIKES HER.
SHE
SHE SAID
MY DAUGHTER LIKES HER.
SHE SAID SHE
SHE SAID SHE IS
MY DAUGHTER LIKES HER.
SHE SAID SHE IS A
SHE SAID SHE IS A NICE
MY DAUGHTER LIKES HER.
SHE SAID SHE IS A NICE PERSON.
WE
WE ARE
SHE SAID SHE IS A NICE PERSON.
WE ARE TIRED
WE ARE TIRED OF
SHE SAID SHE IS A NICE PERSON.
WE ARE TIRED OF THE
WE ARE TIRED OF THE NICE
SHE SAID SHE IS A NICE PERSON.
WE ARE TIRED OF THE NICE PEOPLE.
MR.
MR. TRUMP,
WE ARE TIRED OF THE NICE PEOPLE.
MR. TRUMP, A
MR. TRUMP, A WOMAN
WE ARE TIRED OF THE NICE PEOPLE.
MR. TRUMP, A WOMAN WHO
MR. TRUMP, A WOMAN WHO WAS
WE ARE TIRED OF THE NICE PEOPLE.
MR. TRUMP, A WOMAN WHO WAS A
FAN,
FAN, I
MR. TRUMP, A WOMAN WHO WAS A
FAN, I DON'T
FAN, I DON'T KNOW
MR. TRUMP, A WOMAN WHO WAS A
FAN, I DON'T KNOW IF
FAN, I DON'T KNOW IF OF
MR. TRUMP, A WOMAN WHO WAS A
FAN, I DON'T KNOW IF OF THE
PERSONALITY
PERSONALITY TO
FAN, I DON'T KNOW IF OF THE
PERSONALITY TO GET
PERSONALITY TO GET ELECTED.
YOU
YOU ARE
PERSONALITY TO GET ELECTED.
YOU ARE NOT
YOU ARE NOT A
PERSONALITY TO GET ELECTED.
YOU ARE NOT A NICE
YOU ARE NOT A NICE PERSON.
ACTUALLY
ACTUALLY I
YOU ARE NOT A NICE PERSON.
ACTUALLY I AM
ACTUALLY I AM A
YOU ARE NOT A NICE PERSON.
ACTUALLY I AM A NICE
ACTUALLY I AM A NICE PERSON.
I
I LOVE
ACTUALLY I AM A NICE PERSON.
I LOVE HELPING
I LOVE HELPING PEOPLE.
YOU
YOU WATCH.
I
I WILL
YOU WATCH.
I WILL HELP
I WILL HELP ON
YOU WATCH.
I WILL HELP ON WOMEN'S
I WILL HELP ON WOMEN'S HEALTH
ISSUES
ISSUES MORE
I WILL HELP ON WOMEN'S HEALTH
ISSUES MORE THAN
ISSUES MORE THAN ANYBODY
INCLUDING
INCLUDING THE
ISSUES MORE THAN ANYBODY
INCLUDING THE DEMOCRATIC
INCLUDING THE DEMOCRATIC SIDE.
YOU
YOU WATCH.
HE
HE SAID
YOU WATCH.
HE SAID I
HE SAID I DON'T
YOU WATCH.
HE SAID I DON'T WANT
HE SAID I DON'T WANT TO
YOU WATCH.
HE SAID I DON'T WANT TO FUND
WOMEN'S
WOMEN'S HEALTH
HE SAID I DON'T WANT TO FUND
WOMEN'S HEALTH ISSUES.
THAT
THAT IS
WOMEN'S HEALTH ISSUES.
THAT IS WORSE
THAT IS WORSE THAN
WOMEN'S HEALTH ISSUES.
THAT IS WORSE THAN ROMNEY'S
THAT IS WORSE THAN ROMNEY'S 47%
WHICH
WHICH IS
THAT IS WORSE THAN ROMNEY'S 47%
WHICH IS PROBABLY
WHICH IS PROBABLY WHY
THAT IS WORSE THAN ROMNEY'S 47%
WHICH IS PROBABLY WHY HE
WHICH IS PROBABLY WHY HE LOST
THE
THE ELECTION.
HE
HE FORGOT
THE ELECTION.
HE FORGOT TO
HE FORGOT TO GO
THE ELECTION.
HE FORGOT TO GO ON
HE FORGOT TO GO ON TELEVISION
FOR
FOR THREE
HE FORGOT TO GO ON TELEVISION
FOR THREE WEEKS.
WE
WE HAVE
FOR THREE WEEKS.
WE HAVE TO
WE HAVE TO DO
FOR THREE WEEKS.
WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING,
WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING, AND
FOR THREE WEEKS.
WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING, AND WE
HAVE
HAVE TO
WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING, AND WE
HAVE TO DO
HAVE TO DO IT
WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING, AND WE
HAVE TO DO IT FAST.
IF
IF WE
HAVE TO DO IT FAST.
IF WE DON'T
IF WE DON'T DO
HAVE TO DO IT FAST.
IF WE DON'T DO IT
IF WE DON'T DO IT FAST,
HAVE TO DO IT FAST.
IF WE DON'T DO IT FAST, WE
IF WE DON'T DO IT FAST, WE ARE
NOT
NOT GOING
IF WE DON'T DO IT FAST, WE ARE
NOT GOING TO
NOT GOING TO HAVE
IF WE DON'T DO IT FAST, WE ARE
NOT GOING TO HAVE A
NOT GOING TO HAVE A COUNTRY.
SPEAKING
SPEAKING OF
NOT GOING TO HAVE A COUNTRY.
SPEAKING OF THAT,
SPEAKING OF THAT, SPEAKING
NOT GOING TO HAVE A COUNTRY.
SPEAKING OF THAT, SPEAKING OF
THAT,
THAT, I
SPEAKING OF THAT, SPEAKING OF
THAT, I HAVE
THAT, I HAVE A
SPEAKING OF THAT, SPEAKING OF
THAT, I HAVE A GREAT
THAT, I HAVE A GREAT REVIEW
SPEAKING OF THAT, SPEAKING OF
THAT, I HAVE A GREAT REVIEW ON
THAT, I HAVE A GREAT REVIEW ON A
SPEECH
SPEECH THE
THAT, I HAVE A GREAT REVIEW ON A
SPEECH THE OTHER
SPEECH THE OTHER NIGHT.
HE
HE SPEAKS
SPEECH THE OTHER NIGHT.
HE SPEAKS THROUGH
HE SPEAKS THROUGH HIS
SPEECH THE OTHER NIGHT.
HE SPEAKS THROUGH HIS APPLAUSE.
I
I DO
HE SPEAKS THROUGH HIS APPLAUSE.
I DO HAVE
I DO HAVE TIME
HE SPEAKS THROUGH HIS APPLAUSE.
I DO HAVE TIME TO
I DO HAVE TIME TO WAIT
HE SPEAKS THROUGH HIS APPLAUSE.
I DO HAVE TIME TO WAIT FOR
I DO HAVE TIME TO WAIT FOR THE
APPLAUSE.
I
I WANT
APPLAUSE.
I WANT TO
I WANT TO JUST
APPLAUSE.
I WANT TO JUST DO
I WANT TO JUST DO IT.
HE
HE SAID
I WANT TO JUST DO IT.
HE SAID HE'S
HE SAID HE'S A
I WANT TO JUST DO IT.
HE SAID HE'S A GREAT
HE SAID HE'S A GREAT SPEAKER.
HE
HE DOES
HE SAID HE'S A GREAT SPEAKER.
HE DOES BEAUTIFULLY.
HE
HE IS
HE DOES BEAUTIFULLY.
HE IS NOT
HE IS NOT SCRIPTED.
SUPPOSING
SUPPOSING I
HE IS NOT SCRIPTED.
SUPPOSING I WAS
SUPPOSING I WAS READING
HE IS NOT SCRIPTED.
SUPPOSING I WAS READING THIS
STUFF.
BUT
BUT THE
STUFF.
BUT THE TELEPROMPTERS.
IF
IF YOU'RE
BUT THE TELEPROMPTERS.
IF YOU'RE RUNNING
IF YOU'RE RUNNING FOR
BUT THE TELEPROMPTERS.
IF YOU'RE RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT
YOU
YOU NOT
IF YOU'RE RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT
YOU NOT BE
YOU NOT BE ALLOWED
IF YOU'RE RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT
YOU NOT BE ALLOWED TO
YOU NOT BE ALLOWED TO USE
IF YOU'RE RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT
YOU NOT BE ALLOWED TO USE A
TELEPROMPTER.
IT
IT IS
TELEPROMPTER.
IT IS TRUE.
[APPLAUSE]
IT
IT IS
[APPLAUSE]
IT IS SO
IT IS SO EASY.
YOU
YOU WALK
IT IS SO EASY.
YOU WALK UP,
YOU WALK UP, LADIES
IT IS SO EASY.
YOU WALK UP, LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN
GENTLEMEN HELLO.
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
NO,
NO, NO.
YOU
YOU SHOULD
NO, NO.
YOU SHOULD NOT
YOU SHOULD NOT BE
NO, NO.
YOU SHOULD NOT BE ALLOWED.
YOU
YOU DON'T
YOU SHOULD NOT BE ALLOWED.
YOU DON'T KNOW
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU SHOULD NOT BE ALLOWED.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE GOING
TO
TO GET.
OBAMA
OBAMA IS
TO GET.
OBAMA IS A
OBAMA IS A TELEPROMPTER
TO GET.
OBAMA IS A TELEPROMPTER GOD.
IT
IT IS
OBAMA IS A TELEPROMPTER GOD.
IT IS TRUE.
YOU
YOU DON'T
IT IS TRUE.
YOU DON'T WANT
YOU DON'T WANT A
IT IS TRUE.
YOU DON'T WANT A SCRIPTED
PRESIDENT.
YOU
YOU DON'T
PRESIDENT.
YOU DON'T WANT
YOU DON'T WANT A
PRESIDENT.
YOU DON'T WANT A POLITICALLY
CORRECT
CORRECT PRESIDENT.
IT
IT TAKES
CORRECT PRESIDENT.
IT TAKES TOO
IT TAKES TOO MUCH.
[APPLAUSE]
IT
IT TAKES
[APPLAUSE]
IT TAKES TOO
IT TAKES TOO MUCH
[APPLAUSE]
IT TAKES TOO MUCH TIME.
IT
IT IS
IT TAKES TOO MUCH TIME.
IT IS TRUE.
IT
IT IS
IT IS TRUE.
YOU
YOU DON'T
IT IS TRUE.
YOU DON'T WANT
YOU DON'T WANT THIS
IT IS TRUE.
YOU DON'T WANT THIS POLITICAL
CORRECTNESS.
THERE
THERE IS
CORRECTNESS.
THERE IS A
THERE IS A CERTAIN
CORRECTNESS.
THERE IS A CERTAIN COLLEGE.
THEY
THEY DON'T
THERE IS A CERTAIN COLLEGE.
THEY DON'T WANT
THEY DON'T WANT YOU
THERE IS A CERTAIN COLLEGE.
THEY DON'T WANT YOU TO
DIFFERENTIATE
DIFFERENTIATE BETWEEN
THEY DON'T WANT YOU TO
DIFFERENTIATE BETWEEN A
DIFFERENTIATE BETWEEN A MAN
THEY DON'T WANT YOU TO
DIFFERENTIATE BETWEEN A MAN AND
A
A WOMAN.
YOU
YOU HEARD
A WOMAN.
YOU HEARD ABOUT
YOU HEARD ABOUT THIS
A WOMAN.
YOU HEARD ABOUT THIS ONE.
I'M
I'M GONE.
THAT
THAT IS
I'M GONE.
THAT IS TOO
THAT IS TOO MUCH.
THE
THE THINGS
THAT IS TOO MUCH.
THE THINGS THAT
THE THINGS THAT ARE
THAT IS TOO MUCH.
THE THINGS THAT ARE HAPPENING
ARE
ARE CRAZY.
YOU
YOU HAVE
ARE CRAZY.
YOU HAVE PROBABLY
YOU HAVE PROBABLY HEARD
ARE CRAZY.
YOU HAVE PROBABLY HEARD ABOUT
THE
THE DEBATE
YOU HAVE PROBABLY HEARD ABOUT
THE DEBATE WE
THE DEBATE WE JUST
YOU HAVE PROBABLY HEARD ABOUT
THE DEBATE WE JUST HAD
THE DEBATE WE JUST HAD RECENTLY.
IF
IF I
THE DEBATE WE JUST HAD RECENTLY.
IF I WERE
IF I WERE POLITICALLY
THE DEBATE WE JUST HAD RECENTLY.
IF I WERE POLITICALLY CORRECT
DURING
DURING THAT
IF I WERE POLITICALLY CORRECT
DURING THAT DEBATE
DURING THAT DEBATE I
IF I WERE POLITICALLY CORRECT
DURING THAT DEBATE I WOULD
DURING THAT DEBATE I WOULD HAVE
GOTTEN
GOTTEN CLOBBERED.
WE
WE WON
GOTTEN CLOBBERED.
WE WON THE
WE WON THE DEBATE.
AFTER
AFTER THE
WE WON THE DEBATE.
AFTER THE DEBATE
AFTER THE DEBATE ALL
WE WON THE DEBATE.
AFTER THE DEBATE ALL THE
AFTER THE DEBATE ALL THE POLL
NUMBERS
NUMBERS WENT
AFTER THE DEBATE ALL THE POLL
NUMBERS WENT UP
NUMBERS WENT UP WAS
AFTER THE DEBATE ALL THE POLL
NUMBERS WENT UP WAS THAT
NUMBERS WENT UP WAS THAT A
AFTER THE DEBATE ALL THE POLL
NUMBERS WENT UP WAS THAT A HOWL
OF
OF THE
NUMBERS WENT UP WAS THAT A HOWL
OF THE TIME?
WAS
WAS THAT
OF THE TIME?
WAS THAT INCREDIBLE?
THAT
THAT DEBATE
WAS THAT INCREDIBLE?
THAT DEBATE HAS
THAT DEBATE HAS ALWAYS
WAS THAT INCREDIBLE?
THAT DEBATE HAS ALWAYS HAD
THAT DEBATE HAS ALWAYS HAD 2
MILLION
MILLION PEOPLE.
THE
THE FIRST
MILLION PEOPLE.
THE FIRST DEBATE
THE FIRST DEBATE EVERY
MILLION PEOPLE.
THE FIRST DEBATE EVERY FOUR
YEARS.
24 MILLION
24 MILLION PEOPLE.
PROBABLY
PROBABLY GOING
24 MILLION PEOPLE.
PROBABLY GOING TO
PROBABLY GOING TO GO
24 MILLION PEOPLE.
PROBABLY GOING TO GO UP
PROBABLY GOING TO GO UP HIGHER
WHEN
WHEN THE
PROBABLY GOING TO GO UP HIGHER
WHEN THE FINAL
WHEN THE FINAL NUMBERS
PROBABLY GOING TO GO UP HIGHER
WHEN THE FINAL NUMBERS COME
WHEN THE FINAL NUMBERS COME IN.
DO
DO YOU
WHEN THE FINAL NUMBERS COME IN.
DO YOU THINK
DO YOU THINK THEY
WHEN THE FINAL NUMBERS COME IN.
DO YOU THINK THEY WERE
DO YOU THINK THEY WERE THERE
WHEN THE FINAL NUMBERS COME IN.
DO YOU THINK THEY WERE THERE FOR
JEB
JEB BUSH
DO YOU THINK THEY WERE THERE FOR
JEB BUSH OR
JEB BUSH OR RAND
DO YOU THINK THEY WERE THERE FOR
JEB BUSH OR RAND PAUL?
RAND,
RAND, I'VE
JEB BUSH OR RAND PAUL?
RAND, I'VE HAD
RAND, I'VE HAD YOU
JEB BUSH OR RAND PAUL?
RAND, I'VE HAD YOU UP
RAND, I'VE HAD YOU UP TO
JEB BUSH OR RAND PAUL?
RAND, I'VE HAD YOU UP TO HERE.
IT
IT IS
RAND, I'VE HAD YOU UP TO HERE.
IT IS FUNNY.
RAND
RAND PAUL
IT IS FUNNY.
RAND PAUL --
RAND PAUL -- SIT
IT IS FUNNY.
RAND PAUL -- SIT DOWN.
I
I WILL
RAND PAUL -- SIT DOWN.
I WILL ASK
I WILL ASK YOU
RAND PAUL -- SIT DOWN.
I WILL ASK YOU A
I WILL ASK YOU A QUESTION.
THAT
THAT IS
I WILL ASK YOU A QUESTION.
THAT IS OK.
I
I HAVE
THAT IS OK.
I HAVE SEEN
I HAVE SEEN HIS
THAT IS OK.
I HAVE SEEN HIS FACE
I HAVE SEEN HIS FACE BEFORE.
ONE
ONE AMONG
I HAVE SEEN HIS FACE BEFORE.
ONE AMONG ONE
ONE AMONG ONE TO
I HAVE SEEN HIS FACE BEFORE.
ONE AMONG ONE TO DO,
ONE AMONG ONE TO DO, NOT
I HAVE SEEN HIS FACE BEFORE.
ONE AMONG ONE TO DO, NOT TAKE
HIS
HIS QUESTION?
WAIT.
HE
HE HAS
WAIT.
HE HAS BEEN
HE HAS BEEN HITTING
WAIT.
HE HAS BEEN HITTING ME
HE HAS BEEN HITTING ME BECAUSE
HIS
HIS POLLS
HE HAS BEEN HITTING ME BECAUSE
HIS POLLS ARE
HIS POLLS ARE GOING
HE HAS BEEN HITTING ME BECAUSE
HIS POLLS ARE GOING DOWN.
HE
HE IS
HIS POLLS ARE GOING DOWN.
HE IS WEAK
HE IS WEAK ON
HIS POLLS ARE GOING DOWN.
HE IS WEAK ON MILITARY.
CAN
CAN YOU
HE IS WEAK ON MILITARY.
CAN YOU IMAGINE
CAN YOU IMAGINE TODAY
HE IS WEAK ON MILITARY.
CAN YOU IMAGINE TODAY BEING
CAN YOU IMAGINE TODAY BEING WEAK
ON
ON MILITARY?
NOW
NOW HE
ON MILITARY?
NOW HE HAS
NOW HE HAS BECOME
ON MILITARY?
NOW HE HAS BECOME WORSE
NOW HE HAS BECOME WORSE THAN
ON MILITARY?
NOW HE HAS BECOME WORSE THAN ME.
HE
HE HAS
NOW HE HAS BECOME WORSE THAN ME.
HE HAS BECOME
HE HAS BECOME THIS
NOW HE HAS BECOME WORSE THAN ME.
HE HAS BECOME THIS TOTAL
HE HAS BECOME THIS TOTAL HAWK.
THAT
THAT IS
HE HAS BECOME THIS TOTAL HAWK.
THAT IS GOOD.
RAND
RAND PAUL
THAT IS GOOD.
RAND PAUL IS
RAND PAUL IS WEAK
THAT IS GOOD.
RAND PAUL IS WEAK ON
RAND PAUL IS WEAK ON THE
MILITARY.
HE
HE IS
MILITARY.
HE IS WEAK
HE IS WEAK ON
MILITARY.
HE IS WEAK ON IMMIGRATION.
HE
HE HAS
HE IS WEAK ON IMMIGRATION.
HE HAS NO
HE HAS NO NUMBERS.
ALL
ALL OF
HE HAS NO NUMBERS.
ALL OF A
ALL OF A SUDDEN
HE HAS NO NUMBERS.
ALL OF A SUDDEN I
ALL OF A SUDDEN I SEE
HE HAS NO NUMBERS.
ALL OF A SUDDEN I SEE HIM.
HE
HE CALLED
ALL OF A SUDDEN I SEE HIM.
HE CALLED ME
HE CALLED ME UP
ALL OF A SUDDEN I SEE HIM.
HE CALLED ME UP AND
HE CALLED ME UP AND SAID
ALL OF A SUDDEN I SEE HIM.
HE CALLED ME UP AND SAID --
HE CALLED ME UP AND SAID -- HE
WANTS
WANTS TO
HE CALLED ME UP AND SAID -- HE
WANTS TO PLAY
WANTS TO PLAY A
HE CALLED ME UP AND SAID -- HE
WANTS TO PLAY A ROUND
WANTS TO PLAY A ROUND OF
HE CALLED ME UP AND SAID -- HE
WANTS TO PLAY A ROUND OF GOLF.
DON'T
DON'T TELL
WANTS TO PLAY A ROUND OF GOLF.
DON'T TELL ME.
I'M
I'M A
DON'T TELL ME.
I'M A GOOD
I'M A GOOD GOLFER.
I
I KILLED
I'M A GOOD GOLFER.
I KILLED HIM.
IF
IF I
I KILLED HIM.
IF I DIDN'T
IF I DIDN'T I
I KILLED HIM.
IF I DIDN'T I WOULDN'T
IF I DIDN'T I WOULDN'T SAY
I KILLED HIM.
IF I DIDN'T I WOULDN'T SAY IT.
HE
HE SAID
IF I DIDN'T I WOULDN'T SAY IT.
HE SAID TO
HE SAID TO YOU
IF I DIDN'T I WOULDN'T SAY IT.
HE SAID TO YOU THINK
HE SAID TO YOU THINK YOU
IF I DIDN'T I WOULDN'T SAY IT.
HE SAID TO YOU THINK YOU COULD
DO
DO ME
HE SAID TO YOU THINK YOU COULD
DO ME A
DO ME A FAVOR.
COULD
COULD YOU
DO ME A FAVOR.
COULD YOU CONTRIBUTE
COULD YOU CONTRIBUTE TO
DO ME A FAVOR.
COULD YOU CONTRIBUTE TO MY
COULD YOU CONTRIBUTE TO MY EYE
CENTER?
I
I SAID
CENTER?
I SAID WHAT
I SAID WHAT DO
CENTER?
I SAID WHAT DO YOU
I SAID WHAT DO YOU DO.
I
I JUST
I SAID WHAT DO YOU DO.
I JUST GAVE
I JUST GAVE HIM
I SAID WHAT DO YOU DO.
I JUST GAVE HIM A
I JUST GAVE HIM A LOT
I SAID WHAT DO YOU DO.
I JUST GAVE HIM A LOT OF
I JUST GAVE HIM A LOT OF MONEY.
ALL
ALL OF
I JUST GAVE HIM A LOT OF MONEY.
ALL OF A
ALL OF A SUDDEN
I JUST GAVE HIM A LOT OF MONEY.
ALL OF A SUDDEN I
ALL OF A SUDDEN I SEE
I JUST GAVE HIM A LOT OF MONEY.
ALL OF A SUDDEN I SEE HIM
CHIRPING
CHIRPING ON
ALL OF A SUDDEN I SEE HIM
CHIRPING ON THE
CHIRPING ON THE STAGE.
WHO
WHO IS
CHIRPING ON THE STAGE.
WHO IS THAT
WHO IS THAT OVER
CHIRPING ON THE STAGE.
WHO IS THAT OVER THERE,
WHO IS THAT OVER THERE, THAT
PERSON?
WHO
WHO IS
PERSON?
WHO IS HE?
NOW
NOW HE
WHO IS HE?
NOW HE IS
NOW HE IS GOING
WHO IS HE?
NOW HE IS GOING AROUND
NOW HE IS GOING AROUND SAYING
BAD
BAD THINGS.
WHATEVER.
THE
THE BEAUTY
WHATEVER.
THE BEAUTY IS
THE BEAUTY IS THIS.
NOBODY
NOBODY EVER
THE BEAUTY IS THIS.
NOBODY EVER ATTACKED
NOBODY EVER ATTACKED ME
THE BEAUTY IS THIS.
NOBODY EVER ATTACKED ME LIKE
SENATOR
SENATOR LINDSEY
NOBODY EVER ATTACKED ME LIKE
SENATOR LINDSEY GRAHAM.
HE
HE WENT
SENATOR LINDSEY GRAHAM.
HE WENT FROM
HE WENT FROM 1%
SENATOR LINDSEY GRAHAM.
HE WENT FROM 1% TO
HE WENT FROM 1% TO NOTHING.
[APPLAUSE]
IT
IT IS
[APPLAUSE]
IT IS TRUE.
NOBODY
NOBODY EVER
IT IS TRUE.
NOBODY EVER ATTACKED
NOBODY EVER ATTACKED ME
IT IS TRUE.
NOBODY EVER ATTACKED ME LIKE
PARRY,
PARRY, OF
NOBODY EVER ATTACKED ME LIKE
PARRY, OF TEXAS.
WHO
WHO DID
PARRY, OF TEXAS.
WHO DID A
WHO DID A LOUSY
PARRY, OF TEXAS.
WHO DID A LOUSY JOB
WHO DID A LOUSY JOB AT
PARRY, OF TEXAS.
WHO DID A LOUSY JOB AT THE
BORDER.
HE
HE WAS
BORDER.
HE WAS GOVERNOR
HE WAS GOVERNOR AND
BORDER.
HE WAS GOVERNOR AND HE
HE WAS GOVERNOR AND HE KEEPS
TALKING
TALKING ABOUT
HE WAS GOVERNOR AND HE KEEPS
TALKING ABOUT THE
TALKING ABOUT THE BORDER.
WHY
WHY DID
TALKING ABOUT THE BORDER.
WHY DID YOU
WHY DID YOU FIX
TALKING ABOUT THE BORDER.
WHY DID YOU FIX IT?
THE
THE NEW
WHY DID YOU FIX IT?
THE NEW GOVERNOR
THE NEW GOVERNOR IS
WHY DID YOU FIX IT?
THE NEW GOVERNOR IS DOING
THE NEW GOVERNOR IS DOING BETTER
BUT
BUT WE
THE NEW GOVERNOR IS DOING BETTER
BUT WE WON'T
BUT WE WON'T SAY
THE NEW GOVERNOR IS DOING BETTER
BUT WE WON'T SAY THAT.
HE'S
HE'S ACTUALLY
BUT WE WON'T SAY THAT.
HE'S ACTUALLY A
HE'S ACTUALLY A NICE
BUT WE WON'T SAY THAT.
HE'S ACTUALLY A NICE MAN.
HE
HE DIDN'T
HE'S ACTUALLY A NICE MAN.
HE DIDN'T LIKE
HE DIDN'T LIKE IT
HE'S ACTUALLY A NICE MAN.
HE DIDN'T LIKE IT WHEN
HE DIDN'T LIKE IT WHEN I
HE'S ACTUALLY A NICE MAN.
HE DIDN'T LIKE IT WHEN I SAID
YOU
YOU HAVE
HE DIDN'T LIKE IT WHEN I SAID
YOU HAVE TO
YOU HAVE TO PASS
HE DIDN'T LIKE IT WHEN I SAID
YOU HAVE TO PASS AN
YOU HAVE TO PASS AN IQ
HE DIDN'T LIKE IT WHEN I SAID
YOU HAVE TO PASS AN IQ TEST
YOU HAVE TO PASS AN IQ TEST TO
COME
COME ON
YOU HAVE TO PASS AN IQ TEST TO
COME ON THE
COME ON THE STAGE.
HE
HE SAID
COME ON THE STAGE.
HE SAID TO
HE SAID TO ME,
COME ON THE STAGE.
HE SAID TO ME, DONALD
HE SAID TO ME, DONALD TRUMP
COME ON THE STAGE.
HE SAID TO ME, DONALD TRUMP IS
KEEPING
KEEPING A
HE SAID TO ME, DONALD TRUMP IS
KEEPING A SENATOR,
KEEPING A SENATOR, A
HE SAID TO ME, DONALD TRUMP IS
KEEPING A SENATOR, A FAILED
SENATOR,
SENATOR, OFF
KEEPING A SENATOR, A FAILED
SENATOR, OFF THE
SENATOR, OFF THE STAGE.
WENT
WENT TO
SENATOR, OFF THE STAGE.
WENT TO THE
WENT TO THE BEST
SENATOR, OFF THE STAGE.
WENT TO THE BEST SCHOOLS,
WENT TO THE BEST SCHOOLS, GREAT
STUDENT.
MADE
MADE A
STUDENT.
MADE A FORTUNE.
DID
DID THE
MADE A FORTUNE.
DID THE APPRENTICE,
DID THE APPRENTICE, ONE
MADE A FORTUNE.
DID THE APPRENTICE, ONE OF
DID THE APPRENTICE, ONE OF THE
MOST
MOST SUCCESSFUL
DID THE APPRENTICE, ONE OF THE
MOST SUCCESSFUL SHOWS
MOST SUCCESSFUL SHOWS ON
TELEVISION.
NBC
NBC RENEWED
TELEVISION.
NBC RENEWED IT.
NBC
NBC RENEWED
NBC RENEWED IT.
NBC RENEWED IT,
NBC RENEWED IT, CAME
NBC RENEWED IT.
NBC RENEWED IT, CAME TO
NBC RENEWED IT, CAME TO MY
OFFICE
OFFICE AND
NBC RENEWED IT, CAME TO MY
OFFICE AND SAID
OFFICE AND SAID PLEASE
NBC RENEWED IT, CAME TO MY
OFFICE AND SAID PLEASE DO
OFFICE AND SAID PLEASE DO IT.
I
I WANT
OFFICE AND SAID PLEASE DO IT.
I WANT TO
I WANT TO MAKE
OFFICE AND SAID PLEASE DO IT.
I WANT TO MAKE THIS
I WANT TO MAKE THIS COUNTRY
GREAT
GREAT AGAIN.
WE
WE ARE
GREAT AGAIN.
WE ARE GOING
WE ARE GOING TO
GREAT AGAIN.
WE ARE GOING TO MAKE
WE ARE GOING TO MAKE THE
GREAT AGAIN.
WE ARE GOING TO MAKE THE COUNTRY
GREAT.
[APPLAUSE]
I
I WROTE
[APPLAUSE]
I WROTE MANY
I WROTE MANY BESTSELLERS
INCLUDING
INCLUDING TRUMP,
I WROTE MANY BESTSELLERS
INCLUDING TRUMP, THE
INCLUDING TRUMP, THE ART
I WROTE MANY BESTSELLERS
INCLUDING TRUMP, THE ART OF
INCLUDING TRUMP, THE ART OF THE
DEAL,
DEAL, THE
INCLUDING TRUMP, THE ART OF THE
DEAL, THE NUMBER
DEAL, THE NUMBER ONE
INCLUDING TRUMP, THE ART OF THE
DEAL, THE NUMBER ONE SELLING
BUSINESS
BUSINESS BOOK
DEAL, THE NUMBER ONE SELLING
BUSINESS BOOK OF
BUSINESS BOOK OF ALL
DEAL, THE NUMBER ONE SELLING
BUSINESS BOOK OF ALL TIME.
HE'S
HE'S GOT
BUSINESS BOOK OF ALL TIME.
HE'S GOT IT.
THE
THE OTHER
HE'S GOT IT.
THE OTHER NIGHT
THE OTHER NIGHT I
HE'S GOT IT.
THE OTHER NIGHT I SAID
THE OTHER NIGHT I SAID MY
HE'S GOT IT.
THE OTHER NIGHT I SAID MY SECOND
FAVORITE
FAVORITE BOOK.
MY
MY FIRST
FAVORITE BOOK.
MY FIRST FAVORITE.
THE
THE BIBLE.
I
I DID
THE BIBLE.
I DID NOT
I DID NOT ASK
THE BIBLE.
I DID NOT ASK HIM
I DID NOT ASK HIM TO
THE BIBLE.
I DID NOT ASK HIM TO STAND
I DID NOT ASK HIM TO STAND UP.
I
I GOT
I DID NOT ASK HIM TO STAND UP.
I GOT MY
I GOT MY BIGGEST
I DID NOT ASK HIM TO STAND UP.
I GOT MY BIGGEST HIM
I GOT MY BIGGEST HIM THE
I DID NOT ASK HIM TO STAND UP.
I GOT MY BIGGEST HIM THE OTHER
NIGHT
NIGHT WHEN
I GOT MY BIGGEST HIM THE OTHER
NIGHT WHEN I
NIGHT WHEN I SAID
I GOT MY BIGGEST HIM THE OTHER
NIGHT WHEN I SAID THAT.
I
I SAID
NIGHT WHEN I SAID THAT.
I SAID MY
I SAID MY FAVORITE
NIGHT WHEN I SAID THAT.
I SAID MY FAVORITE BOOK
I SAID MY FAVORITE BOOK IS
NIGHT WHEN I SAID THAT.
I SAID MY FAVORITE BOOK IS THE
BIBLE.
MY
MY SECOND
BIBLE.
MY SECOND FAVORITE
MY SECOND FAVORITE BOOK
BIBLE.
MY SECOND FAVORITE BOOK IS
MY SECOND FAVORITE BOOK IS "THE
ART
ART OF
MY SECOND FAVORITE BOOK IS "THE
ART OF THE
ART OF THE DEAL."
BUT
BUT ANYWAY,
ART OF THE DEAL."
BUT ANYWAY, SO,
BUT ANYWAY, SO, THESE
ART OF THE DEAL."
BUT ANYWAY, SO, THESE PEOPLE
THEY
THEY WENT
BUT ANYWAY, SO, THESE PEOPLE
THEY WENT DOWN.
SO,
SO, NOW
THEY WENT DOWN.
SO, NOW I
SO, NOW I HAVE,
THEY WENT DOWN.
SO, NOW I HAVE, I
SO, NOW I HAVE, I HAVE
THEY WENT DOWN.
SO, NOW I HAVE, I HAVE A
SO, NOW I HAVE, I HAVE A NEW
THEY WENT DOWN.
SO, NOW I HAVE, I HAVE A NEW GUY
COMING.
IT'S
IT'S RAND
COMING.
IT'S RAND PAUL.
CARLY
CARLY WAS
IT'S RAND PAUL.
CARLY WAS NASTY
CARLY WAS NASTY TO
IT'S RAND PAUL.
CARLY WAS NASTY TO ME.
THE
THE CAREFUL,
CARLY WAS NASTY TO ME.
THE CAREFUL, CARLY.
I
I CANNOT
THE CAREFUL, CARLY.
I CANNOT SAY
I CANNOT SAY ANYTHING
THE CAREFUL, CARLY.
I CANNOT SAY ANYTHING TO
I CANNOT SAY ANYTHING TO HER
BECAUSE
BECAUSE SHE
I CANNOT SAY ANYTHING TO HER
BECAUSE SHE WAS
BECAUSE SHE WAS A
I CANNOT SAY ANYTHING TO HER
BECAUSE SHE WAS A WOMAN
BECAUSE SHE WAS A WOMAN AND
I CANNOT SAY ANYTHING TO HER
BECAUSE SHE WAS A WOMAN AND I
BECAUSE SHE WAS A WOMAN AND I DO
NOT
NOT WANT
BECAUSE SHE WAS A WOMAN AND I DO
NOT WANT TO
NOT WANT TO BE
BECAUSE SHE WAS A WOMAN AND I DO
NOT WANT TO BE ACCUSED
NOT WANT TO BE ACCUSED OF
BECAUSE SHE WAS A WOMAN AND I DO
NOT WANT TO BE ACCUSED OF BEING
TOUGH
TOUGH ON
NOT WANT TO BE ACCUSED OF BEING
TOUGH ON A
TOUGH ON A WOMAN.
I
I CANNOT
TOUGH ON A WOMAN.
I CANNOT DO
I CANNOT DO THAT.
WOMEN,
WOMEN, AM
I CANNOT DO THAT.
WOMEN, AM I
WOMEN, AM I ALLOWED
I CANNOT DO THAT.
WOMEN, AM I ALLOWED TO
WOMEN, AM I ALLOWED TO FIGHT
BACK?
AM
AM I
BACK?
AM I ALLOWED?
SHE
SHE HAS
AM I ALLOWED?
SHE HAS BEEN
SHE HAS BEEN NASTY
AM I ALLOWED?
SHE HAS BEEN NASTY TO
SHE HAS BEEN NASTY TO ME.
SO
SO I
SHE HAS BEEN NASTY TO ME.
SO I PROMISED
SO I PROMISED I
SHE HAS BEEN NASTY TO ME.
SO I PROMISED I WOULD
SO I PROMISED I WOULD NOT
SHE HAS BEEN NASTY TO ME.
SO I PROMISED I WOULD NOT SAY
SO I PROMISED I WOULD NOT SAY --
I
I SAID
SO I PROMISED I WOULD NOT SAY --
I SAID TO
I SAID TO MYSELF.
I
I PROMISED
I SAID TO MYSELF.
I PROMISED I
I PROMISED I WOULD
I SAID TO MYSELF.
I PROMISED I WOULD NOT
I PROMISED I WOULD NOT SAY
I SAID TO MYSELF.
I PROMISED I WOULD NOT SAY THAT
SHE
SHE RAN
I PROMISED I WOULD NOT SAY THAT
SHE RAN HEWLETT
SHE RAN HEWLETT PACKARD
I PROMISED I WOULD NOT SAY THAT
SHE RAN HEWLETT PACKARD INTO
SHE RAN HEWLETT PACKARD INTO THE
GROUND.
I
I SAID
GROUND.
I SAID I
I SAID I WOULD
GROUND.
I SAID I WOULD NOT
I SAID I WOULD NOT SAY
GROUND.
I SAID I WOULD NOT SAY THAT
I SAID I WOULD NOT SAY THAT HER
STOCK
STOCK VALUE
I SAID I WOULD NOT SAY THAT HER
STOCK VALUE TANKED.
SHE
SHE LAID
STOCK VALUE TANKED.
SHE LAID OFF
SHE LAID OFF TENS
STOCK VALUE TANKED.
SHE LAID OFF TENS OF
SHE LAID OFF TENS OF THOUSANDS
OF
OF PEOPLE.
SHE
SHE GOT
OF PEOPLE.
SHE GOT VICIOUSLY
SHE GOT VICIOUSLY FIRED.
I
I SAID
SHE GOT VICIOUSLY FIRED.
I SAID I
I SAID I WILL
SHE GOT VICIOUSLY FIRED.
I SAID I WILL NOT
I SAID I WILL NOT SAY
SHE GOT VICIOUSLY FIRED.
I SAID I WILL NOT SAY THAT.
SHE
SHE THEN
I SAID I WILL NOT SAY THAT.
SHE THEN WENT
SHE THEN WENT OUT
I SAID I WILL NOT SAY THAT.
SHE THEN WENT OUT AND
SHE THEN WENT OUT AND RAN
AGAINST
AGAINST BARBARA
SHE THEN WENT OUT AND RAN
AGAINST BARBARA BOXER
AGAINST BARBARA BOXER FOR
SHE THEN WENT OUT AND RAN
AGAINST BARBARA BOXER FOR THE
UNITED
UNITED STATES
AGAINST BARBARA BOXER FOR THE
UNITED STATES SENATE
UNITED STATES SENATE IN
CALIFORNIA.
A
A RACE
CALIFORNIA.
A RACE THAT
A RACE THAT SHOULD'VE
CALIFORNIA.
A RACE THAT SHOULD'VE BEEN
A RACE THAT SHOULD'VE BEEN WON
AND
AND SHE
A RACE THAT SHOULD'VE BEEN WON
AND SHE LOST
AND SHE LOST IN
A RACE THAT SHOULD'VE BEEN WON
AND SHE LOST IN THE
AND SHE LOST IN THE LANDSLIDE.
I
I SAID,
AND SHE LOST IN THE LANDSLIDE.
I SAID, I
I SAID, I WILL
AND SHE LOST IN THE LANDSLIDE.
I SAID, I WILL NOT
I SAID, I WILL NOT SAY
AND SHE LOST IN THE LANDSLIDE.
I SAID, I WILL NOT SAY THAT,
I SAID, I WILL NOT SAY THAT, OK?
ALL
ALL RIGHT?
SO
SO I
ALL RIGHT?
SO I AM
SO I AM NOT
ALL RIGHT?
SO I AM NOT GOING
SO I AM NOT GOING TO
ALL RIGHT?
SO I AM NOT GOING TO SAY
SO I AM NOT GOING TO SAY IT.
SO
SO OUR
SO I AM NOT GOING TO SAY IT.
SO OUR COUNTRY
SO OUR COUNTRY HAS
SO I AM NOT GOING TO SAY IT.
SO OUR COUNTRY HAS TREMENDOUS
POTENTIAL.
WE
WE HAVE
POTENTIAL.
WE HAVE TO
WE HAVE TO TAKE
POTENTIAL.
WE HAVE TO TAKE BACK
WE HAVE TO TAKE BACK OUR
POTENTIAL.
WE HAVE TO TAKE BACK OUR JOBS
FROM
FROM CHINA
WE HAVE TO TAKE BACK OUR JOBS
FROM CHINA AND
FROM CHINA AND ALL
WE HAVE TO TAKE BACK OUR JOBS
FROM CHINA AND ALL OF
FROM CHINA AND ALL OF THE
WE HAVE TO TAKE BACK OUR JOBS
FROM CHINA AND ALL OF THE OTHER
PEOPLE.
WE
WE HAVE
PEOPLE.
WE HAVE TO
WE HAVE TO RENEGOTIATE
PEOPLE.
WE HAVE TO RENEGOTIATE OUR
WE HAVE TO RENEGOTIATE OUR TRADE
DEALS
DEALS BY
WE HAVE TO RENEGOTIATE OUR TRADE
DEALS BY GETTING
DEALS BY GETTING PEOPLE
WE HAVE TO RENEGOTIATE OUR TRADE
DEALS BY GETTING PEOPLE LIKE
CARL
CARL ICAHN.
WE
WE HAVE
CARL ICAHN.
WE HAVE THE
WE HAVE THE GREATEST
CARL ICAHN.
WE HAVE THE GREATEST DEALMAKERS
IN
IN THE
WE HAVE THE GREATEST DEALMAKERS
IN THE WORLD.
CARL
CARL IS
IN THE WORLD.
CARL IS VERY
CARL IS VERY BUSY.
I
I CALLED
CARL IS VERY BUSY.
I CALLED HIM,
I CALLED HIM, HE
CARL IS VERY BUSY.
I CALLED HIM, HE SAID,
I CALLED HIM, HE SAID, YOU
CARL IS VERY BUSY.
I CALLED HIM, HE SAID, YOU ARE
DOING
DOING GREAT.
TOUGH
TOUGH GUY.
EVERY
EVERY POLL,
TOUGH GUY.
EVERY POLL, YOU
EVERY POLL, YOU ARE
TOUGH GUY.
EVERY POLL, YOU ARE DOING
AMAZING.
JUST
JUST RELAX.
IF
IF I
JUST RELAX.
IF I WIN,
IF I WIN, YOU
JUST RELAX.
IF I WIN, YOU TAKE
IF I WIN, YOU TAKE CHINA.
I'LL
I'LL GET
IF I WIN, YOU TAKE CHINA.
I'LL GET SOMEBODY
I'LL GET SOMEBODY ELSE
IF I WIN, YOU TAKE CHINA.
I'LL GET SOMEBODY ELSE TO
I'LL GET SOMEBODY ELSE TO TAKE
THIS
THIS ONE.
WE
WE WILL
THIS ONE.
WE WILL HAVE
WE WILL HAVE OUR
THIS ONE.
WE WILL HAVE OUR BEST.
THESE
THESE PEOPLE.
CARL
CARL IS
THESE PEOPLE.
CARL IS A
CARL IS A NICE
THESE PEOPLE.
CARL IS A NICE GUY.
SOME
SOME OF
CARL IS A NICE GUY.
SOME OF THEM
SOME OF THEM ARE
CARL IS A NICE GUY.
SOME OF THEM ARE NOT
SOME OF THEM ARE NOT NICE.
SOME
SOME ARE
SOME OF THEM ARE NOT NICE.
SOME ARE HORRIBLE
SOME ARE HORRIBLE HUMAN
SOME OF THEM ARE NOT NICE.
SOME ARE HORRIBLE HUMAN BEINGS
BUT
BUT THEY
SOME ARE HORRIBLE HUMAN BEINGS
BUT THEY ARE
BUT THEY ARE THE
SOME ARE HORRIBLE HUMAN BEINGS
BUT THEY ARE THE GREATEST
BUT THEY ARE THE GREATEST IN
SOME ARE HORRIBLE HUMAN BEINGS
BUT THEY ARE THE GREATEST IN THE
WORLD.
DO
DO WE
WORLD.
DO WE WANT
DO WE WANT NICE
WORLD.
DO WE WANT NICE PEOPLE
DO WE WANT NICE PEOPLE OR
WORLD.
DO WE WANT NICE PEOPLE OR DO
DO WE WANT NICE PEOPLE OR DO WE
WANT
WANT THESE
DO WE WANT NICE PEOPLE OR DO WE
WANT THESE HORRIBLE
WANT THESE HORRIBLE HUMAN
DO WE WANT NICE PEOPLE OR DO WE
WANT THESE HORRIBLE HUMAN BEINGS
NEGOTIATING?
HORRIBLE.
I
I WANT
HORRIBLE.
I WANT THE
I WANT THE HORRIBLE
HORRIBLE.
I WANT THE HORRIBLE ONES.
WE
WE WILL
I WANT THE HORRIBLE ONES.
WE WILL MAKE
WE WILL MAKE GREAT
I WANT THE HORRIBLE ONES.
WE WILL MAKE GREAT TRADE
WE WILL MAKE GREAT TRADE DEALS.
WE
WE WILL
WE WILL MAKE GREAT TRADE DEALS.
WE WILL SAVE
WE WILL SAVE SOCIAL
WE WILL MAKE GREAT TRADE DEALS.
WE WILL SAVE SOCIAL SECURITY
WITHOUT
WITHOUT CUTS.
WE
WE WILL
WITHOUT CUTS.
WE WILL COME
WE WILL COME UP
WITHOUT CUTS.
WE WILL COME UP WITH
WE WILL COME UP WITH HEALTH
WITHOUT CUTS.
WE WILL COME UP WITH HEALTH CARE
PLANS
PLANS THAT
WE WILL COME UP WITH HEALTH CARE
PLANS THAT WILL
PLANS THAT WILL BE
WE WILL COME UP WITH HEALTH CARE
PLANS THAT WILL BE PHENOMENAL,
PHENOMENAL.
THAT
THAT WILL
PHENOMENAL.
THAT WILL BE
THAT WILL BE LESS
PHENOMENAL.
THAT WILL BE LESS EXPENSIVE.
WE
WE HAVE
THAT WILL BE LESS EXPENSIVE.
WE HAVE TO
WE HAVE TO GET
THAT WILL BE LESS EXPENSIVE.
WE HAVE TO GET RID
WE HAVE TO GET RID OF
THAT WILL BE LESS EXPENSIVE.
WE HAVE TO GET RID OF THE
ARTIFICIAL
ARTIFICIAL CIRCLES.
I
I CALL
ARTIFICIAL CIRCLES.
I CALL THEM
I CALL THEM THE
ARTIFICIAL CIRCLES.
I CALL THEM THE INSURANCE
COMPANY
COMPANY CIRCLES.
YOU
YOU KNOW
COMPANY CIRCLES.
YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU KNOW WHAT I
COMPANY CIRCLES.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
WE
WE HAVE
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
WE HAVE TO
WE HAVE TO GET
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
WE HAVE TO GET RID
WE HAVE TO GET RID OF
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
WE HAVE TO GET RID OF THE
ARTIFICIAL
ARTIFICIAL CIRCLES
WE HAVE TO GET RID OF THE
ARTIFICIAL CIRCLES WRAPPING
AROUND
AROUND THE
ARTIFICIAL CIRCLES WRAPPING
AROUND THE STATES
AROUND THE STATES ALL
ARTIFICIAL CIRCLES WRAPPING
AROUND THE STATES ALL PAID
AROUND THE STATES ALL PAID FOR
BY
BY YOUR
AROUND THE STATES ALL PAID FOR
BY YOUR LOCAL
BY YOUR LOCAL INSURANCE
COMPANIES.
BECAUSE
BECAUSE THEY
COMPANIES.
BECAUSE THEY HAVE
BECAUSE THEY HAVE MONOPOLIES.
I
I HAVE
BECAUSE THEY HAVE MONOPOLIES.
I HAVE A
I HAVE A HUGE
BECAUSE THEY HAVE MONOPOLIES.
I HAVE A HUGE COMPANY.
IF
IF I'M
I HAVE A HUGE COMPANY.
IF I'M IN
IF I'M IN NEW
I HAVE A HUGE COMPANY.
IF I'M IN NEW YORK,
IF I'M IN NEW YORK, I
I HAVE A HUGE COMPANY.
IF I'M IN NEW YORK, I GET
IF I'M IN NEW YORK, I GET NO
BIDS.
I
I GET
BIDS.
I GET ONE
I GET ONE BID.
I
I GO
I GET ONE BID.
I GO TO
I GO TO NEW
I GET ONE BID.
I GO TO NEW JERSEY.
I
I GO
I GO TO NEW JERSEY.
I GO TO
I GO TO CALIFORNIA.
I
I GO
I GO TO CALIFORNIA.
I GO TO
I GO TO FLORIDA.
THERE'S
THERE'S NO
I GO TO FLORIDA.
THERE'S NO BIDS.
BECAUSE
BECAUSE THEY
THERE'S NO BIDS.
BECAUSE THEY HAVE
BECAUSE THEY HAVE MONOPOLY.
SO,
SO, THEY
BECAUSE THEY HAVE MONOPOLY.
SO, THEY WOULD
SO, THEY WOULD RATHER
BECAUSE THEY HAVE MONOPOLY.
SO, THEY WOULD RATHER HAVE
MONOPOLY
MONOPOLY THAN
SO, THEY WOULD RATHER HAVE
MONOPOLY THAN BE
MONOPOLY THAN BE ABLE
SO, THEY WOULD RATHER HAVE
MONOPOLY THAN BE ABLE TO
NEGOTIATE
NEGOTIATE ALL
MONOPOLY THAN BE ABLE TO
NEGOTIATE ALL OVER
NEGOTIATE ALL OVER THE
MONOPOLY THAN BE ABLE TO
NEGOTIATE ALL OVER THE COUNTRY.
THEY
THEY WOULD
NEGOTIATE ALL OVER THE COUNTRY.
THEY WOULD RATHER
THEY WOULD RATHER HAVE
NEGOTIATE ALL OVER THE COUNTRY.
THEY WOULD RATHER HAVE NEW
THEY WOULD RATHER HAVE NEW YORK
SEWED
SEWED UP
THEY WOULD RATHER HAVE NEW YORK
SEWED UP THAN
SEWED UP THAN HAVE
THEY WOULD RATHER HAVE NEW YORK
SEWED UP THAN HAVE COMPETITION
WITH
WITH A
SEWED UP THAN HAVE COMPETITION
WITH A HAVE
WITH A HAVE TO
SEWED UP THAN HAVE COMPETITION
WITH A HAVE TO GO
WITH A HAVE TO GO AND
SEWED UP THAN HAVE COMPETITION
WITH A HAVE TO GO AND WORK
WITH A HAVE TO GO AND WORK FOR
THEIR
THEIR MONEY.
THAT
THAT IS
THEIR MONEY.
THAT IS OVER.
THAT'S
THAT'S OVER.
[APPLAUSE]
AND
AND YOU
[APPLAUSE]
AND YOU HAVE
AND YOU HAVE PHENOMENAL
[APPLAUSE]
AND YOU HAVE PHENOMENAL PLANTS
--
-- FOR
AND YOU HAVE PHENOMENAL PLANTS
-- FOR MUCH
-- FOR MUCH LESS
AND YOU HAVE PHENOMENAL PLANTS
-- FOR MUCH LESS MONEY.
INSURANCE
INSURANCE COMPANIES
-- FOR MUCH LESS MONEY.
INSURANCE COMPANIES WILL
INSURANCE COMPANIES WILL NOT
-- FOR MUCH LESS MONEY.
INSURANCE COMPANIES WILL NOT BE
HAPPY
HAPPY BUT
INSURANCE COMPANIES WILL NOT BE
HAPPY BUT YOU
HAPPY BUT YOU HAVE
INSURANCE COMPANIES WILL NOT BE
HAPPY BUT YOU HAVE TO
HAPPY BUT YOU HAVE TO --
INSURANCE COMPANIES WILL NOT BE
HAPPY BUT YOU HAVE TO -- THEY
GIVE
GIVE TO
HAPPY BUT YOU HAVE TO -- THEY
GIVE TO JEB.
THEY
THEY GIVE
GIVE TO JEB.
THEY GIVE TO
THEY GIVE TO HILLARY.
THEY
THEY GET
THEY GIVE TO HILLARY.
THEY GET TO
THEY GET TO EVERYBODY.
I
I DO
THEY GET TO EVERYBODY.
I DO NOT
I DO NOT WANT
THEY GET TO EVERYBODY.
I DO NOT WANT THEIR
I DO NOT WANT THEIR MONEY.
I
I WAS
I DO NOT WANT THEIR MONEY.
I WAS CALLED
I WAS CALLED TODAY
I DO NOT WANT THEIR MONEY.
I WAS CALLED TODAY BY
I WAS CALLED TODAY BY THE
BIGGEST
BIGGEST LOBBYIST.
HE
HE SAID,
BIGGEST LOBBYIST.
HE SAID, DONALD,
HE SAID, DONALD, I
BIGGEST LOBBYIST.
HE SAID, DONALD, I WOULD
HE SAID, DONALD, I WOULD LOVE
BIGGEST LOBBYIST.
HE SAID, DONALD, I WOULD LOVE TO
MAKE
MAKE A
HE SAID, DONALD, I WOULD LOVE TO
MAKE A MAJOR
MAKE A MAJOR CONTRIBUTION
HE SAID, DONALD, I WOULD LOVE TO
MAKE A MAJOR CONTRIBUTION TO
YOUR
YOUR CAMPAIGN.
I
I DO
YOUR CAMPAIGN.
I DO NOT
I DO NOT WANT
YOUR CAMPAIGN.
I DO NOT WANT YOUR
I DO NOT WANT YOUR MONEY.
NO,
NO, YOU
I DO NOT WANT YOUR MONEY.
NO, YOU DO
NO, YOU DO NOT
I DO NOT WANT YOUR MONEY.
NO, YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND.
IT
IT WAS
NO, YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND.
IT WAS LIKE
IT WAS LIKE HE
NO, YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND.
IT WAS LIKE HE NEVER
IT WAS LIKE HE NEVER HEARD
NO, YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND.
IT WAS LIKE HE NEVER HEARD THIS
BEFORE.
HE
HE SAID,
BEFORE.
HE SAID, I
HE SAID, I WANT
BEFORE.
HE SAID, I WANT TO
HE SAID, I WANT TO GET
BEFORE.
HE SAID, I WANT TO GET $4
MILLION.
YOU
YOU ARE
MILLION.
YOU ARE LEADING
YOU ARE LEADING IN
MILLION.
YOU ARE LEADING IN ALL
YOU ARE LEADING IN ALL THE
POLLS.
THEY
THEY HAVE
POLLS.
THEY HAVE TO
THEY HAVE TO PROTECT,
POLLS.
THEY HAVE TO PROTECT, TRUMP
WINS,
WINS, THEY
THEY HAVE TO PROTECT, TRUMP
WINS, THEY HAVE
WINS, THEY HAVE GOT
THEY HAVE TO PROTECT, TRUMP
WINS, THEY HAVE GOT TO
WINS, THEY HAVE GOT TO PROTECT
THEMSELVES.
I
I SAID,
THEMSELVES.
I SAID, YOU
I SAID, YOU ARE
THEMSELVES.
I SAID, YOU ARE FRONT
I SAID, YOU ARE FRONT A
THEMSELVES.
I SAID, YOU ARE FRONT A MONTH
I SAID, YOU ARE FRONT A MONTH OR
IT
IT I
I SAID, YOU ARE FRONT A MONTH OR
IT I DO
IT I DO NOT
I SAID, YOU ARE FRONT A MONTH OR
IT I DO NOT WANT
IT I DO NOT WANT YOUR
I SAID, YOU ARE FRONT A MONTH OR
IT I DO NOT WANT YOUR MONEY.
BECAUSE
BECAUSE WHAT
IT I DO NOT WANT YOUR MONEY.
BECAUSE WHAT HE
BECAUSE WHAT HE IS
IT I DO NOT WANT YOUR MONEY.
BECAUSE WHAT HE IS GOING
BECAUSE WHAT HE IS GOING TO
IT I DO NOT WANT YOUR MONEY.
BECAUSE WHAT HE IS GOING TO DO
IS
IS IF
BECAUSE WHAT HE IS GOING TO DO
IS IF I
IS IF I WIN
BECAUSE WHAT HE IS GOING TO DO
IS IF I WIN AND
IS IF I WIN AND WHEN
BECAUSE WHAT HE IS GOING TO DO
IS IF I WIN AND WHEN ONE
IS IF I WIN AND WHEN ONE OF
BECAUSE WHAT HE IS GOING TO DO
IS IF I WIN AND WHEN ONE OF HIS
COMPANIES
COMPANIES HAS
IS IF I WIN AND WHEN ONE OF HIS
COMPANIES HAS A
COMPANIES HAS A PROBLEM,
IS IF I WIN AND WHEN ONE OF HIS
COMPANIES HAS A PROBLEM, I'M
GOING
GOING TO
COMPANIES HAS A PROBLEM, I'M
GOING TO DO
GOING TO DO WHAT
COMPANIES HAS A PROBLEM, I'M
GOING TO DO WHAT IS
GOING TO DO WHAT IS RIGHT
COMPANIES HAS A PROBLEM, I'M
GOING TO DO WHAT IS RIGHT FOR
THE
THE PEOPLE
GOING TO DO WHAT IS RIGHT FOR
THE PEOPLE OF
THE PEOPLE OF THE
GOING TO DO WHAT IS RIGHT FOR
THE PEOPLE OF THE COUNTRY.
[APPLAUSE]
I'M
I'M NOT
[APPLAUSE]
I'M NOT GOING
I'M NOT GOING TO
[APPLAUSE]
I'M NOT GOING TO DO
I'M NOT GOING TO DO WHAT
[APPLAUSE]
I'M NOT GOING TO DO WHAT IS
RIGHT
RIGHT FOR
I'M NOT GOING TO DO WHAT IS
RIGHT FOR HIM
RIGHT FOR HIM AND
I'M NOT GOING TO DO WHAT IS
RIGHT FOR HIM AND HIS
RIGHT FOR HIM AND HIS PEOPLE.
SO
SO YOU
RIGHT FOR HIM AND HIS PEOPLE.
SO YOU HAVE
SO YOU HAVE THE
RIGHT FOR HIM AND HIS PEOPLE.
SO YOU HAVE THE SPECIAL
SO YOU HAVE THE SPECIAL INTEREST
PEOPLE
PEOPLE AND
SO YOU HAVE THE SPECIAL INTEREST
PEOPLE AND YOU
PEOPLE AND YOU HAVE
SO YOU HAVE THE SPECIAL INTEREST
PEOPLE AND YOU HAVE THE
PEOPLE AND YOU HAVE THE DONORS.
I
I WILL
PEOPLE AND YOU HAVE THE DONORS.
I WILL TELL
I WILL TELL YOU
PEOPLE AND YOU HAVE THE DONORS.
I WILL TELL YOU NOBODY
I WILL TELL YOU NOBODY IS
PEOPLE AND YOU HAVE THE DONORS.
I WILL TELL YOU NOBODY IS GOING
TO
TO CONTROL
I WILL TELL YOU NOBODY IS GOING
TO CONTROL US.
WE
WE ARE
TO CONTROL US.
WE ARE GOING
WE ARE GOING TO
TO CONTROL US.
WE ARE GOING TO WORK
WE ARE GOING TO WORK THIS
TOGETHER
TOGETHER AND
WE ARE GOING TO WORK THIS
TOGETHER AND MAKE
TOGETHER AND MAKE IT
WE ARE GOING TO WORK THIS
TOGETHER AND MAKE IT SO
TOGETHER AND MAKE IT SO STRONG
AND
AND SO
TOGETHER AND MAKE IT SO STRONG
AND SO GREAT.
I
I USE
AND SO GREAT.
I USE THE
I USE THE CONCEPT
AND SO GREAT.
I USE THE CONCEPT OF
I USE THE CONCEPT OF THE
AND SO GREAT.
I USE THE CONCEPT OF THE FORD
PLANT
PLANT BUILT
I USE THE CONCEPT OF THE FORD
PLANT BUILT IN
PLANT BUILT IN MEXICO.
WE
WE WANT
PLANT BUILT IN MEXICO.
WE WANT IT
WE WANT IT BUILT
PLANT BUILT IN MEXICO.
WE WANT IT BUILT IN
WE WANT IT BUILT IN MICHIGAN.
WE
WE WANT
WE WANT IT BUILT IN MICHIGAN.
WE WANT IT
WE WANT IT BUILT
WE WANT IT BUILT IN MICHIGAN.
WE WANT IT BUILT IN
WE WANT IT BUILT IN NEW
HAMPSHIRE.
WE
WE WANT
HAMPSHIRE.
WE WANT IT
WE WANT IT BUILT
HAMPSHIRE.
WE WANT IT BUILT IN
WE WANT IT BUILT IN IOWA.
HOW
HOW DOES
WE WANT IT BUILT IN IOWA.
HOW DOES IT
HOW DOES IT HELP
WE WANT IT BUILT IN IOWA.
HOW DOES IT HELP US?
HOW
HOW DOES
HOW DOES IT HELP US?
HOW DOES IT
HOW DOES IT HELP
HOW DOES IT HELP US?
YOU
YOU GO
HOW DOES IT HELP US?
YOU GO TO
YOU GO TO THE
HOW DOES IT HELP US?
YOU GO TO THE GREAT
YOU GO TO THE GREAT BUSINESS
SCHOOLS
SCHOOLS AND
YOU GO TO THE GREAT BUSINESS
SCHOOLS AND YOU
SCHOOLS AND YOU DO
YOU GO TO THE GREAT BUSINESS
SCHOOLS AND YOU DO REALLY
SCHOOLS AND YOU DO REALLY WELL
AND
AND THEN
SCHOOLS AND YOU DO REALLY WELL
AND THEN YOU
AND THEN YOU COME
SCHOOLS AND YOU DO REALLY WELL
AND THEN YOU COME HOME
AND THEN YOU COME HOME AND
SCHOOLS AND YOU DO REALLY WELL
AND THEN YOU COME HOME AND SAY,
LET'S
LET'S FIGURE
AND THEN YOU COME HOME AND SAY,
LET'S FIGURE THIS
LET'S FIGURE THIS OUT.
THEY'RE
THEY'RE GOING
LET'S FIGURE THIS OUT.
THEY'RE GOING TO
THEY'RE GOING TO SPEND
LET'S FIGURE THIS OUT.
THEY'RE GOING TO SPEND $2.5
BILLION
BILLION BUILDING
THEY'RE GOING TO SPEND $2.5
BILLION BUILDING A
BILLION BUILDING A PLANT
THEY'RE GOING TO SPEND $2.5
BILLION BUILDING A PLANT IN
MEXICO.
THEY'RE
THEY'RE GOING
MEXICO.
THEY'RE GOING TO
THEY'RE GOING TO MAKE
MEXICO.
THEY'RE GOING TO MAKE CARS,
TRACKS
TRACKS AND
THEY'RE GOING TO MAKE CARS,
TRACKS AND PARTS
TRACKS AND PARTS AND
THEY'RE GOING TO MAKE CARS,
TRACKS AND PARTS AND SHIP
TRACKS AND PARTS AND SHIP IT
BACK
BACK TO
TRACKS AND PARTS AND SHIP IT
BACK TO THE
BACK TO THE UNITED
TRACKS AND PARTS AND SHIP IT
BACK TO THE UNITED STATES.
HOW
HOW DOES
BACK TO THE UNITED STATES.
HOW DOES THAT
HOW DOES THAT HELP
BACK TO THE UNITED STATES.
HOW DOES THAT HELP US?
WE
WE GET
HOW DOES THAT HELP US?
WE GET NO
WE GET NO TAX.
SO,
SO, WHEN
WE GET NO TAX.
SO, WHEN JEB
SO, WHEN JEB BECOMES
WE GET NO TAX.
SO, WHEN JEB BECOMES PRESIDENT,
IF
IF THAT
SO, WHEN JEB BECOMES PRESIDENT,
IF THAT EVER
IF THAT EVER HAPPENS,
SO, WHEN JEB BECOMES PRESIDENT,
IF THAT EVER HAPPENS, OR
IF THAT EVER HAPPENS, OR WHEN
HILLARY,
HILLARY, IF
IF THAT EVER HAPPENS, OR WHEN
HILLARY, IF THAT
HILLARY, IF THAT EVER
IF THAT EVER HAPPENS, OR WHEN
HILLARY, IF THAT EVER HAPPENS,
OR
OR WHEN
HILLARY, IF THAT EVER HAPPENS,
OR WHEN --
[CROWD
[CROWD BOOING]
HEY,
HEY, IT
[CROWD BOOING]
HEY, IT CAN
HEY, IT CAN HAPPEN,
[CROWD BOOING]
HEY, IT CAN HAPPEN, FOLKS.
I
I THINK
HEY, IT CAN HAPPEN, FOLKS.
I THINK IT
I THINK IT IS
HEY, IT CAN HAPPEN, FOLKS.
I THINK IT IS UNLIKELY
I THINK IT IS UNLIKELY BUT
HEY, IT CAN HAPPEN, FOLKS.
I THINK IT IS UNLIKELY BUT IF
JEB
JEB BECAME
I THINK IT IS UNLIKELY BUT IF
JEB BECAME PRESIDENT,
JEB BECAME PRESIDENT, WHEN
I THINK IT IS UNLIKELY BUT IF
JEB BECAME PRESIDENT, WHEN THEY
SAY
SAY MR.
JEB BECAME PRESIDENT, WHEN THEY
SAY MR. PRESIDENT,
SAY MR. PRESIDENT, IT
JEB BECAME PRESIDENT, WHEN THEY
SAY MR. PRESIDENT, IT IS
SAY MR. PRESIDENT, IT IS VERY
BAD
BAD THAT
SAY MR. PRESIDENT, IT IS VERY
BAD THAT FORD
BAD THAT FORD IS
SAY MR. PRESIDENT, IT IS VERY
BAD THAT FORD IS BUILDING
BAD THAT FORD IS BUILDING IN
MEXICO.
OK,
OK, WE
MEXICO.
OK, WE WILL
OK, WE WILL DO
MEXICO.
OK, WE WILL DO SOMETHING.
LET
LET ME
OK, WE WILL DO SOMETHING.
LET ME GO
LET ME GO TO
OK, WE WILL DO SOMETHING.
LET ME GO TO SLEEP
LET ME GO TO SLEEP FIRST.
WE
WE WILL
LET ME GO TO SLEEP FIRST.
WE WILL DO
WE WILL DO SOMETHING
LET ME GO TO SLEEP FIRST.
WE WILL DO SOMETHING ABOUT
WE WILL DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
AS
AS SOON
WE WILL DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
AS SOON AS
AS SOON AS HE
WE WILL DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
AS SOON AS HE SAYS
AS SOON AS HE SAYS WE
WE WILL DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
AS SOON AS HE SAYS WE WILL
AS SOON AS HE SAYS WE WILL DO
SOMETHING,
SOMETHING, HE
AS SOON AS HE SAYS WE WILL DO
SOMETHING, HE IS
SOMETHING, HE IS NOT
AS SOON AS HE SAYS WE WILL DO
SOMETHING, HE IS NOT STUPID.
THE
THE LOBBYISTS
SOMETHING, HE IS NOT STUPID.
THE LOBBYISTS WILL
THE LOBBYISTS WILL CALL
SOMETHING, HE IS NOT STUPID.
THE LOBBYISTS WILL CALL HIM.
THEY
THEY GAVE
THE LOBBYISTS WILL CALL HIM.
THEY GAVE THEM
THEY GAVE THEM SOME
THE LOBBYISTS WILL CALL HIM.
THEY GAVE THEM SOME OF
THEY GAVE THEM SOME OF THIS
THE LOBBYISTS WILL CALL HIM.
THEY GAVE THEM SOME OF THIS $114
MILLION.
AND
AND THE
MILLION.
AND THE SPECIAL
AND THE SPECIAL INTEREST.
WE
WE HAVE
AND THE SPECIAL INTEREST.
WE HAVE STOCK
WE HAVE STOCK IN
AND THE SPECIAL INTEREST.
WE HAVE STOCK IN FORD.
WE
WE WANT
WE HAVE STOCK IN FORD.
WE WANT FORD
WE WANT FORD TO
WE HAVE STOCK IN FORD.
WE WANT FORD TO DO
WE WANT FORD TO DO WHAT
WE HAVE STOCK IN FORD.
WE WANT FORD TO DO WHAT THEY
WANT.
AND
AND THE
WANT.
AND THE LOBBYISTS
AND THE LOBBYISTS WILL
WANT.
AND THE LOBBYISTS WILL GO
AND THE LOBBYISTS WILL GO UP
WANT.
AND THE LOBBYISTS WILL GO UP TO
HIM
HIM AND
AND THE LOBBYISTS WILL GO UP TO
HIM AND SAY,
HIM AND SAY, MR.
AND THE LOBBYISTS WILL GO UP TO
HIM AND SAY, MR. PRESIDENT,
HIM AND SAY, MR. PRESIDENT, YOU
CANNOT
CANNOT DO
HIM AND SAY, MR. PRESIDENT, YOU
CANNOT DO THIS.
THESE
THESE PEOPLE
CANNOT DO THIS.
THESE PEOPLE GAVE
THESE PEOPLE GAVE YOU
CANNOT DO THIS.
THESE PEOPLE GAVE YOU $2
MILLION.
THAT'S
THAT'S RIGHT.
AND
AND THEY
THAT'S RIGHT.
AND THEY WILL
AND THEY WILL BUILD
THAT'S RIGHT.
AND THEY WILL BUILD HAPPILY
AND THEY WILL BUILD HAPPILY AND
THEY
THEY WILL
AND THEY WILL BUILD HAPPILY AND
THEY WILL HAVE
THEY WILL HAVE A
AND THEY WILL BUILD HAPPILY AND
THEY WILL HAVE A NICE
THEY WILL HAVE A NICE PLANT
AND THEY WILL BUILD HAPPILY AND
THEY WILL HAVE A NICE PLANT AND
WE
WE WILL
THEY WILL HAVE A NICE PLANT AND
WE WILL LOSE
WE WILL LOSE THOUSANDS
THEY WILL HAVE A NICE PLANT AND
WE WILL LOSE THOUSANDS OF
WE WILL LOSE THOUSANDS OF JOBS.
TERRIBLE.
WHAT
WHAT I
TERRIBLE.
WHAT I SAY
WHAT I SAY IS
TERRIBLE.
WHAT I SAY IS DIFFERENT.
THEY
THEY WILL
WHAT I SAY IS DIFFERENT.
THEY WILL CALL
THEY WILL CALL ME
WHAT I SAY IS DIFFERENT.
THEY WILL CALL ME TO
THEY WILL CALL ME TO BUT
WHAT I SAY IS DIFFERENT.
THEY WILL CALL ME TO BUT I
THEY WILL CALL ME TO BUT I WOULD
NOT
NOT EVEN
THEY WILL CALL ME TO BUT I WOULD
NOT EVEN TAKE
NOT EVEN TAKE THEIR
THEY WILL CALL ME TO BUT I WOULD
NOT EVEN TAKE THEIR CALL.
SOME
SOME OF
NOT EVEN TAKE THEIR CALL.
SOME OF THEM
SOME OF THEM ARE
NOT EVEN TAKE THEIR CALL.
SOME OF THEM ARE ACTUALLY
SOME OF THEM ARE ACTUALLY NICE
GUYS.
I'LL
I'LL SAY
GUYS.
I'LL SAY NO.
BY
BY THE
I'LL SAY NO.
BY THE WAY,
BY THE WAY, I
I'LL SAY NO.
BY THE WAY, I HOPE
BY THE WAY, I HOPE THE
I'LL SAY NO.
BY THE WAY, I HOPE THE PRESS
CALLS
CALLS CARL
BY THE WAY, I HOPE THE PRESS
CALLS CARL ICAHN.
HE'S
HE'S WEALTHY.
THEY
THEY ALL
HE'S WEALTHY.
THEY ALL WANT
THEY ALL WANT TO
HE'S WEALTHY.
THEY ALL WANT TO DO
THEY ALL WANT TO DO IT.
A
A GUY
THEY ALL WANT TO DO IT.
A GUY LIKE
A GUY LIKE CARL
THEY ALL WANT TO DO IT.
A GUY LIKE CARL ICAHN
A GUY LIKE CARL ICAHN IS
THEY ALL WANT TO DO IT.
A GUY LIKE CARL ICAHN IS WORTH
MANY
MANY BILLIONS
A GUY LIKE CARL ICAHN IS WORTH
MANY BILLIONS OF
MANY BILLIONS OF DOLLARS.
HE
HE WANTS
MANY BILLIONS OF DOLLARS.
HE WANTS TO
HE WANTS TO DO
MANY BILLIONS OF DOLLARS.
HE WANTS TO DO IT.
IT'S
IT'S MORE
HE WANTS TO DO IT.
IT'S MORE IMPORTANT
IT'S MORE IMPORTANT TO
HE WANTS TO DO IT.
IT'S MORE IMPORTANT TO HIM
IT'S MORE IMPORTANT TO HIM --
HE WANTS TO DO IT.
IT'S MORE IMPORTANT TO HIM -- HE
DOES
DOES NOT
IT'S MORE IMPORTANT TO HIM -- HE
DOES NOT KNOW
DOES NOT KNOW --
HOW
HOW MANY
DOES NOT KNOW --
HOW MANY DEALS
HOW MANY DEALS CAN
DOES NOT KNOW --
HOW MANY DEALS CAN YOU
HOW MANY DEALS CAN YOU DO?
THE
THE GREAT
HOW MANY DEALS CAN YOU DO?
THE GREAT DEAL
THE GREAT DEAL IS
HOW MANY DEALS CAN YOU DO?
THE GREAT DEAL IS THIS
THE GREAT DEAL IS THIS COUNTRY.
WE
WE HAVE
THE GREAT DEAL IS THIS COUNTRY.
WE HAVE TO
WE HAVE TO MAKE
THE GREAT DEAL IS THIS COUNTRY.
WE HAVE TO MAKE THIS
WE HAVE TO MAKE THIS COUNTRY
RICH.
AND
AND THEN
RICH.
AND THEN WE
AND THEN WE HAVE
RICH.
AND THEN WE HAVE GOT
AND THEN WE HAVE GOT TO
RICH.
AND THEN WE HAVE GOT TO MAKE
AND THEN WE HAVE GOT TO MAKE IT
GREAT.
[APPLAUSE]
AND
AND I
[APPLAUSE]
AND I SAID
AND I SAID THE
[APPLAUSE]
AND I SAID THE SAME
AND I SAID THE SAME THING
[APPLAUSE]
AND I SAID THE SAME THING TO
OTHERS.
THEY
THEY COME
OTHERS.
THEY COME TO
THEY COME TO TRUMP,
I
I WOULD
THEY COME TO TRUMP,
I WOULD NOT
I WOULD NOT CALL
THEY COME TO TRUMP,
I WOULD NOT CALL ANY
I WOULD NOT CALL ANY OF
THEY COME TO TRUMP,
I WOULD NOT CALL ANY OF THESE
GUYS
GUYS BECAUSE
I WOULD NOT CALL ANY OF THESE
GUYS BECAUSE THEY
GUYS BECAUSE THEY ARE
I WOULD NOT CALL ANY OF THESE
GUYS BECAUSE THEY ARE TOO
GUYS BECAUSE THEY ARE TOO EASY.
HE
HE WOKE
GUYS BECAUSE THEY ARE TOO EASY.
HE WOKE ME
HE WOKE ME UP,
GUYS BECAUSE THEY ARE TOO EASY.
HE WOKE ME UP, MR.
HE WOKE ME UP, MR. PRESIDENT,
GUYS BECAUSE THEY ARE TOO EASY.
HE WOKE ME UP, MR. PRESIDENT, WE
REALLY
REALLY WANT
HE WOKE ME UP, MR. PRESIDENT, WE
REALLY WANT TO
REALLY WANT TO BUILD
HE WOKE ME UP, MR. PRESIDENT, WE
REALLY WANT TO BUILD THIS
REALLY WANT TO BUILD THIS PLAN
TO
TO MEXICO.
I
I SAID,
TO MEXICO.
I SAID, CONGRATULATIONS
I SAID, CONGRATULATIONS BUT
YOU'RE
YOU'RE NOT
I SAID, CONGRATULATIONS BUT
YOU'RE NOT GOING
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
I SAID, CONGRATULATIONS BUT
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO DO
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO DO IT.
THAT'S
THAT'S OK.
THAT
THAT WE
THAT'S OK.
THAT WE ARE
THAT WE ARE GOING
THAT'S OK.
THAT WE ARE GOING TO
THAT WE ARE GOING TO CHARGE
THAT'S OK.
THAT WE ARE GOING TO CHARGE TO
CHARGE
CHARGE YOU
THAT WE ARE GOING TO CHARGE TO
CHARGE YOU A
CHARGE YOU A 35%
THAT WE ARE GOING TO CHARGE TO
CHARGE YOU A 35% TAX
CHARGE YOU A 35% TAX ON
THAT WE ARE GOING TO CHARGE TO
CHARGE YOU A 35% TAX ON EVERY
CAR
CAR AND
CHARGE YOU A 35% TAX ON EVERY
CAR AND TRUCK
CAR AND TRUCK AND
CHARGE YOU A 35% TAX ON EVERY
CAR AND TRUCK AND PART
CAR AND TRUCK AND PART THAT
COMES
COMES INTO
CAR AND TRUCK AND PART THAT
COMES INTO OUR
COMES INTO OUR COUNTRY.
EVERY
EVERY SINGLE
COMES INTO OUR COUNTRY.
EVERY SINGLE ONE.
35%.
HE
HE SAYS,
35%.
HE SAYS, YOU
HE SAYS, YOU CANNOT
35%.
HE SAYS, YOU CANNOT DO
HE SAYS, YOU CANNOT DO THAT
35%.
HE SAYS, YOU CANNOT DO THAT OR
TRUST
TRUST ME.
I
I CAN
TRUST ME.
I CAN DO
I CAN DO IT.
WHAT
WHAT HAPPENS
I CAN DO IT.
WHAT HAPPENS IT'S
WHAT HAPPENS IT'S PROBABLY
I CAN DO IT.
WHAT HAPPENS IT'S PROBABLY THEY
FOLD
FOLD BEFORE
WHAT HAPPENS IT'S PROBABLY THEY
FOLD BEFORE 5:00.
IT
IT COULD
FOLD BEFORE 5:00.
IT COULD BE
IT COULD BE THEY
FOLD BEFORE 5:00.
IT COULD BE THEY WILL
IT COULD BE THEY WILL PLAY
FOLD BEFORE 5:00.
IT COULD BE THEY WILL PLAY TOUGH
AND
AND WAIT
IT COULD BE THEY WILL PLAY TOUGH
AND WAIT UNTIL
AND WAIT UNTIL THE
IT COULD BE THEY WILL PLAY TOUGH
AND WAIT UNTIL THE NEXT
AND WAIT UNTIL THE NEXT DAY.
I
I SAY
AND WAIT UNTIL THE NEXT DAY.
I SAY THEY
I SAY THEY FOLD
AND WAIT UNTIL THE NEXT DAY.
I SAY THEY FOLD BEFORE
I SAY THEY FOLD BEFORE 5:00.
THE
THE REASON
I SAY THEY FOLD BEFORE 5:00.
THE REASON I
THE REASON I WOULD
I SAY THEY FOLD BEFORE 5:00.
THE REASON I WOULD NOT
THE REASON I WOULD NOT WASTE
I SAY THEY FOLD BEFORE 5:00.
THE REASON I WOULD NOT WASTE THE
TIME
TIME OF
THE REASON I WOULD NOT WASTE THE
TIME OF THE
TIME OF THE KILLERS
THE REASON I WOULD NOT WASTE THE
TIME OF THE KILLERS I
TIME OF THE KILLERS I TOLD
THE REASON I WOULD NOT WASTE THE
TIME OF THE KILLERS I TOLD YOU
ABOUT,
ABOUT, THE
TIME OF THE KILLERS I TOLD YOU
ABOUT, THE GREAT
ABOUT, THE GREAT NEGOTIATORS
BECAUSE
BECAUSE THIS
ABOUT, THE GREAT NEGOTIATORS
BECAUSE THIS IS
BECAUSE THIS IS TOO
ABOUT, THE GREAT NEGOTIATORS
BECAUSE THIS IS TOO EASY.
THIS
THIS IS
BECAUSE THIS IS TOO EASY.
THIS IS A
THIS IS A COUPLE
BECAUSE THIS IS TOO EASY.
THIS IS A COUPLE OF
THIS IS A COUPLE OF PHONE
BECAUSE THIS IS TOO EASY.
THIS IS A COUPLE OF PHONE CALLS.
SO,
SO, WHAT
THIS IS A COUPLE OF PHONE CALLS.
SO, WHAT HAPPENS
SO, WHAT HAPPENS NOW
THIS IS A COUPLE OF PHONE CALLS.
SO, WHAT HAPPENS NOW IS
SO, WHAT HAPPENS NOW IS THE
THIS IS A COUPLE OF PHONE CALLS.
SO, WHAT HAPPENS NOW IS THE NEXT
DAY
DAY THEY
SO, WHAT HAPPENS NOW IS THE NEXT
DAY THEY WILL
DAY THEY WILL CALL
SO, WHAT HAPPENS NOW IS THE NEXT
DAY THEY WILL CALL UP.
AND
AND THEY
DAY THEY WILL CALL UP.
AND THEY WILL
AND THEY WILL SAY,
DAY THEY WILL CALL UP.
AND THEY WILL SAY, PLEASE.
I
I SAY,
AND THEY WILL SAY, PLEASE.
I SAY, NO,
I SAY, NO, I
AND THEY WILL SAY, PLEASE.
I SAY, NO, I WANT
I SAY, NO, I WANT YOU
AND THEY WILL SAY, PLEASE.
I SAY, NO, I WANT YOU BUILDING
IN
IN THE
I SAY, NO, I WANT YOU BUILDING
IN THE UNITED
IN THE UNITED STATES.
THAT
THAT IS
IN THE UNITED STATES.
THAT IS THE
THAT IS THE WAY
IN THE UNITED STATES.
THAT IS THE WAY IT
THAT IS THE WAY IT IS.
AND
AND THEY
THAT IS THE WAY IT IS.
AND THEY WILL
AND THEY WILL SAY,
THAT IS THE WAY IT IS.
AND THEY WILL SAY, MR.
PRESIDENT,
PRESIDENT, WE
AND THEY WILL SAY, MR.
PRESIDENT, WE ARE
PRESIDENT, WE ARE BUILDING
AND THEY WILL SAY, MR.
PRESIDENT, WE ARE BUILDING OUR
PLANT
PLANT IN
PRESIDENT, WE ARE BUILDING OUR
PLANT IN THE
PLANT IN THE UNITED
PRESIDENT, WE ARE BUILDING OUR
PLANT IN THE UNITED STATES.
IT'S
IT'S THAT
PLANT IN THE UNITED STATES.
IT'S THAT SIMPLE.
IT'S
IT'S THAT
IT'S THAT SIMPLE.
WHO
WHO WOULD
IT'S THAT SIMPLE.
WHO WOULD LET
WHO WOULD LET NABISCO
IT'S THAT SIMPLE.
WHO WOULD LET NABISCO GO
WHO WOULD LET NABISCO GO TO
MEXICO?
WHO
WHO WOULD
MEXICO?
WHO WOULD LET
WHO WOULD LET THESE
MEXICO?
WHO WOULD LET THESE CAR
COMPANIES
COMPANIES --
WHO WOULD LET THESE CAR
COMPANIES -- IN
COMPANIES -- IN TENNESSEE
WHO WOULD LET THESE CAR
COMPANIES -- IN TENNESSEE THEY
WERE
WERE RESPECTING
COMPANIES -- IN TENNESSEE THEY
WERE RESPECTING A
WERE RESPECTING A GREAT
COMPANIES -- IN TENNESSEE THEY
WERE RESPECTING A GREAT DEAL
WITH
WITH A
WERE RESPECTING A GREAT DEAL
WITH A MAJOR
WITH A MAJOR FOREIGN
WERE RESPECTING A GREAT DEAL
WITH A MAJOR FOREIGN CAR
COMPANY.
BUILT
BUILT IN
COMPANY.
BUILT IN TENNESSEE.
GOING
GOING TO
BUILT IN TENNESSEE.
GOING TO BE
GOING TO BE BUILT
BUILT IN TENNESSEE.
GOING TO BE BUILT IN
GOING TO BE BUILT IN TENNESSEE.
GOING
GOING TO
GOING TO BE BUILT IN TENNESSEE.
GOING TO BE
GOING TO BE A
GOING TO BE BUILT IN TENNESSEE.
GOING TO BE A GREAT
GOING TO BE A GREAT DEAL.
AT
AT THE
GOING TO BE A GREAT DEAL.
AT THE LAST
AT THE LAST MOMENT,
GOING TO BE A GREAT DEAL.
AT THE LAST MOMENT, THEY
ANNOUNCED
ANNOUNCED THEY
AT THE LAST MOMENT, THEY
ANNOUNCED THEY ARE
ANNOUNCED THEY ARE NOT
AT THE LAST MOMENT, THEY
ANNOUNCED THEY ARE NOT GOING
ANNOUNCED THEY ARE NOT GOING TO
DO
DO IT
ANNOUNCED THEY ARE NOT GOING TO
DO IT IN
DO IT IN TENNESSEE.
THEY
THEY WILL
DO IT IN TENNESSEE.
THEY WILL DO
THEY WILL DO IT
DO IT IN TENNESSEE.
THEY WILL DO IT IN
THEY WILL DO IT IN MEXICO.
WHO
WHO WOULD
THEY WILL DO IT IN MEXICO.
WHO WOULD ALLOW
WHO WOULD ALLOW THAT
THEY WILL DO IT IN MEXICO.
WHO WOULD ALLOW THAT TO
WHO WOULD ALLOW THAT TO HAPPEN?
>>
>> OBAMA.
MR.
MR. TRUMP:
>> OBAMA.
MR. TRUMP: YOU
MR. TRUMP: YOU ARE
>> OBAMA.
MR. TRUMP: YOU ARE RIGHT
MR. TRUMP: YOU ARE RIGHT ABOUT
THAT.
IT
IT WILL
THAT.
IT WILL NOT
IT WILL NOT HAPPEN
THAT.
IT WILL NOT HAPPEN WITH
IT WILL NOT HAPPEN WITH TRUMP.
BELIEVE
BELIEVE ME.
WITH
WITH TRUMP,
BELIEVE ME.
WITH TRUMP, IT
WITH TRUMP, IT WON'T
BELIEVE ME.
WITH TRUMP, IT WON'T HAPPEN.
THIS
THIS GUY
WITH TRUMP, IT WON'T HAPPEN.
THIS GUY --
THIS GUY -- I
WITH TRUMP, IT WON'T HAPPEN.
THIS GUY -- I HOPE
THIS GUY -- I HOPE THIS
QUESTION
QUESTION IS
THIS GUY -- I HOPE THIS
QUESTION IS WORTH
QUESTION IS WORTH IT.
THIS
THIS GUY
QUESTION IS WORTH IT.
THIS GUY HAS
THIS GUY HAS BEEN
QUESTION IS WORTH IT.
THIS GUY HAS BEEN STANDING
THIS GUY HAS BEEN STANDING UP
FOR
FOR THE
THIS GUY HAS BEEN STANDING UP
FOR THE ENTIRE
FOR THE ENTIRE THING.
I
I HOPE
FOR THE ENTIRE THING.
I HOPE IT
I HOPE IT WILL
FOR THE ENTIRE THING.
I HOPE IT WILL BE
I HOPE IT WILL BE A
FOR THE ENTIRE THING.
I HOPE IT WILL BE A GOOD
QUESTION.
GO
GO AHEAD.
>>
>> 30
GO AHEAD.
>> 30 YEARS,
>> 30 YEARS, I'VE
GO AHEAD.
>> 30 YEARS, I'VE HAD
>> 30 YEARS, I'VE HAD THREATS
GO AHEAD.
>> 30 YEARS, I'VE HAD THREATS ON
MY
MY LIFE
>> 30 YEARS, I'VE HAD THREATS ON
MY LIFE --
AND
AND FOX
MY LIFE --
AND FOX HASN'T
AND FOX HASN'T TOUCHED
MY LIFE --
AND FOX HASN'T TOUCHED THIS.
I
I HAVE
AND FOX HASN'T TOUCHED THIS.
I HAVE BEEN
I HAVE BEEN IN
AND FOX HASN'T TOUCHED THIS.
I HAVE BEEN IN TOUCH
I HAVE BEEN IN TOUCH WITH
AND FOX HASN'T TOUCHED THIS.
I HAVE BEEN IN TOUCH WITH KELLY,
TOO.
MR.
MR. TRUMP:
TOO.
MR. TRUMP: COME
MR. TRUMP: COME ON.
GOT
GOT TO
MR. TRUMP: COME ON.
GOT TO GO.
GO
GO AHEAD.
>>
>> THERE'S
GO AHEAD.
>> THERE'S COUNTERFEIT
SUBSTANDARD
SUBSTANDARD PARTS
>> THERE'S COUNTERFEIT
SUBSTANDARD PARTS AND
SUBSTANDARD PARTS AND MOST
>> THERE'S COUNTERFEIT
SUBSTANDARD PARTS AND MOST OF
THE
THE NUCLEAR
SUBSTANDARD PARTS AND MOST OF
THE NUCLEAR PLANTS
THE NUCLEAR PLANTS --
MR.
MR. TRUMP:
THE NUCLEAR PLANTS --
MR. TRUMP: IN
MR. TRUMP: IN NUCLEAR
THE NUCLEAR PLANTS --
MR. TRUMP: IN NUCLEAR PLANTS
MR. TRUMP: IN NUCLEAR PLANTS IN
THE
THE UNITED
MR. TRUMP: IN NUCLEAR PLANTS IN
THE UNITED STATES.
I'M
I'M NOT
THE UNITED STATES.
I'M NOT SURPRISED
I'M NOT SURPRISED TO
THE UNITED STATES.
I'M NOT SURPRISED TO HEAR
I'M NOT SURPRISED TO HEAR THAT.
>>
>> AND
I'M NOT SURPRISED TO HEAR THAT.
>> AND SOME
>> AND SOME OF
I'M NOT SURPRISED TO HEAR THAT.
>> AND SOME OF THEM
>> AND SOME OF THEM HAVE
I'M NOT SURPRISED TO HEAR THAT.
>> AND SOME OF THEM HAVE COME
FROM
FROM CHINA.
WHEN
WHEN I
FROM CHINA.
WHEN I BROUGHT
WHEN I BROUGHT THIS
FROM CHINA.
WHEN I BROUGHT THIS OUT
WHEN I BROUGHT THIS OUT THE
FROM CHINA.
WHEN I BROUGHT THIS OUT THE NRC,
NUCLEAR
NUCLEAR REGULATORY
WHEN I BROUGHT THIS OUT THE NRC,
NUCLEAR REGULATORY COMMISSION,
ACCUSED
ACCUSED ME
NUCLEAR REGULATORY COMMISSION,
ACCUSED ME OF
ACCUSED ME OF CONSPIRING
NUCLEAR REGULATORY COMMISSION,
ACCUSED ME OF CONSPIRING TO
TOPPLE
TOPPLE THEIR
ACCUSED ME OF CONSPIRING TO
TOPPLE THEIR AGENCY,
TOPPLE THEIR AGENCY, HAD
ACCUSED ME OF CONSPIRING TO
TOPPLE THEIR AGENCY, HAD ME
TOPPLE THEIR AGENCY, HAD ME IN
FEDERAL
FEDERAL COURT
TOPPLE THEIR AGENCY, HAD ME IN
FEDERAL COURT FOR
FEDERAL COURT FOR SIX
TOPPLE THEIR AGENCY, HAD ME IN
FEDERAL COURT FOR SIX YEARS.
NOW,
NOW, RIGHT
FEDERAL COURT FOR SIX YEARS.
NOW, RIGHT NOW
NOW, RIGHT NOW YOU
FEDERAL COURT FOR SIX YEARS.
NOW, RIGHT NOW YOU COULD
NOW, RIGHT NOW YOU COULD DO
SOMETHING
SOMETHING FOR
NOW, RIGHT NOW YOU COULD DO
SOMETHING FOR THE
SOMETHING FOR THE STATE
NOW, RIGHT NOW YOU COULD DO
SOMETHING FOR THE STATE OF
MASSACHUSETTS
MASSACHUSETTS AND
SOMETHING FOR THE STATE OF
MASSACHUSETTS AND NEW
MASSACHUSETTS AND NEW HAMPSHIRE.
I
I JUST
MASSACHUSETTS AND NEW HAMPSHIRE.
I JUST GOT
I JUST GOT BACK
MASSACHUSETTS AND NEW HAMPSHIRE.
I JUST GOT BACK FROM
CHATTANOOGA,
CHATTANOOGA, TOO.
MARINES
MARINES THERE.
THE
THE SECURITY
MARINES THERE.
THE SECURITY --
MR.
MR. TRUMP:
THE SECURITY --
MR. TRUMP: DID
MR. TRUMP: DID I
THE SECURITY --
MR. TRUMP: DID I DO
MR. TRUMP: DID I DO THE
THE SECURITY --
MR. TRUMP: DID I DO THE RIGHT
THING?
BY
BY THE
THING?
BY THE WAY,
BY THE WAY, HE
THING?
BY THE WAY, HE HAPPENS
BY THE WAY, HE HAPPENS TO
THING?
BY THE WAY, HE HAPPENS TO BE
RIGHT.
YOU
YOU DO
RIGHT.
YOU DO NOT
YOU DO NOT EVEN
RIGHT.
YOU DO NOT EVEN HAVE
YOU DO NOT EVEN HAVE TO
RIGHT.
YOU DO NOT EVEN HAVE TO TELL
YOU DO NOT EVEN HAVE TO TELL ME.
I
I GUARANTEE
YOU DO NOT EVEN HAVE TO TELL ME.
I GUARANTEE YOU
I GUARANTEE YOU THAT
YOU DO NOT EVEN HAVE TO TELL ME.
I GUARANTEE YOU THAT THEY
I GUARANTEE YOU THAT THEY HAVE
SUBSTANDARD
SUBSTANDARD PARTS
I GUARANTEE YOU THAT THEY HAVE
SUBSTANDARD PARTS IN
SUBSTANDARD PARTS IN NUCLEAR
I GUARANTEE YOU THAT THEY HAVE
SUBSTANDARD PARTS IN NUCLEAR AND
AIRPLANES,
AIRPLANES, BECAUSE
SUBSTANDARD PARTS IN NUCLEAR AND
AIRPLANES, BECAUSE THEY
AIRPLANES, BECAUSE THEY GET
SUBSTANDARD PARTS IN NUCLEAR AND
AIRPLANES, BECAUSE THEY GET THEM
FROM
FROM CHINA.
WHAT
WHAT YOU
FROM CHINA.
WHAT YOU GET
WHAT YOU GET FROM
FROM CHINA.
WHAT YOU GET FROM CHINA,
WHAT YOU GET FROM CHINA, YOU
FROM CHINA.
WHAT YOU GET FROM CHINA, YOU DO
NOT
NOT KNOW
WHAT YOU GET FROM CHINA, YOU DO
NOT KNOW WHAT
NOT KNOW WHAT THE
WHAT YOU GET FROM CHINA, YOU DO
NOT KNOW WHAT THE HELL
NOT KNOW WHAT THE HELL YOU
WHAT YOU GET FROM CHINA, YOU DO
NOT KNOW WHAT THE HELL YOU ARE
GETTING.
FINISH
FINISH YOUR
GETTING.
FINISH YOUR QUESTION
FINISH YOUR QUESTION FAST.
THE
THE THE
FINISH YOUR QUESTION FAST.
THE THE SECURITY
THE THE SECURITY --
>>
>> THE
THE THE SECURITY --
>> THE SEABROOK
>> THE SEABROOK NUCLEAR
THE THE SECURITY --
>> THE SEABROOK NUCLEAR PLANT
>> THE SEABROOK NUCLEAR PLANT IS
EMPTY
EMPTY NOW
>> THE SEABROOK NUCLEAR PLANT IS
EMPTY NOW AND
EMPTY NOW AND THE
>> THE SEABROOK NUCLEAR PLANT IS
EMPTY NOW AND THE NRC
EMPTY NOW AND THE NRC SAID
>> THE SEABROOK NUCLEAR PLANT IS
EMPTY NOW AND THE NRC SAID IT
EMPTY NOW AND THE NRC SAID IT IS
NOT
NOT REQUIRED.
OK?
NOW,
NOW, I
OK?
NOW, I GOT
NOW, I GOT INVOLVED
OK?
NOW, I GOT INVOLVED BECAUSE
NOW, I GOT INVOLVED BECAUSE I
OK?
NOW, I GOT INVOLVED BECAUSE I AM
IN
IN THE
NOW, I GOT INVOLVED BECAUSE I AM
IN THE NURSING
IN THE NURSING HOME
NOW, I GOT INVOLVED BECAUSE I AM
IN THE NURSING HOME PROFESSION.
MR.
MR. TRUMP:
IN THE NURSING HOME PROFESSION.
MR. TRUMP: I
MR. TRUMP: I GOT
IN THE NURSING HOME PROFESSION.
MR. TRUMP: I GOT TO
MR. TRUMP: I GOT TO GO.
>>
>> WAIT
MR. TRUMP: I GOT TO GO.
>> WAIT A
>> WAIT A MINUTE.
LET
LET ME
>> WAIT A MINUTE.
LET ME FINISH
LET ME FINISH THIS.
MR.
MR. TRUMP:
LET ME FINISH THIS.
MR. TRUMP: I
MR. TRUMP: I THINK
LET ME FINISH THIS.
MR. TRUMP: I THINK YOUR
MR. TRUMP: I THINK YOUR QUESTION
IS
IS GREAT.
HE
HE IS
IS GREAT.
HE IS TALKING
HE IS TALKING ABOUT
IS GREAT.
HE IS TALKING ABOUT COUNTERFEIT
PARTS,
PARTS, TO
HE IS TALKING ABOUT COUNTERFEIT
PARTS, TO CUT
PARTS, TO CUT TO
HE IS TALKING ABOUT COUNTERFEIT
PARTS, TO CUT TO THE
PARTS, TO CUT TO THE CHASE.
WE
WE DO
PARTS, TO CUT TO THE CHASE.
WE DO NOT
WE DO NOT HAVE
PARTS, TO CUT TO THE CHASE.
WE DO NOT HAVE TO
WE DO NOT HAVE TO KNOW
PARTS, TO CUT TO THE CHASE.
WE DO NOT HAVE TO KNOW WHAT
WE DO NOT HAVE TO KNOW WHAT --
THAT
THAT YOU
WE DO NOT HAVE TO KNOW WHAT --
THAT YOU ARE
THAT YOU ARE IN
WE DO NOT HAVE TO KNOW WHAT --
THAT YOU ARE IN THE
THAT YOU ARE IN THE NURSING
WE DO NOT HAVE TO KNOW WHAT --
THAT YOU ARE IN THE NURSING HOME
BUSINESS.
ARE
ARE YOU
BUSINESS.
ARE YOU TRYING
ARE YOU TRYING TO
BUSINESS.
ARE YOU TRYING TO TALK
ARE YOU TRYING TO TALK TO
BUSINESS.
ARE YOU TRYING TO TALK TO SOME
OF
OF US
ARE YOU TRYING TO TALK TO SOME
OF US ABOUT
OF US ABOUT JOINING
ARE YOU TRYING TO TALK TO SOME
OF US ABOUT JOINING HER
OF US ABOUT JOINING HER HOME?
WE
WE THINK
OF US ABOUT JOINING HER HOME?
WE THINK YOUR
WE THINK YOUR POINT
OF US ABOUT JOINING HER HOME?
WE THINK YOUR POINT IS
WE THINK YOUR POINT IS GOOD.
GIVE
GIVE IT
WE THINK YOUR POINT IS GOOD.
GIVE IT TO
GIVE IT TO HIM.
GOOD.
I'LL
I'LL READ
GOOD.
I'LL READ IT
I'LL READ IT TONIGHT
GOOD.
I'LL READ IT TONIGHT AROUND
I'LL READ IT TONIGHT AROUND 1:00
IN
IN THE
I'LL READ IT TONIGHT AROUND 1:00
IN THE MORNING
IN THE MORNING INSTEAD
I'LL READ IT TONIGHT AROUND 1:00
IN THE MORNING INSTEAD OF
SLEEPING.
IT'S
IT'S GOOD.
GO,
GO, SIT.
COME
COME ON,
GO, SIT.
COME ON, COME
COME ON, COME ON.
LET'S
LET'S GO.
WHAT
WHAT A
LET'S GO.
WHAT A NICE
WHAT A NICE GUY,
LET'S GO.
WHAT A NICE GUY, RIGHT?
HEY,
HEY, HE
WHAT A NICE GUY, RIGHT?
HEY, HE MEANS
HEY, HE MEANS WELL.
HONESTLY,
HONESTLY, HE
HEY, HE MEANS WELL.
HONESTLY, HE MEANS
HONESTLY, HE MEANS WELL.
YOU
YOU DO.
STAND
STAND UP.
YOU
YOU STAND
STAND UP.
YOU STAND UP.
THIS
THIS GUY
YOU STAND UP.
THIS GUY I
THIS GUY I LOVE.
TELL
TELL ME,
THIS GUY I LOVE.
TELL ME, HOW
TELL ME, HOW BAD
THIS GUY I LOVE.
TELL ME, HOW BAD ARE
TELL ME, HOW BAD ARE THE
THIS GUY I LOVE.
TELL ME, HOW BAD ARE THE VETS
BEING
BEING TREATED?
>>
>> YOU
BEING TREATED?
>> YOU UNDERSTAND.
WAY
WAY WORSE
>> YOU UNDERSTAND.
WAY WORSE THAN
WAY WORSE THAN WE
>> YOU UNDERSTAND.
WAY WORSE THAN WE UNDERSTAND.
WITH
WITH 8000
WAY WORSE THAN WE UNDERSTAND.
WITH 8000 VETERANS
WITH 8000 VETERANS A
WAY WORSE THAN WE UNDERSTAND.
WITH 8000 VETERANS A YEAR
WITH 8000 VETERANS A YEAR THAT
CANNOT
CANNOT GET
WITH 8000 VETERANS A YEAR THAT
CANNOT GET ACCESS
CANNOT GET ACCESS TO
WITH 8000 VETERANS A YEAR THAT
CANNOT GET ACCESS TO CARE.
LET
LET ME
CANNOT GET ACCESS TO CARE.
LET ME PUT
LET ME PUT THIS
CANNOT GET ACCESS TO CARE.
LET ME PUT THIS IN
LET ME PUT THIS IN CONTEXT.
8000 VETERANS
8000 VETERANS ARE
LET ME PUT THIS IN CONTEXT.
8000 VETERANS ARE COMMITTING
SUICIDE
SUICIDE BECAUSE
8000 VETERANS ARE COMMITTING
SUICIDE BECAUSE OF
SUICIDE BECAUSE OF THE
INCOMPETENCE
INCOMPETENCE AND
SUICIDE BECAUSE OF THE
INCOMPETENCE AND THE
INCOMPETENCE AND THE CORRUPTION
GOING
GOING ON
INCOMPETENCE AND THE CORRUPTION
GOING ON IN
GOING ON IN THE
INCOMPETENCE AND THE CORRUPTION
GOING ON IN THE V.A.
GOING ON IN THE V.A. SYSTEM.
THOSE
THOSE ARE
GOING ON IN THE V.A. SYSTEM.
THOSE ARE JUST
THOSE ARE JUST THE
GOING ON IN THE V.A. SYSTEM.
THOSE ARE JUST THE ONES
COMMITTING
COMMITTING SUICIDE.
PUT
PUT THIS
COMMITTING SUICIDE.
PUT THIS IN
PUT THIS IN CONTEXT,
COMMITTING SUICIDE.
PUT THIS IN CONTEXT, THAT
PUT THIS IN CONTEXT, THAT IS
COMMITTING SUICIDE.
PUT THIS IN CONTEXT, THAT IS THE
EQUIVALENT
EQUIVALENT OF
PUT THIS IN CONTEXT, THAT IS THE
EQUIVALENT OF A
EQUIVALENT OF A WORLD
PUT THIS IN CONTEXT, THAT IS THE
EQUIVALENT OF A WORLD WAR
EQUIVALENT OF A WORLD WAR II
BATON
BATON DEATH
EQUIVALENT OF A WORLD WAR II
BATON DEATH MARCH
BATON DEATH MARCH EVERY
EQUIVALENT OF A WORLD WAR II
BATON DEATH MARCH EVERY YEAR.
MR.
MR. TRUMP:
BATON DEATH MARCH EVERY YEAR.
MR. TRUMP: THANK
MR. TRUMP: THANK YOU
BATON DEATH MARCH EVERY YEAR.
MR. TRUMP: THANK YOU SO
MR. TRUMP: THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THIS
THIS IS
MR. TRUMP: THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
>>
>> 47,000
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
>> 47,000 VETERANS
>> 47,000 VETERANS --
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
>> 47,000 VETERANS -- FOR
>> 47,000 VETERANS -- FOR ALL
KINDS
KINDS OF
>> 47,000 VETERANS -- FOR ALL
KINDS OF OTHER
KINDS OF OTHER REASONS.
NO
NO ONE
KINDS OF OTHER REASONS.
NO ONE IS
NO ONE IS BEING
KINDS OF OTHER REASONS.
NO ONE IS BEING INDICTED.
NO
NO ONE
NO ONE IS BEING INDICTED.
NO ONE IS
NO ONE IS GOING
NO ONE IS BEING INDICTED.
NO ONE IS GOING TO
NO ONE IS GOING TO JAIL.
THEY
THEY HAVE
NO ONE IS GOING TO JAIL.
THEY HAVE BEEN
THEY HAVE BEEN PROVEN
NO ONE IS GOING TO JAIL.
THEY HAVE BEEN PROVEN TO
THEY HAVE BEEN PROVEN TO COVER
IT
IT UP.
HE
HE JUST
IT UP.
HE JUST LOST
HE JUST LOST HIS
IT UP.
HE JUST LOST HIS JOB
HE JUST LOST HIS JOB RECENTLY.
WHEN
WHEN YOU
HE JUST LOST HIS JOB RECENTLY.
WHEN YOU ARE
WHEN YOU ARE PRESIDENT,
HE JUST LOST HIS JOB RECENTLY.
WHEN YOU ARE PRESIDENT, CAN
WHEN YOU ARE PRESIDENT, CAN I
HAVE
HAVE YOUR
WHEN YOU ARE PRESIDENT, CAN I
HAVE YOUR WORD
HAVE YOUR WORD THAT
WHEN YOU ARE PRESIDENT, CAN I
HAVE YOUR WORD THAT YOU
HAVE YOUR WORD THAT YOU WILL
BRING
BRING IN
HAVE YOUR WORD THAT YOU WILL
BRING IN THE
BRING IN THE FBI
HAVE YOUR WORD THAT YOU WILL
BRING IN THE FBI AND
BRING IN THE FBI AND START
INVESTIGATING
INVESTIGATING THIS
BRING IN THE FBI AND START
INVESTIGATING THIS V.A.?
[APPLAUSE]
MR.
MR. TRUMP:
[APPLAUSE]
MR. TRUMP: IT
MR. TRUMP: IT CAN'T
[APPLAUSE]
MR. TRUMP: IT CAN'T BE.
GREAT
GREAT QUESTION.
IT
IT CANNOT
GREAT QUESTION.
IT CANNOT BE
IT CANNOT BE JUST
GREAT QUESTION.
IT CANNOT BE JUST INCOMPETENCE.
BECAUSE
BECAUSE IT
IT CANNOT BE JUST INCOMPETENCE.
BECAUSE IT IS
BECAUSE IT IS SO
IT CANNOT BE JUST INCOMPETENCE.
BECAUSE IT IS SO BAD
BECAUSE IT IS SO BAD WHAT
IT CANNOT BE JUST INCOMPETENCE.
BECAUSE IT IS SO BAD WHAT IS
HAPPENING
HAPPENING TO
BECAUSE IT IS SO BAD WHAT IS
HAPPENING TO THE
HAPPENING TO THE VETS
BECAUSE IT IS SO BAD WHAT IS
HAPPENING TO THE VETS AND
HAPPENING TO THE VETS AND THE
V.A.
IT
IT IS
V.A.
IT IS SO
IT IS SO BAD
V.A.
IT IS SO BAD THAT
IT IS SO BAD THAT IT
V.A.
IT IS SO BAD THAT IT CANNOT
IT IS SO BAD THAT IT CANNOT BE
JUST
JUST INCOMPETENCE.
IT
IT IS
JUST INCOMPETENCE.
IT IS GOT
IT IS GOT TO
JUST INCOMPETENCE.
IT IS GOT TO BE
IT IS GOT TO BE THEFT
JUST INCOMPETENCE.
IT IS GOT TO BE THEFT AND
IT IS GOT TO BE THEFT AND A
JUST INCOMPETENCE.
IT IS GOT TO BE THEFT AND A LOT
MORE
MORE THAN
IT IS GOT TO BE THEFT AND A LOT
MORE THAN WHAT
MORE THAN WHAT WE
IT IS GOT TO BE THEFT AND A LOT
MORE THAN WHAT WE ARE
MORE THAN WHAT WE ARE HEARING
ABOUT.
SO
SO I
ABOUT.
SO I WOULD
SO I WOULD DO
ABOUT.
SO I WOULD DO THAT.
THANK
THANK YOU.
[APPLAUSE]
GO
GO AHEAD.
COME
COME ON.
>>
>> I
COME ON.
>> I HAVE
>> I HAVE TO
COME ON.
>> I HAVE TO FIGHT
>> I HAVE TO FIGHT FOR
COME ON.
>> I HAVE TO FIGHT FOR THIS
BECAUSE
BECAUSE MY
>> I HAVE TO FIGHT FOR THIS
BECAUSE MY SON
BECAUSE MY SON IS
>> I HAVE TO FIGHT FOR THIS
BECAUSE MY SON IS AN
BECAUSE MY SON IS AN ACTIVE
>> I HAVE TO FIGHT FOR THIS
BECAUSE MY SON IS AN ACTIVE DUTY
GUNNY
GUNNY SERGEANT
BECAUSE MY SON IS AN ACTIVE DUTY
GUNNY SERGEANT IN
GUNNY SERGEANT IN THE
BECAUSE MY SON IS AN ACTIVE DUTY
GUNNY SERGEANT IN THE MARINE
CORPS.
I
I WILL
CORPS.
I WILL NOT
I WILL NOT LET
CORPS.
I WILL NOT LET HIM
I WILL NOT LET HIM WALK
CORPS.
I WILL NOT LET HIM WALK INTO
THIS
THIS NIGHTMARE
I WILL NOT LET HIM WALK INTO
THIS NIGHTMARE LIKE
THIS NIGHTMARE LIKE I
I WILL NOT LET HIM WALK INTO
THIS NIGHTMARE LIKE I DID.
MR.
MR. TRUMP:
THIS NIGHTMARE LIKE I DID.
MR. TRUMP: OK.
I
I LOVE
MR. TRUMP: OK.
I LOVE IT.
THANK
THANK YOU.
[APPLAUSE]
GO
GO AHEAD.
LET'S
LET'S TAKE.
WHO
WHO WANTS
LET'S TAKE.
WHO WANTS TO
WHO WANTS TO LEAVE?
DOES
DOES ANYBODY
WHO WANTS TO LEAVE?
DOES ANYBODY WANT
DOES ANYBODY WANT TO
WHO WANTS TO LEAVE?
DOES ANYBODY WANT TO WAIT?
>>
>> NO!
MR.
MR. TRUMP:
>> NO!
MR. TRUMP: I
MR. TRUMP: I HAVE
>> NO!
MR. TRUMP: I HAVE ALL
MR. TRUMP: I HAVE ALL NIGHT.
>>
>> DO
MR. TRUMP: I HAVE ALL NIGHT.
>> DO YOU
>> DO YOU THINK
MR. TRUMP: I HAVE ALL NIGHT.
>> DO YOU THINK YOU
>> DO YOU THINK YOU CAN
MR. TRUMP: I HAVE ALL NIGHT.
>> DO YOU THINK YOU CAN FIRE
SOME
SOME OF
>> DO YOU THINK YOU CAN FIRE
SOME OF THESE
SOME OF THESE FEDERAL
>> DO YOU THINK YOU CAN FIRE
SOME OF THESE FEDERAL EMPLOYEES
AT
AT THE
SOME OF THESE FEDERAL EMPLOYEES
AT THE V.A.?
MR.
MR. TRUMP:
AT THE V.A.?
MR. TRUMP: HOW
MR. TRUMP: HOW ABOUT
AT THE V.A.?
MR. TRUMP: HOW ABOUT THE
MR. TRUMP: HOW ABOUT THE EPA?
HOW
HOW ABOUT
MR. TRUMP: HOW ABOUT THE EPA?
HOW ABOUT OUR
HOW ABOUT OUR COMMON
MR. TRUMP: HOW ABOUT THE EPA?
HOW ABOUT OUR COMMON CORE
HOW ABOUT OUR COMMON CORE FOLKS
IN
IN WASHINGTON?
HOW
HOW ABOUT
IN WASHINGTON?
HOW ABOUT COMMON
HOW ABOUT COMMON CORE
IN WASHINGTON?
HOW ABOUT COMMON CORE IN
WASHINGTON?
RIGHT.
GOOD
GOOD QUESTION.
YES,
YES, SIR.
YOUNG
YOUNG GUY
YES, SIR.
YOUNG GUY HERE.
>>
>> I'M
YOUNG GUY HERE.
>> I'M A
>> I'M A NASA
YOUNG GUY HERE.
>> I'M A NASA SPACE
>> I'M A NASA SPACE TECHNOLOGY
RESEARCH
RESEARCH FELLOW
>> I'M A NASA SPACE TECHNOLOGY
RESEARCH FELLOW AT
RESEARCH FELLOW AT THE
MASSACHUSETTS
MASSACHUSETTS INSTITUTE
RESEARCH FELLOW AT THE
MASSACHUSETTS INSTITUTE OF
TECHNOLOGY.
MR.
MR. TRUMP:
TECHNOLOGY.
MR. TRUMP: MY
MR. TRUMP: MY UNCLE
TECHNOLOGY.
MR. TRUMP: MY UNCLE WAS
MR. TRUMP: MY UNCLE WAS A
PROFESSOR
PROFESSOR AT
MR. TRUMP: MY UNCLE WAS A
PROFESSOR AT MIT.
>>
>> AND
PROFESSOR AT MIT.
>> AND HARVARD
>> AND HARVARD MEDICAL
PROFESSOR AT MIT.
>> AND HARVARD MEDICAL SCHOOL.
AND
AND I
>> AND HARVARD MEDICAL SCHOOL.
AND I AM
AND I AM A
>> AND HARVARD MEDICAL SCHOOL.
AND I AM A GRADUATE
AND I AM A GRADUATE OF
WINNACUNNET
WINNACUNNET --
MR.
MR. TRUMP:
WINNACUNNET --
MR. TRUMP: HE
MR. TRUMP: HE IS
WINNACUNNET --
MR. TRUMP: HE IS A
MR. TRUMP: HE IS A SMART
WINNACUNNET --
MR. TRUMP: HE IS A SMART GUY.
GO
GO AHEAD.
>>
>> WHEN
GO AHEAD.
>> WHEN YOU
>> WHEN YOU ANNOUNCED
GO AHEAD.
>> WHEN YOU ANNOUNCED YOU
>> WHEN YOU ANNOUNCED YOU WERE
GOING
GOING TO
>> WHEN YOU ANNOUNCED YOU WERE
GOING TO RUN
GOING TO RUN FOR
>> WHEN YOU ANNOUNCED YOU WERE
GOING TO RUN FOR PRESIDENT
GOING TO RUN FOR PRESIDENT YOU
SAID
SAID THAT
GOING TO RUN FOR PRESIDENT YOU
SAID THAT AMERICA
SAID THAT AMERICA NEEDS
VICTORIES
VICTORIES AGAIN.
MR.
MR. TRUMP:
VICTORIES AGAIN.
MR. TRUMP: WE
MR. TRUMP: WE HAVE
VICTORIES AGAIN.
MR. TRUMP: WE HAVE NO
MR. TRUMP: WE HAVE NO VICTORIES.
WHEN
WHEN DID
MR. TRUMP: WE HAVE NO VICTORIES.
WHEN DID WE
WHEN DID WE BEAT
MR. TRUMP: WE HAVE NO VICTORIES.
WHEN DID WE BEAT SOMEBODY
WHEN DID WE BEAT SOMEBODY IN
TRADE?
WE
WE DO
TRADE?
WE DO NOT
WE DO NOT BEAT
TRADE?
WE DO NOT BEAT ANYBODY.
>>
>> IN
WE DO NOT BEAT ANYBODY.
>> IN MY
>> IN MY INDUSTRY
WE DO NOT BEAT ANYBODY.
>> IN MY INDUSTRY --
MR.
MR. TRUMP:
>> IN MY INDUSTRY --
MR. TRUMP: WE
MR. TRUMP: WE ARE
>> IN MY INDUSTRY --
MR. TRUMP: WE ARE GOING
MR. TRUMP: WE ARE GOING TO
>> IN MY INDUSTRY --
MR. TRUMP: WE ARE GOING TO HAVE
SO
SO MANY
MR. TRUMP: WE ARE GOING TO HAVE
SO MANY VICTORIES
SO MANY VICTORIES --
YOU
YOU WATCH.
GO
GO AHEAD.
>>
>> IN
GO AHEAD.
>> IN MY
>> IN MY INDUSTRY,
GO AHEAD.
>> IN MY INDUSTRY, ONE
>> IN MY INDUSTRY, ONE OF
GO AHEAD.
>> IN MY INDUSTRY, ONE OF MY
BIGGEST
BIGGEST VICTORIES
>> IN MY INDUSTRY, ONE OF MY
BIGGEST VICTORIES WAS
BIGGEST VICTORIES WAS PUTTING
>> IN MY INDUSTRY, ONE OF MY
BIGGEST VICTORIES WAS PUTTING A
MAN
MAN ON
BIGGEST VICTORIES WAS PUTTING A
MAN ON THE
MAN ON THE MOON.
WHAT
WHAT DO
MAN ON THE MOON.
WHAT DO YOU
WHAT DO YOU THINK
MAN ON THE MOON.
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT PUTTING
HUMANS
HUMANS ON
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT PUTTING
HUMANS ON MARS?
MR.
MR. TRUMP:
HUMANS ON MARS?
MR. TRUMP: HONESTLY,
MR. TRUMP: HONESTLY, I
HUMANS ON MARS?
MR. TRUMP: HONESTLY, I THINK
MR. TRUMP: HONESTLY, I THINK IT
IS
IS WONDERFUL.
I
I WANT
IS WONDERFUL.
I WANT TO
I WANT TO INBUILT
IS WONDERFUL.
I WANT TO INBUILT --
I WANT TO INBUILT -- REBUILD
IS WONDERFUL.
I WANT TO INBUILT -- REBUILD OUR
INFRASTRUCTURE
INFRASTRUCTURE FIRST.
I
I THINK
INFRASTRUCTURE FIRST.
I THINK IT
I THINK IT IS
INFRASTRUCTURE FIRST.
I THINK IT IS WONDERFUL.
GO
GO AHEAD.
YEAH?
GO
GO AHEAD.
WAIT
WAIT FOR
GO AHEAD.
WAIT FOR THAT
WAIT FOR THAT MIC.
GO
GO AHEAD.
JUST
JUST SHOUT.
>>
>> I
JUST SHOUT.
>> I HAVE
>> I HAVE BEEN
JUST SHOUT.
>> I HAVE BEEN A
>> I HAVE BEEN A CAREGIVER
JUST SHOUT.
>> I HAVE BEEN A CAREGIVER FOR
10 YEARS.
MY
MY MOTHER
10 YEARS.
MY MOTHER HAS
MY MOTHER HAS ALZHEIMER'S
DISEASE.
MY
MY HUSBAND
DISEASE.
MY HUSBAND HAS
MY HUSBAND HAS ALZHEIMER'S
DISEASE.
IT
IT RECEIVES
DISEASE.
IT RECEIVES $600
IT RECEIVES $600 MILLION
DISEASE.
IT RECEIVES $600 MILLION FROM
NIH,
NIH, WHILE
IT RECEIVES $600 MILLION FROM
NIH, WHILE WE
NIH, WHILE WE ARE
IT RECEIVES $600 MILLION FROM
NIH, WHILE WE ARE SPENDING
NIH, WHILE WE ARE SPENDING $153
BILLION
BILLION IN
NIH, WHILE WE ARE SPENDING $153
BILLION IN MEDICARE
BILLION IN MEDICARE AND
MEDICAID.
WHAT
WHAT WILL
MEDICAID.
WHAT WILL YOU
WHAT WILL YOU DO
MEDICAID.
WHAT WILL YOU DO TO
WHAT WILL YOU DO TO ENSURE
MEDICAID.
WHAT WILL YOU DO TO ENSURE THAT
THIS
THIS DEVASTATING
WHAT WILL YOU DO TO ENSURE THAT
THIS DEVASTATING DISEASE
THIS DEVASTATING DISEASE IS
WHAT WILL YOU DO TO ENSURE THAT
THIS DEVASTATING DISEASE IS A
TOP
TOP PRIORITY?
MR.
MR. TRUMP:
TOP PRIORITY?
MR. TRUMP: I
MR. TRUMP: I HAVE
TOP PRIORITY?
MR. TRUMP: I HAVE SO
MR. TRUMP: I HAVE SO MANY
FRIENDS
FRIENDS WHOSE
MR. TRUMP: I HAVE SO MANY
FRIENDS WHOSE FAMILY
FRIENDS WHOSE FAMILY IS
DEVASTATED
DEVASTATED BY
FRIENDS WHOSE FAMILY IS
DEVASTATED BY ALZHEIMER'S.
WE
WE CAN
DEVASTATED BY ALZHEIMER'S.
WE CAN GET
WE CAN GET AN
DEVASTATED BY ALZHEIMER'S.
WE CAN GET AN ANSWER.
THERE
THERE ARE
WE CAN GET AN ANSWER.
THERE ARE SOME
THERE ARE SOME ANSWERS.
WE'VE
WE'VE MADE
THERE ARE SOME ANSWERS.
WE'VE MADE LES
WE'VE MADE LES PROJECTS
THERE ARE SOME ANSWERS.
WE'VE MADE LES PROJECTS --
WE'VE MADE LES PROJECTS -- LESS
PROGRESS
PROGRESS THE
WE'VE MADE LES PROJECTS -- LESS
PROGRESS THE WITH
PROGRESS THE WITH HOPE.
YES,
YES, MA'AM.
YES?
[INDISCERNIBLE]
I
I WONDERED
[INDISCERNIBLE]
I WONDERED YOU
I WONDERED YOU MIGHT
[INDISCERNIBLE]
I WONDERED YOU MIGHT SPEAK
I WONDERED YOU MIGHT SPEAK FROM
THE
THE HEART
I WONDERED YOU MIGHT SPEAK FROM
THE HEART AND
THE HEART AND TELL
I WONDERED YOU MIGHT SPEAK FROM
THE HEART AND TELL US
THE HEART AND TELL US WHAT
I WONDERED YOU MIGHT SPEAK FROM
THE HEART AND TELL US WHAT IS
ENDEARING
ENDEARING NEW
THE HEART AND TELL US WHAT IS
ENDEARING NEW HAMPSHIRE
ENDEARING NEW HAMPSHIRE TO
THE HEART AND TELL US WHAT IS
ENDEARING NEW HAMPSHIRE TO YOU?
MR.
MR. TRUMP:
ENDEARING NEW HAMPSHIRE TO YOU?
MR. TRUMP: THE
MR. TRUMP: THE PEOPLE.
HONESTLY,
HONESTLY, I
MR. TRUMP: THE PEOPLE.
HONESTLY, I HAVE
HONESTLY, I HAVE HAD
MR. TRUMP: THE PEOPLE.
HONESTLY, I HAVE HAD SUCH
HONESTLY, I HAVE HAD SUCH A
GREAT
GREAT RESPONSE.
SOMEBODY,
SOMEBODY, ONE
GREAT RESPONSE.
SOMEBODY, ONE OF
SOMEBODY, ONE OF MY
GREAT RESPONSE.
SOMEBODY, ONE OF MY FRIENDS,
THANK
THANK YOU.
ONE
ONE OF
THANK YOU.
ONE OF MY
ONE OF MY FRIENDS
THANK YOU.
ONE OF MY FRIENDS WAS
ONE OF MY FRIENDS WAS ASKING
THANK YOU.
ONE OF MY FRIENDS WAS ASKING ME
WHAT
WHAT WAS
ONE OF MY FRIENDS WAS ASKING ME
WHAT WAS IT
WHAT WAS IT LIKE?
I
I HAVE
WHAT WAS IT LIKE?
I HAVE BEEN
I HAVE BEEN HERE
WHAT WAS IT LIKE?
I HAVE BEEN HERE A
I HAVE BEEN HERE A LOT.
WE
WE HAVE
I HAVE BEEN HERE A LOT.
WE HAVE DONE
WE HAVE DONE SO
I HAVE BEEN HERE A LOT.
WE HAVE DONE SO MANY
WE HAVE DONE SO MANY TOWN
I HAVE BEEN HERE A LOT.
WE HAVE DONE SO MANY TOWN HALLS
AND
AND SO
WE HAVE DONE SO MANY TOWN HALLS
AND SO DIFFERENT
AND SO DIFFERENT MEETINGS.
WE
WE ARE
AND SO DIFFERENT MEETINGS.
WE ARE HAVING
WE ARE HAVING SO
AND SO DIFFERENT MEETINGS.
WE ARE HAVING SO MANY
WE ARE HAVING SO MANY PEOPLE
AND SO DIFFERENT MEETINGS.
WE ARE HAVING SO MANY PEOPLE WE
NEED
NEED --
WE ARE HAVING SO MANY PEOPLE WE
NEED -- WHICH
NEED -- WHICH WORKED
WE ARE HAVING SO MANY PEOPLE WE
NEED -- WHICH WORKED OUT
NEED -- WHICH WORKED OUT WELL.
I
I AM
NEED -- WHICH WORKED OUT WELL.
I AM GOING
I AM GOING TO
NEED -- WHICH WORKED OUT WELL.
I AM GOING TO GO
I AM GOING TO GO SEE
NEED -- WHICH WORKED OUT WELL.
I AM GOING TO GO SEE THE
I AM GOING TO GO SEE THE OTHER
AUDITORY
AUDITORY WHERE
I AM GOING TO GO SEE THE OTHER
AUDITORY WHERE THEY
AUDITORY WHERE THEY DID
I AM GOING TO GO SEE THE OTHER
AUDITORY WHERE THEY DID NOT
AUDITORY WHERE THEY DID NOT HAVE
THE
THE GREAT
AUDITORY WHERE THEY DID NOT HAVE
THE GREAT REAL
THE GREAT REAL ESTATE.
I'M
I'M GOING
THE GREAT REAL ESTATE.
I'M GOING TO
I'M GOING TO SEE
THE GREAT REAL ESTATE.
I'M GOING TO SEE THE
I'M GOING TO SEE THE PEOPLE
OUTSIDE
OUTSIDE THAT
I'M GOING TO SEE THE PEOPLE
OUTSIDE THAT ARE
OUTSIDE THAT ARE WAITING
I'M GOING TO SEE THE PEOPLE
OUTSIDE THAT ARE WAITING TO
OUTSIDE THAT ARE WAITING TO SEE
US.
[APPLAUSE]
BUT
BUT THE
[APPLAUSE]
BUT THE PEOPLE
BUT THE PEOPLE OF
[APPLAUSE]
BUT THE PEOPLE OF NEW
BUT THE PEOPLE OF NEW HAMPSHIRE
ARE
ARE AMAZING.
THEY'RE
THEY'RE LIKE
ARE AMAZING.
THEY'RE LIKE THE
THEY'RE LIKE THE PEOPLE
ARE AMAZING.
THEY'RE LIKE THE PEOPLE THAT
BUILT
BUILT THIS
THEY'RE LIKE THE PEOPLE THAT
BUILT THIS COUNTRY.
THEY
THEY WORK
BUILT THIS COUNTRY.
THEY WORK HARD.
THEY
THEY ARE
THEY WORK HARD.
THEY ARE SMART,
THEY ARE SMART, INDUSTRIOUS,
THEY WORK HARD.
THEY ARE SMART, INDUSTRIOUS, AND
THEY
THEY LOVE
THEY ARE SMART, INDUSTRIOUS, AND
THEY LOVE THIS
THEY LOVE THIS COUNTRY.
THEY
THEY WANT
THEY LOVE THIS COUNTRY.
THEY WANT TO
THEY WANT TO SEE
THEY LOVE THIS COUNTRY.
THEY WANT TO SEE IT
THEY WANT TO SEE IT HAPPEN.
THEY
THEY ARE
THEY WANT TO SEE IT HAPPEN.
THEY ARE GREAT
THEY ARE GREAT PEOPLE.
I
I WAS
THEY ARE GREAT PEOPLE.
I WAS SO
I WAS SO HONORED,
THEY ARE GREAT PEOPLE.
I WAS SO HONORED, BECAUSE
RECENTLY
RECENTLY EVERYBODY
I WAS SO HONORED, BECAUSE
RECENTLY EVERYBODY SAID
RECENTLY EVERYBODY SAID THAT
I WAS SO HONORED, BECAUSE
RECENTLY EVERYBODY SAID THAT A
WALKER
WALKER WOULD
RECENTLY EVERYBODY SAID THAT A
WALKER WOULD WIN
WALKER WOULD WIN IOWA.
AND
AND BUSH,
WALKER WOULD WIN IOWA.
AND BUSH, WHO'S
AND BUSH, WHO'S FALLING
WALKER WOULD WIN IOWA.
AND BUSH, WHO'S FALLING LIKE
AND BUSH, WHO'S FALLING LIKE A
STONE,
STONE, BECAUSE
AND BUSH, WHO'S FALLING LIKE A
STONE, BECAUSE HE'S
STONE, BECAUSE HE'S --
TELL
TELL ME
STONE, BECAUSE HE'S --
TELL ME IS
TELL ME IS THAT
STONE, BECAUSE HE'S --
TELL ME IS THAT REALLY
TELL ME IS THAT REALLY SO
STONE, BECAUSE HE'S --
TELL ME IS THAT REALLY SO --
THAT
THAT IS
TELL ME IS THAT REALLY SO --
THAT IS FROM
THAT IS FROM A
TELL ME IS THAT REALLY SO --
THAT IS FROM A DIFFERENT
THAT IS FROM A DIFFERENT PLANET,
RIGHT?
I
I DO
RIGHT?
I DO NOT
I DO NOT GET
RIGHT?
I DO NOT GET IT.
BUT
BUT THEY
I DO NOT GET IT.
BUT THEY SAID
BUT THEY SAID BUSH
I DO NOT GET IT.
BUT THEY SAID BUSH HE'S
BUT THEY SAID BUSH HE'S BEING
DOWN
DOWN BIG.
AND
AND WALKER,
DOWN BIG.
AND WALKER, YOU
AND WALKER, YOU HAVE
DOWN BIG.
AND WALKER, YOU HAVE TO
AND WALKER, YOU HAVE TO REMEMBER
WALKER
WALKER GREW
AND WALKER, YOU HAVE TO REMEMBER
WALKER GREW UP
WALKER GREW UP A
AND WALKER, YOU HAVE TO REMEMBER
WALKER GREW UP A LITTLE
WALKER GREW UP A LITTLE IN
AND WALKER, YOU HAVE TO REMEMBER
WALKER GREW UP A LITTLE IN IOWA.
BECAME
BECAME THE
WALKER GREW UP A LITTLE IN IOWA.
BECAME THE GOVERNOR
BECAME THE GOVERNOR OF
WALKER GREW UP A LITTLE IN IOWA.
BECAME THE GOVERNOR OF THE
ADJOINING
ADJOINING STATE.
THEY
THEY HAVE
ADJOINING STATE.
THEY HAVE MASSIVE
THEY HAVE MASSIVE DEFICITS.
THEY
THEY HAVE
THEY HAVE MASSIVE DEFICITS.
THEY HAVE VERY
THEY HAVE VERY POOR
THEY HAVE MASSIVE DEFICITS.
THEY HAVE VERY POOR EMPLOYMENT,
NEW
NEW JOBS.
THEY
THEY HAVE
NEW JOBS.
THEY HAVE A
THEY HAVE A LOT
NEW JOBS.
THEY HAVE A LOT OF
THEY HAVE A LOT OF DISSENSION.
A
A LOT
THEY HAVE A LOT OF DISSENSION.
A LOT OF
A LOT OF PROBLEMS
THEY HAVE A LOT OF DISSENSION.
A LOT OF PROBLEMS IN
A LOT OF PROBLEMS IN WISCONSIN
WHICH
WHICH IS
A LOT OF PROBLEMS IN WISCONSIN
WHICH IS A
WHICH IS A STATE
A LOT OF PROBLEMS IN WISCONSIN
WHICH IS A STATE I
WHICH IS A STATE I LOVE.
BUT
BUT THEY
WHICH IS A STATE I LOVE.
BUT THEY HAVE
BUT THEY HAVE A
WHICH IS A STATE I LOVE.
BUT THEY HAVE A LOT
BUT THEY HAVE A LOT OF
WHICH IS A STATE I LOVE.
BUT THEY HAVE A LOT OF PROMISE
WITH
WITH HER
BUT THEY HAVE A LOT OF PROMISE
WITH HER EDUCATION.
AND
AND WITH
WITH HER EDUCATION.
AND WITH THEIR
AND WITH THEIR DEBT.
THEY
THEY ARE
AND WITH THEIR DEBT.
THEY ARE PUTTING
THEY ARE PUTTING UP
AND WITH THEIR DEBT.
THEY ARE PUTTING UP TREMENDOUS
DEBT.
I
I WAS
DEBT.
I WAS VERY
I WAS VERY NICE
DEBT.
I WAS VERY NICE TO
I WAS VERY NICE TO WALKER.
I
I GAVE
I WAS VERY NICE TO WALKER.
I GAVE HIM
I GAVE HIM MONEY
I WAS VERY NICE TO WALKER.
I GAVE HIM MONEY FOR
I GAVE HIM MONEY FOR HIS
CAMPAIGN.
I
I GET
CAMPAIGN.
I GET TO
I GET TO ANYBODY.
I
I GIVE
I GET TO ANYBODY.
I GIVE A
I GIVE A LOT
I GET TO ANYBODY.
I GIVE A LOT OF
I GIVE A LOT OF MONEY.
HE
HE CAME
I GIVE A LOT OF MONEY.
HE CAME UP
HE CAME UP TO
I GIVE A LOT OF MONEY.
HE CAME UP TO SEE
HE CAME UP TO SEE ME
I GIVE A LOT OF MONEY.
HE CAME UP TO SEE ME SIX
HE CAME UP TO SEE ME SIX MONTH
AGO.
HE
HE GAVE
AGO.
HE GAVE ME
HE GAVE ME A
AGO.
HE GAVE ME A PLAQUE.
YOU
YOU NEED
HE GAVE ME A PLAQUE.
YOU NEED SOME
YOU NEED SOME MONEY?
[LAUGHTER]
BUT
BUT HE
[LAUGHTER]
BUT HE GAVE
BUT HE GAVE ME
[LAUGHTER]
BUT HE GAVE ME A
BUT HE GAVE ME A PLAQUE.
IT
IT WAS
BUT HE GAVE ME A PLAQUE.
IT WAS VERY
IT WAS VERY NICE.
AND
AND THEN
IT WAS VERY NICE.
AND THEN I
AND THEN I WAS
IT WAS VERY NICE.
AND THEN I WAS VERY
AND THEN I WAS VERY NICE
IT WAS VERY NICE.
AND THEN I WAS VERY NICE TO
AND THEN I WAS VERY NICE TO HIM.
I
I CANNOT
AND THEN I WAS VERY NICE TO HIM.
I CANNOT BE
I CANNOT BE MEAN
AND THEN I WAS VERY NICE TO HIM.
I CANNOT BE MEAN TO
I CANNOT BE MEAN TO SOMEONE
AND THEN I WAS VERY NICE TO HIM.
I CANNOT BE MEAN TO SOMEONE --
THERE
THERE ARE
I CANNOT BE MEAN TO SOMEONE --
THERE ARE COUPLE
THERE ARE COUPLE OF
I CANNOT BE MEAN TO SOMEONE --
THERE ARE COUPLE OF GUYS
THERE ARE COUPLE OF GUYS RUNNING
THAT
THAT HAVE
THERE ARE COUPLE OF GUYS RUNNING
THAT HAVE BEEN
THAT HAVE BEEN SO
THERE ARE COUPLE OF GUYS RUNNING
THAT HAVE BEEN SO NICE
THAT HAVE BEEN SO NICE TO
THERE ARE COUPLE OF GUYS RUNNING
THAT HAVE BEEN SO NICE TO ME.
I
I WANT
THAT HAVE BEEN SO NICE TO ME.
I WANT TO.
ONE
ONE OF
I WANT TO.
ONE OF HIS
ONE OF HIS UNDERLINGS
I WANT TO.
ONE OF HIS UNDERLINGS SAID
SOMETHING
SOMETHING NASTY
ONE OF HIS UNDERLINGS SAID
SOMETHING NASTY ABOUT
SOMETHING NASTY ABOUT ME.
I
I SAID,
SOMETHING NASTY ABOUT ME.
I SAID, FINALLY
I SAID, FINALLY I
SOMETHING NASTY ABOUT ME.
I SAID, FINALLY I CAN
I SAID, FINALLY I CAN TALK
SOMETHING NASTY ABOUT ME.
I SAID, FINALLY I CAN TALK ABOUT
WISCONSIN.
IT
IT WAS
WISCONSIN.
IT WAS SO
IT WAS SO GOOD.
HE
HE PLUNGED
IT WAS SO GOOD.
HE PLUNGED IN
HE PLUNGED IN IOWA.
AND
AND I
HE PLUNGED IN IOWA.
AND I AM
AND I AM LEADING
HE PLUNGED IN IOWA.
AND I AM LEADING IOWA
AND I AM LEADING IOWA BIG.
WE
WE ARE
AND I AM LEADING IOWA BIG.
WE ARE LEADING
WE ARE LEADING NEW
AND I AM LEADING IOWA BIG.
WE ARE LEADING NEW HAMPSHIRE
BIG.
YOU
YOU KNOW,
BIG.
YOU KNOW, WE
YOU KNOW, WE ARE
BIG.
YOU KNOW, WE ARE LEADING
YOU KNOW, WE ARE LEADING NEVADA
BIG.
WHAT
WHAT I
BIG.
WHAT I LOVED
WHAT I LOVED ABOUT
BIG.
WHAT I LOVED ABOUT NEVADA.
THEY
THEY DID
WHAT I LOVED ABOUT NEVADA.
THEY DID A
THEY DID A SECOND
WHAT I LOVED ABOUT NEVADA.
THEY DID A SECOND PART
THEY DID A SECOND PART AT
WHAT I LOVED ABOUT NEVADA.
THEY DID A SECOND PART AT THE
POLL.
IT
IT CAME
POLL.
IT CAME OUT
IT CAME OUT LAST
POLL.
IT CAME OUT LAST WEEK.
EVERYBODY
EVERYBODY WAS
IT CAME OUT LAST WEEK.
EVERYBODY WAS IN
EVERYBODY WAS IN SHOCK.
I
I WAS
EVERYBODY WAS IN SHOCK.
I WAS NOT
I WAS NOT BECAUSE
EVERYBODY WAS IN SHOCK.
I WAS NOT BECAUSE I
I WAS NOT BECAUSE I WILL
EVERYBODY WAS IN SHOCK.
I WAS NOT BECAUSE I WILL BRING
JOBS
JOBS BACK
I WAS NOT BECAUSE I WILL BRING
JOBS BACK INTO
JOBS BACK INTO THIS
I WAS NOT BECAUSE I WILL BRING
JOBS BACK INTO THIS COUNTRY.
I
I WAS
JOBS BACK INTO THIS COUNTRY.
I WAS LEADING
I WAS LEADING ALL
JOBS BACK INTO THIS COUNTRY.
I WAS LEADING ALL CANDIDATES
I WAS LEADING ALL CANDIDATES IN
THE
THE HISPANIC
I WAS LEADING ALL CANDIDATES IN
THE HISPANIC VOTE.
EVERYBODY
EVERYBODY WAS
THE HISPANIC VOTE.
EVERYBODY WAS SURPRISED.
WHY?
I
I EMPLOY
WHY?
I EMPLOY THOUSANDS
I EMPLOY THOUSANDS AND
WHY?
I EMPLOY THOUSANDS AND THOUSANDS
OF
OF HISPANICS.
THEY
THEY ARE
OF HISPANICS.
THEY ARE AMAZING
THEY ARE AMAZING PEOPLE
OF HISPANICS.
THEY ARE AMAZING PEOPLE BUT
PEOPLE
PEOPLE WERE
THEY ARE AMAZING PEOPLE BUT
PEOPLE WERE SURPRISED
PEOPLE WERE SURPRISED TO
THEY ARE AMAZING PEOPLE BUT
PEOPLE WERE SURPRISED TO SEE
THAT.
NORTH
NORTH CAROLINA
THAT.
NORTH CAROLINA WE
NORTH CAROLINA WE ARE
THAT.
NORTH CAROLINA WE ARE LEADING
NORTH CAROLINA WE ARE LEADING BY
MASSIVE
MASSIVE NUMBERS.
SOUTH
SOUTH CAROLINA.
WE
WE ARE
SOUTH CAROLINA.
WE ARE LEADING
WE ARE LEADING EVERYWHERE.
A
A POLL
WE ARE LEADING EVERYWHERE.
A POLL CAME
A POLL CAME OUT
WE ARE LEADING EVERYWHERE.
A POLL CAME OUT 32%
A POLL CAME OUT 32% NATIONWIDE.
ANOTHER
ANOTHER ONE
A POLL CAME OUT 32% NATIONWIDE.
ANOTHER ONE 24%,
ANOTHER ONE 24%, FOX.
PEOPLE
PEOPLE ARE
ANOTHER ONE 24%, FOX.
PEOPLE ARE TIRED
PEOPLE ARE TIRED OF
ANOTHER ONE 24%, FOX.
PEOPLE ARE TIRED OF WHAT
PEOPLE ARE TIRED OF WHAT IS
HAPPENING
HAPPENING TO
PEOPLE ARE TIRED OF WHAT IS
HAPPENING TO OUR
HAPPENING TO OUR COUNTRY.
THEY
THEY ARE
HAPPENING TO OUR COUNTRY.
THEY ARE TIRED
THEY ARE TIRED OF
HAPPENING TO OUR COUNTRY.
THEY ARE TIRED OF BEING
THEY ARE TIRED OF BEING RIPPED
OFF
OFF BY
THEY ARE TIRED OF BEING RIPPED
OFF BY EVERYBODY
OFF BY EVERYBODY IN
THEY ARE TIRED OF BEING RIPPED
OFF BY EVERYBODY IN THE
OFF BY EVERYBODY IN THE WORLD.
THEY
THEY ARE
OFF BY EVERYBODY IN THE WORLD.
THEY ARE TIRED
THEY ARE TIRED OF
OFF BY EVERYBODY IN THE WORLD.
THEY ARE TIRED OF IT.
YOU
YOU KNOW
THEY ARE TIRED OF IT.
YOU KNOW --
[APPLAUSE]
THE
THE AMERICAN
[APPLAUSE]
THE AMERICAN DREAM,
THE AMERICAN DREAM, WE
[APPLAUSE]
THE AMERICAN DREAM, WE TALK
ABOUT
ABOUT IT.
AND
AND I
ABOUT IT.
AND I USED
AND I USED THE
ABOUT IT.
AND I USED THE EXPRESSION
AND I USED THE EXPRESSION A
ABOUT IT.
AND I USED THE EXPRESSION A LOT
--
-- THE
AND I USED THE EXPRESSION A LOT
-- THE AMERICAN
-- THE AMERICAN DREAM.
LOOK
LOOK AT
-- THE AMERICAN DREAM.
LOOK AT ALL
LOOK AT ALL THOSE
-- THE AMERICAN DREAM.
LOOK AT ALL THOSE CAMERAS
BLAZING
BLAZING BACK
LOOK AT ALL THOSE CAMERAS
BLAZING BACK THERE.
THIS
THIS IS
BLAZING BACK THERE.
THIS IS LIVE
THIS IS LIVE ALL
BLAZING BACK THERE.
THIS IS LIVE ALL OVER
THIS IS LIVE ALL OVER THE
BLAZING BACK THERE.
THIS IS LIVE ALL OVER THE PLACE.
ON
ON FOX,
THIS IS LIVE ALL OVER THE PLACE.
ON FOX, ON
ON FOX, ON CNN.
I
I GET
ON FOX, ON CNN.
I GET UP
I GET UP AND
ON FOX, ON CNN.
I GET UP AND I
I GET UP AND I SPEAK
ON FOX, ON CNN.
I GET UP AND I SPEAK FROM
I GET UP AND I SPEAK FROM THE
HEART.
I
I REALLY
HEART.
I REALLY DO.
LOOK,
LOOK, THERE
I REALLY DO.
LOOK, THERE IS
LOOK, THERE IS NOTHING.
I
I SPEAK
LOOK, THERE IS NOTHING.
I SPEAK FROM
I SPEAK FROM THE
LOOK, THERE IS NOTHING.
I SPEAK FROM THE HEART.
BUT
BUT --
I SPEAK FROM THE HEART.
BUT -- BUT
BUT -- BUT A
I SPEAK FROM THE HEART.
BUT -- BUT A BIG
BUT -- BUT A BIG PORTION,
I SPEAK FROM THE HEART.
BUT -- BUT A BIG PORTION, NOT
ALL
ALL OF
BUT -- BUT A BIG PORTION, NOT
ALL OF IT,
ALL OF IT, BUT
BUT -- BUT A BIG PORTION, NOT
ALL OF IT, BUT A
ALL OF IT, BUT A BIG
BUT -- BUT A BIG PORTION, NOT
ALL OF IT, BUT A BIG PORTION
ALL OF IT, BUT A BIG PORTION OF
THE
THE MEDIA,
ALL OF IT, BUT A BIG PORTION OF
THE MEDIA, THE
THE MEDIA, THE POLITICAL
ALL OF IT, BUT A BIG PORTION OF
THE MEDIA, THE POLITICAL MEDIA
IS
IS SO
THE MEDIA, THE POLITICAL MEDIA
IS SO DISHONEST.
THEY
THEY ARE
IS SO DISHONEST.
THEY ARE REALLY
THEY ARE REALLY DISHONEST
PEOPLE.
YOU
YOU PROBABLY
PEOPLE.
YOU PROBABLY HEARD
YOU PROBABLY HEARD ME
PEOPLE.
YOU PROBABLY HEARD ME SAY
YOU PROBABLY HEARD ME SAY I
ALWAYS
ALWAYS SAY
YOU PROBABLY HEARD ME SAY I
ALWAYS SAY I
ALWAYS SAY I LIKE
YOU PROBABLY HEARD ME SAY I
ALWAYS SAY I LIKE TO
ALWAYS SAY I LIKE TO SAVE
YOU PROBABLY HEARD ME SAY I
ALWAYS SAY I LIKE TO SAVE THE
AMERICAN
AMERICAN DREAM
ALWAYS SAY I LIKE TO SAVE THE
AMERICAN DREAM IS
AMERICAN DREAM IS DEAD
ALWAYS SAY I LIKE TO SAVE THE
AMERICAN DREAM IS DEAD BUT
AMERICAN DREAM IS DEAD BUT I'M
GOING
GOING TO
AMERICAN DREAM IS DEAD BUT I'M
GOING TO MAKE
GOING TO MAKE IT
AMERICAN DREAM IS DEAD BUT I'M
GOING TO MAKE IT BIGGER
GOING TO MAKE IT BIGGER AND
BETTER
BETTER AND
GOING TO MAKE IT BIGGER AND
BETTER AND STRONGER
BETTER AND STRONGER THAN
GOING TO MAKE IT BIGGER AND
BETTER AND STRONGER THAN EVER
BEFORE,
BEFORE, OK?
I
I SAY
BEFORE, OK?
I SAY IT
I SAY IT ALL
BEFORE, OK?
I SAY IT ALL THE
I SAY IT ALL THE TIME.
THE
THE AMERICAN
I SAY IT ALL THE TIME.
THE AMERICAN DREAM
THE AMERICAN DREAM IS
I SAY IT ALL THE TIME.
THE AMERICAN DREAM IS DEAD
THE AMERICAN DREAM IS DEAD BUT
I'M
I'M GOING
THE AMERICAN DREAM IS DEAD BUT
I'M GOING TO
I'M GOING TO MAKE
THE AMERICAN DREAM IS DEAD BUT
I'M GOING TO MAKE A
I'M GOING TO MAKE A BIGGER,
BETTER,
BETTER, STORM
I'M GOING TO MAKE A BIGGER,
BETTER, STORM OF
BETTER, STORM OF IT
I'M GOING TO MAKE A BIGGER,
BETTER, STORM OF IT EVER.
SO
SO I
BETTER, STORM OF IT EVER.
SO I GO
SO I GO HOME
BETTER, STORM OF IT EVER.
SO I GO HOME A
SO I GO HOME A MONTH
BETTER, STORM OF IT EVER.
SO I GO HOME A MONTH AGO.
MY
MY WIFE
SO I GO HOME A MONTH AGO.
MY WIFE SOME
MY WIFE SOME IS
SO I GO HOME A MONTH AGO.
MY WIFE SOME IS SPEAKING
MY WIFE SOME IS SPEAKING ON
TELEVISION.
AND
AND SHE
TELEVISION.
AND SHE SAID,
AND SHE SAID, DARLING,
TELEVISION.
AND SHE SAID, DARLING, THAT
AND SHE SAID, DARLING, THAT WAS
SUCH
SUCH A
AND SHE SAID, DARLING, THAT WAS
SUCH A HORRIBLE
SUCH A HORRIBLE THING
AND SHE SAID, DARLING, THAT WAS
SUCH A HORRIBLE THING YOU
SUCH A HORRIBLE THING YOU SAID.
IT
IT WAS
SUCH A HORRIBLE THING YOU SAID.
IT WAS SO
IT WAS SO NASTY.
I
I SAID,
IT WAS SO NASTY.
I SAID, WHAT
I SAID, WHAT DID
IT WAS SO NASTY.
I SAID, WHAT DID I
I SAID, WHAT DID I SAY?
YOU
YOU SAID
I SAID, WHAT DID I SAY?
YOU SAID THE
YOU SAID THE AMERICAN
I SAID, WHAT DID I SAY?
YOU SAID THE AMERICAN DREAM
YOU SAID THE AMERICAN DREAM IS
DEAD.
I
I SAID
DEAD.
I SAID IT
I SAID IT IS
DEAD.
I SAID IT IS DEAD,
I SAID IT IS DEAD, BUT
DEAD.
I SAID IT IS DEAD, BUT WE
I SAID IT IS DEAD, BUT WE ARE
GOING
GOING TO
I SAID IT IS DEAD, BUT WE ARE
GOING TO MAKE
GOING TO MAKE A
I SAID IT IS DEAD, BUT WE ARE
GOING TO MAKE A GREAT.
SO
SO I
GOING TO MAKE A GREAT.
SO I TURN
SO I TURN ON
GOING TO MAKE A GREAT.
SO I TURN ON TELEVISION.
I
I TURN
SO I TURN ON TELEVISION.
I TURN ON
I TURN ON TELEVISION
SO I TURN ON TELEVISION.
I TURN ON TELEVISION AND
I TURN ON TELEVISION AND I
SO I TURN ON TELEVISION.
I TURN ON TELEVISION AND I SEE
IT.
IT
IT SAYS,
IT.
IT SAYS, THE
IT SAYS, THE AMERICAN
IT.
IT SAYS, THE AMERICAN DREAM
IT SAYS, THE AMERICAN DREAM IS
DEAD.
PERIOD.
I
I SAID,
PERIOD.
I SAID, THAT
I SAID, THAT IS
PERIOD.
I SAID, THAT IS TERRIBLE.
IT
IT IS
I SAID, THAT IS TERRIBLE.
IT IS DISHONEST.
BUT
BUT THE
IT IS DISHONEST.
BUT THE FACT
BUT THE FACT IS,
IT IS DISHONEST.
BUT THE FACT IS, A
BUT THE FACT IS, A LOT
IT IS DISHONEST.
BUT THE FACT IS, A LOT OF
BUT THE FACT IS, A LOT OF PEOPLE
THINK
THINK IT
BUT THE FACT IS, A LOT OF PEOPLE
THINK IT IS
THINK IT IS DEAD.
AND
AND IT
THINK IT IS DEAD.
AND IT HAS
AND IT HAS GOT
THINK IT IS DEAD.
AND IT HAS GOT A
AND IT HAS GOT A LOT
THINK IT IS DEAD.
AND IT HAS GOT A LOT OF
PROBLEMS,
PROBLEMS, NO
AND IT HAS GOT A LOT OF
PROBLEMS, NO QUESTION
PROBLEMS, NO QUESTION ABOUT
AND IT HAS GOT A LOT OF
PROBLEMS, NO QUESTION ABOUT IT.
BUT
BUT WE
PROBLEMS, NO QUESTION ABOUT IT.
BUT WE ARE
BUT WE ARE GOING
PROBLEMS, NO QUESTION ABOUT IT.
BUT WE ARE GOING TO
BUT WE ARE GOING TO MAKE
PROBLEMS, NO QUESTION ABOUT IT.
BUT WE ARE GOING TO MAKE OUR
COUNTRY
COUNTRY GREAT
BUT WE ARE GOING TO MAKE OUR
COUNTRY GREAT AGAIN.
WE
WE ARE
COUNTRY GREAT AGAIN.
WE ARE GOING
WE ARE GOING TO
COUNTRY GREAT AGAIN.
WE ARE GOING TO DO
WE ARE GOING TO DO THINGS
COUNTRY GREAT AGAIN.
WE ARE GOING TO DO THINGS WITH
OUR
OUR COUNTRY
WE ARE GOING TO DO THINGS WITH
OUR COUNTRY --
[APPLAUSE]
THAT
THAT ARE
[APPLAUSE]
THAT ARE GOING
THAT ARE GOING TO
[APPLAUSE]
THAT ARE GOING TO BE
THAT ARE GOING TO BE SO
[APPLAUSE]
THAT ARE GOING TO BE SO GOOD
THAT ARE GOING TO BE SO GOOD AND
SO
SO SMART
THAT ARE GOING TO BE SO GOOD AND
SO SMART AND
SO SMART AND SO
THAT ARE GOING TO BE SO GOOD AND
SO SMART AND SO SPECTACULAR.
AND
AND WE
SO SMART AND SO SPECTACULAR.
AND WE GOING
AND WE GOING TO
SO SMART AND SO SPECTACULAR.
AND WE GOING TO BE
AND WE GOING TO BE RESPECTED
SO SMART AND SO SPECTACULAR.
AND WE GOING TO BE RESPECTED BY
THE
THE WORLD
AND WE GOING TO BE RESPECTED BY
THE WORLD AGAIN
THE WORLD AGAIN AND
AND WE GOING TO BE RESPECTED BY
THE WORLD AGAIN AND NOT
THE WORLD AGAIN AND NOT LAUGHED
IT
IT LIKE
THE WORLD AGAIN AND NOT LAUGHED
IT LIKE WE
IT LIKE WE ARE
THE WORLD AGAIN AND NOT LAUGHED
IT LIKE WE ARE ALL
IT LIKE WE ARE ALL A
THE WORLD AGAIN AND NOT LAUGHED
IT LIKE WE ARE ALL A BUNCH
IT LIKE WE ARE ALL A BUNCH OF
STUPID
STUPID PEOPLE.
IT
IT IS
STUPID PEOPLE.
IT IS NOT
IT IS NOT GOING
STUPID PEOPLE.
IT IS NOT GOING TO
IT IS NOT GOING TO GO
STUPID PEOPLE.
IT IS NOT GOING TO GO ON
IT IS NOT GOING TO GO ON ANY
LONGER.
WE
WE ARE
LONGER.
WE ARE NOT
WE ARE NOT GOING
LONGER.
WE ARE NOT GOING TO
WE ARE NOT GOING TO TAKE
LONGER.
WE ARE NOT GOING TO TAKE IT
WE ARE NOT GOING TO TAKE IT ANY
LONGER.
WE
WE ARE
LONGER.
WE ARE GOING
WE ARE GOING TO
LONGER.
WE ARE GOING TO MAKE
WE ARE GOING TO MAKE AMERICA
GREAT
GREAT AGAIN.
THANK
THANK YOU,
GREAT AGAIN.
THANK YOU, AND
THANK YOU, AND I
GREAT AGAIN.
THANK YOU, AND I LOVE
THANK YOU, AND I LOVE YOU,
PEOPLE.
I
I LOVE
PEOPLE.
I LOVE YOU
I LOVE YOU PEOPLE.
THANK
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU
THANK YOU VERY
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK
THANK YOU,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU, THANK
THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
THANK
THANK YOU.
(music)
WE'RE
WE'RE NOT
(music)
WE'RE NOT GONNA
WE'RE NOT GONNA TAKE
(music)
WE'RE NOT GONNA TAKE IT
NO,
NO, WE
WE'RE NOT GONNA TAKE IT
NO, WE AIN'T
NO, WE AIN'T GONNA
WE'RE NOT GONNA TAKE IT
NO, WE AIN'T GONNA TAKE
NO, WE AIN'T GONNA TAKE IT
WE'RE
WE'RE NOT
NO, WE AIN'T GONNA TAKE IT
WE'RE NOT GONNA
WE'RE NOT GONNA TAKE
NO, WE AIN'T GONNA TAKE IT
WE'RE NOT GONNA TAKE IT
WE'RE NOT GONNA TAKE IT ANYMORE
(music)
WE'RE
WE'RE NOT
(music)
WE'RE NOT GONNA
WE'RE NOT GONNA TAKE
(music)
WE'RE NOT GONNA TAKE IT
NO,
NO, WE
WE'RE NOT GONNA TAKE IT
NO, WE AIN'T
NO, WE AIN'T GONNA
WE'RE NOT GONNA TAKE IT
NO, WE AIN'T GONNA TAKE
NO, WE AIN'T GONNA TAKE IT
WE'RE
WE'RE NOT
NO, WE AIN'T GONNA TAKE IT
WE'RE NOT GONNA
WE'RE NOT GONNA TAKE
NO, WE AIN'T GONNA TAKE IT
WE'RE NOT GONNA TAKE IT
ANYMORE
(music)
MR.
MR. TRUMP:
(music)
MR. TRUMP: WAS
MR. TRUMP: WAS THAT
(music)
MR. TRUMP: WAS THAT GOOD?
>>
>> THINK
MR. TRUMP: WAS THAT GOOD?
>> THINK ABOUT
>> THINK ABOUT THE
MR. TRUMP: WAS THAT GOOD?
>> THINK ABOUT THE UNIONS.
MR.
MR. TRUMP:
>> THINK ABOUT THE UNIONS.
MR. TRUMP: I
MR. TRUMP: I WILL.
>>
>> THANK
MR. TRUMP: I WILL.
>> THANK YOU.
>>
>> YOU'RE
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE GREAT.
MR.
MR. TRUMP:
>> YOU'RE GREAT.
MR. TRUMP: THANK
MR. TRUMP: THANK YOU.
(music)
[INDISCERNIBLE]
[CAPTIONS
[CAPTIONS COPYRIGHT
[INDISCERNIBLE]
[CAPTIONS COPYRIGHT NATIONAL
CABLE
CABLE SATELLITE
[CAPTIONS COPYRIGHT NATIONAL
CABLE SATELLITE CORP.
CABLE SATELLITE CORP. 2015]
[CAPTIONING
[CAPTIONING PERFORMED
CABLE SATELLITE CORP. 2015]
[CAPTIONING PERFORMED BY
[CAPTIONING PERFORMED BY THE
NATIONAL
NATIONAL CAPTIONING
[CAPTIONING PERFORMED BY THE
NATIONAL CAPTIONING INSTITUTE,
WHICH
WHICH IS
NATIONAL CAPTIONING INSTITUTE,
WHICH IS RESPONSIBLE
WHICH IS RESPONSIBLE FOR
NATIONAL CAPTIONING INSTITUTE,
WHICH IS RESPONSIBLE FOR ITS
CAPTION
CAPTION CONTENT
WHICH IS RESPONSIBLE FOR ITS
CAPTION CONTENT AND
CAPTION CONTENT AND ACCURACY.
VISIT
VISIT NCICAP.ORG]
>>